Chapter 582: Secret 6

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Well, that's enough." Raffaele was grabbing Garen's hand, she liked to see his helpless expression. "Speaking of which, recently there's been a lot of stuff happening on my side as well. When it rains it pours, all kinds of troubles are starting to pile up, making me extremely busy. If it weren't for my sisters who came back from their universities, I think I wouldn't have any time left for even myself."

"There sure are a lot of people coming to the town recently."

"Yeah, all the inns are fully booked, and a lot of tourists have no choice but to stay in the townspeople's houses. However that's not a bad thing, and it gives everyone some bonus side income." Raffaele nodded, "It's probably because word of ‘that' got out to the public."

"That?" Garen didn't notice anything out of the particular.

"The biggest bear species, the Mika Bear, is supposedly the world's biggest species of bears ever discovered, breaking even the Brown Bear's record. It's almost a third bigger than the Brown Bear." Raffaele softly answered, "A lot of tourists are here to find out more about the Mika Bear, but the amount of Mika Bears are very few, in my entire life here I've only seen 2 of them."

"Is it really that big?" Garen was interested.

"It is, when standing, it can go up to 4 meters in height, however, it is non-hostile in nature and won't act aggressively towards humans unless provoked." Raffaele explained, "The 2 times I saw them was when they were out fishing."

Although it sounded ferocious, Raffaele showed no fear in her eyes.

Noticing this, Garen decided to change the topic.

"Oh right. I loved the Buck Badge you gave me last time, Can you bring me to see other similar antique items?"

"Err... That requires my grandma's permission…" Raffaele hesitated.

"I just want to look at them and admire them, you know how much I'm interested in antiques." Garen sincerely asked.

Raffaele already knew how fond Garen was of antiques, it could even be said that his knowledge in antiques had surpassed even that of experts, at least those shown on television series anyways, or so she felt. The more she started to understand Garen's strengths and weaknesses, the more she adored and loved this ideal man.

Although she was hailed as Grano's Strongest Witch with the strongest affinity for Ancient Power and her domination of all the witches from all the regional towns, besides that, Garen outshone her in every way.

"I'll go ask my grandma then. Like they say, Antiques are like the precious treasures of elders. They are very protective of them, it's not within my control whether she will let you see them."

"I understand." Garen nodded, his potential points had not increased even after all these years.

Recently, his secret technique progression entered a slow state, and without potential points, all he could do was to grind it out with time. The degree of growth had hit new extremes of slowness, and if he wanted to get back to his previous form, it'd have to take a lot longer.

Potential points could largely decrease the needed time and give him a distinct advantage. As such, he needed to utilize it as soon as possible.

After killing that vampire and measuring his strength, Garen started to feel an urgent need to increase his abilities and get back to his previous form as soon as possible. Otherwise, if he met a stronger Blood Breed someday or faced an unknown power, he wouldn't know how to react. With the power he had right now, it would be a suicide mission.

His experience and technique did make up for some of his lack of power, but that was only in a situation where the power difference wasn't too huge. If he had to face an opponent much stronger than him, he'd be in trouble.

Furthermore, regarding whether the Blood Breed was actually immortal, that statement piqued his interest.

"I'll give you an answer latest by the day after tomorrow. As you know, my grandma is a very strict person, I'll try to ask her when she's in a good mood." Raffaele said apologetically.

"Thanks!" Garen gave her a kiss on her right cheek and pulled her back into his embrace.

Regarding Raffaele, he had very complicated feelings, his identity in this world naturally accepted her, but the Garen hidden deep in his heart seemed to treat this as nothing more than a game.

Maybe Raffaele felt that hence she was reluctant to give her first time to him.

Garen had lived through 2 worlds and he had already become used to keeping all his feelings to himself. In comparison with Raffaele's astounding age, he would not easily accept her as well.

He had already planned to take matters into his own hands if her grandmother declined his request and use the antiques in secret, hopefully activating an effect on his progression.

After chatting for a bit on the beach, catching and cooking some scallops, the two saw that it was almost time, so Garen got on his bike and bid farewell to Raffaele.

Raffaele saw Garen off, her long hair swaying in the sea breeze.

A young girl in a grey shirt walked out from the crevices of the rocks from a small distance away and stood next to her.

Looking at the infatuated expression of her chief, she let out a helpless sigh.

From the point of view of others, regardless of whether it was the Blood Breed or the Witches, their chiefs were prideful and cold. The monstrous beauty that people call the Strongest Witch had revealed her horns since the very beginning, during which she managed to recruit all of the witches in the Alice Forest area. She was known to the witches in the other areas as the Sun's Will. This nickname was due to her overwhelming willpower; as strong as the sun's rays, inexorable, and a powerful leader.

In the early years, after a meeting with North America's chief of the Witches - the Moonlight's Darkness, Raffaele was unanimously nominated to be the 3rd strongest witch in America. Her talent was monstrous, she had a strong heart, and left a strong impression on the Blood Breeds and the Witches from other countries who were there to witness her presence.

However, this great being, the Queen Witch of the Forest, was now infatuated with such a normal boy.

"What's the matter?" Raffaele looked at her sisters on her sides.

"Nothing much, we were just jealous of your pure relationship with Garen." The girl muttered, "Maybe I should follow your example and use a hidden identity to find a nice guy that isn't after my position. That kind of relationship should be pure, right?"

Raffaele started giggling, and her smile had a sense of warmth that no outsider had ever seen.

******

"Sis, can we really live here for a period of time?" Arisa asked, wide-eyed staring at Isaros.

The sisters were walking side by side in the town center, following closely behind Jason and Vivien who were leading the way. They seem to have not heard the sisters' conversation.

Isaros carefully assessed the surroundings.

"This seems like a place the Primary Colours cannot get into, they haven't found our trail, if we remain hidden for long enough, we can live here for quite some time."

"That's great!" Arisa couldn't resist the joy and started skipping around gleefully.

"Don't worry, if we plan this well enough, they might never be able to find us in this lifetime," Isaros smiled while patting Arisa's head.

The Primary Colours, Asia's strongest shadow syndicate, had countless connections with numerous governments and also a strong standing in the Asian underground world. Their leader was Rabstein Cairo, the board chairman of the third largest financial group in the world and the owner of numerous banks, energy companies, firearm dealers, and black markets.

The Primary Colours as a whole was like a monster, having a major influence in every field, from military to politics, and legal to black markets. The sisters were merely average European girls born in a wealthy family, but because their genes were appropriate for the human strengthening experimentations of the Primary Colors, their families and lives were destroyed. Miraculously, they'd managed to escape during one of the experiments, and their life on the run had somehow led them to Grano.

Thinking back to how the Primary Colors managed to send elite military-trained soldiers and their multiple attempts of kidnappings, it sent a shiver down her spine as she reached out to softly caress the scar on her sister's neck.

No one would have thought, that scar was the aftermath of a near-fatal slash to the neck that should've killed her. If it was not for the increased regenerative abilities from the experimentation upon her, her sister Arisa would have entered an eternal slumber.

She had originally considered claiming revenge, but against a monster that had completely dominated the entirety of Asia, taking care of them was as simple as sending out some hired soldiers, mercenaries, and assassins. There were even more rumors about their underground sector having acquired technology like mutant soldiers and killing machines. The entire organization had completely conquered Asia's underground world, if they used their true power against the sisters, they wouldn't even stand a chance.

Isaros did not want her sister to suffer anymore. She was so young, yet she already experienced countless near-death incidents...

Even if she wanted to get revenge, thinking of the amount of increasingly powerful opponents and the Primary Colour's seamless authority over Asia, it sent a chill down her spine. In the experimentation lab, she'd once seen that terrifying man - Rabstein Cairo. He had a nickname back there - Titan.

That man gave off a strong fear-inducing aura, making even someone like her, who'd survived the experiments, tremble uncontrollably in fear. That strong aura made a glance at him feel as though she was a baby facing off against a ferocious lion.

"Who cares about revenge… I should just give up. As long as Arisa is happy and safe…" Isaros lightly nudged Arisa's back, letting her walk together with Vivien. The two started happily chatting with each other.

From the front, Jason kept looking back to steal a glance at her, making her chuckle.

This household that lived peacefully in this little town of Grano, having no qualms with the world, left a strong impression on her. After chatting with Jason for a bit, Jason blurted out every detail he could about his family.

Their parents were the standard intellectuals, were kind to others, but spend a lot of their time on their own work.

Their children were all somewhat mature. The oldest child, Jason was very muscular, with a huge body. He liked to practice martial arts, and overall, was just a pure-hearted upper-secondary student.

Their second son, Garen, was the most mature of them all, his position in their household hierarchy seemed to be higher than Jason's. He was immensely handsome, had a calm demeanor, liked to play the violin, and was one of the most popular kids in school. There were even rumors that there were multiple girls fighting over him.

Their youngest daughter, Vivien, was still a young kid, pure and energetic, sometimes weird in a cute way. She adored his brother Garen but also liked to tease and play pranks on Jason.

This tight-knit family had Isaros a bit of envy. On the other hand, Arisa was completely immersed in the atmosphere, becoming best friends with Vivien within such a short period of time, even sharing all her treats with her, making the actual sister feel a bit jealous.

Chapter 583: Secret Technique and Reward 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Do you know why seahorses are so slow?"

Garen looked back and asked Isaros a strange question.

Isaros thought for a bit, then shook her head. "I don't know."

"Because seahorses are the smallest horse! Hahahahaha…" Jason started laughing out loud.

Isaros looked at him silently, the other two young ones were also speechlessly staring at him.

Out of the 4 people, he was the only one laughing.

"Hahaha… Err… Haha… Didn't you guys find that funny?" Jason finally stopped laughing. Looking at the 3 cringing people before him, he realized how lame his joke was.

"Err… Alright… Alright, let me tell another joke."

******

As he slowly maneuvered his motorcycle into his garage, he noticed that no one else was here.

The house was completely empty, needless to say, Alma and Trish had both gone off to do their own research work.

After securing his bike, he opened the door to his house, took off his shoes, then swiftly shut the door.

He had no clue why, but his mind was still lingering on the strange feeling he got from the sisters, the soul seed wouldn't have this kind of reaction for no reason.

The strange yet familiar feeling was exactly the same as when he was viewing the planet history in the Totem World.

Quickly moving to his room, he took out his laptop and connected to the web.

After browsing through the news about Grano, he found the first result was the Mika Bear. The appearance of the world's largest bear species in this forest had attracted tourists not just to Grano, but also to multiple far-off small towns.

In other news, there were more articles on wild wolves attacking humans, leaving 1 dead and 1 wounded. Other than that, nothing much had happened.

Closing the laptop, Garen went into deep thought.

Crack!

A sudden crisp cracking could be heard from downstairs. If it was any other person, they would've probably thought that this was because some parts of the material of this wooden house had broke.

However, Garen regained his calm, silently stood up, walked towards the door and lightly pulled on it. The door opened smoothly and silently.

He slowly peered down from the railing of the 2nd-floor staircase.

There was a bald man in a black leather coat, calmly walking around the room without making a sound. He was looking left and right as if he was searching for something.

On his black leather coat, there was an image of a white phoenix stitched on the chest area. A muscular guy wearing a coat with a stitching of a white phoenix, it seemed weird. However, this person didn't seem to care; his face was as emotionless as a piece of wood and his skin appeared like there was no blood circulating under it, as though he was wearing a mask.

Garen silently observed his movement around the building. Ignoring all other rooms, he walked straight towards Arisa's bedroom. He reached his hand out the touch the bedroom door, then suddenly raised his head.

The second-floor common space was completely empty, not a soul in sight.

The baldie frowned, slightly pushed open the door to Vivien's bedroom. However, he did not enter the room, he just stood in the doorway and sniffed a bit.

"Isaros's scent isn't present." He muttered in a soft voice, he spoke in Classical Arabic, which was written as Asia's Quran Language.

Garen once spent half a year learning all of the major languages in the world. At his current skill level, he could completely understand what the man was saying.

Only then did he notice that the man was wearing a black earpiece.

"There were some traces over here, it must've been her." From the earpiece came a soft female voice.

"Looks like they've temporarily left the house to play, this time the mission is quite easy." The baldie said with a small grin.

"Don't be too careless. Earlier, all my D-ranked men were wiped out, something must be up." The voice said.

"Don't worry, I'm not like that D-ranked garbage." The baldie laughed lazily.

He quickly closed the door and retraced his steps back to where he originally came from. At the same time, he was holding a long pole with a fluffy circular cloth on one end, wiping away his footsteps as he left.

In no time, all traces of the baldie's entrance had been removed, he then swiftly closed the door and left.

This entire time, he did not go up to the second floor, probably because he already knew there were people upstairs.

After the door closed, Garen's silhouette emerged behind the door. Looking through the door viewer, seeing the baldie's back as he walked off, he couldn't help but let out a small grin on his face.

"The aura of potential…"

He lightly touched the places where the baldie had reached to touch, that tingling familiar aura turned his bad mood around completely.

"That baldie is probably from some organization hunting for Arisa and her sister, his body had remnants of potential aura… Looks like there is stuff with potential in this world after all. This is great news." Garen started smiling.

He suddenly remembered about the weird feeling he got from the sisters.

It was the same feeling he got off of Beckstone and Goth at the start. It was a special reaction of the soul, an indescribable feeling without a clear cause.

If one had to describe it, it would be that it felt influential.

Similar to Beckstone and Goth, Arisa and her sister should be very influential trendsetters, like the first domino in a domino show. More accurately, they could be said to be the leading actors in a paradigm shift, like the butterflies in the butterfly effect, with just one flutter of their wings, it could start a chain reaction of small influences, adding up together creating even stronger forces, and eventually becoming a gigantic tornado.

Taking out his phone and checking the time, Garen sent a message to Raffaele.

In almost an instant, he got a reply.

"Already reached home, don't worry, I'll take care of myself"

"That's good"

Garen didn't want to cause trouble or damage on Raffaele's side so he followed the vampire's instructions, even though he did leave a bit earlier.

Softly opening the door, Garen observed his surroundings. It didn't seem that there were any people from Raffaele tasked to protect him. The baldie was also nowhere to be seen.

He sniffed around for a bit, then walked out of his yard in a carefree manner, headed towards the byway on the left side of the road.

No one bothered about the actions of a 10+-year-old boy. It was noon and most people were at home eating lunch, and there were barely any cars on the road, nor were there any passersby. You could only hear some vague conversations from the houses.

The sun was shining brightly, baking the ground.

Garen was walking on a grassy field, Grano's forests were different from a lot of other places, the grass here grew extremely tall, and could grow up to one's knees, completely covering one's shins.

Normally people had to pay attention to where they were walking due to the presence of poisonous bugs and snakes, but Garen was completely carefree about that, instead, he was completely focused on finding the baldie.

Slowly, the number of trees started increasing, from just a few trees scattered about into a condensed canopy blocking out all sunlight.

After a short while, in a small bush tucked between two trees, he saw two silhouettes in black leather coats. One of them was obviously the baldie who left his house just a moment ago, while the other was a black haired girl with a bombshell body.

"Are you guys crazy? Wearing black leather in this kind of weather." Garen laughed as he walked over.

"Who's there!"

The baldie roared, looking towards his direction.

With the two's alerted gazes on him, Garen slowly walked out of the bush, stepping on some tree roots protruding from the ground.

"The two of you just visited me a moment ago, how can you have forgotten the owner already?"

He laughed with his hands tucked into his pockets.

Baldie looked as if he saw a ghost, looking over to the lady next to him in uncertainty. She shook her head, stating that she didn't know what was going on either.

"Who are you?"

His hand was gripping onto his suppressed handgun on his waist.

"What organization are the two of you from? Why did you sneak into my house?" Garen ignored their actions, though now changing his language, speaking fluently in Classical Arabic, shocking the two.

"Fire!"

The baldie did a combat roll and pulled out another black handgun. In a flash, he fired 3 bullets. Without even looking at the aftermath, he swiftly hid behind a tree.

The lady also did the same thing, except in the other direction.

6 bullets were fired spread out in the area Garen was standing. Even if Garen did not move, it would have hit him right in the forehead and at his heart.

However, right before they fired, Garen tensed his body up and leaped forward into the bush, almost as if a slithering cobra, he rushed towards the baldie. Out of the 6 bullets, none of them hit their mark.

He swiped his right arm forward.

Hiss.

His arm suddenly curved as if it was a noodle, going around the tree and pinning the hiding baldie to the tree.

His nails turned into sharp black claws, looking almost metallic, and pinned the baldie to the tree by his neck.

The lady on the other side looked as if she'd just seen a demon. Garen swiftly jumped in front of the baldie, his face still smiling.

"Now will you answer my question?"

"Y… Yes…" The baldie gulped and motioned for the lady to drop her gun. His face was completely pale and his heart was beating like crazy, one small movement and he was done for. Looking at his opponent's black claws, he knew that this time he had kicked a hornet's nest.

"What do you want to know sir? I swear we won't hide anything from you, sir." He answered quickly without any resistance.

"Who are you guys? What business do you have over here?"

"We are from the Asian White Phoenix society, we were hired as mercenaries to come over to recover the escaped test subjects."

"Asian White Phoenix? What kind of organization is that?"

"It's one of the main combat branches of the Primary Colors, as for the Primary Colors Organization you can probably find out a lot more about them online, sir."

"Then, what are you referring to when you say test subjects?"

"I really don't know, sir. We are only external mercenaries, we have no clue about the backstory of the targets, as, sir, you may know, knowing too much isn't always a good thing." The baldie answered sheepishly.

"So the test subjects are Arisa and Isaros?"

"Yes, sir. Our objective was to capture them alive and we were to only take action if we truly were unable to capture them alive."

Chapter 584: Secret Technique and Reward 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen looked over at the lady, the two seemed to be a married couple. She was worriedly staring at the claws wrapped tightly around the baldie's neck, trying to not move even a single inch.

The two were only mercenaries trained by the military. Their abilities with firearms were definitely exceptional and their reaction speed was quick as well, but compared to a real Grandmaster of Combat, they would be defeated instantly.

The same could be said if they were to fight against the monstrous beings in the town.

The two were just average humans, and as the baldie said himself, they were just hired mercenaries.

However, Garen's objective was not that simple.

He carefully looked through the pockets of the baldie, swiftly ripping out a small black wooden cross from his robes.

The moment he made contact with that cross, a cooling aura flowed through his arm, and a sparkle blinked to life in his eyes.

"Where did you get this thing?"

The baldie's face seemed to wince in pain.

"This is a souvenir from a friend, a very good friend of mine. He asked me to always carry it and to never let it out of my sight."

"What a great souvenir," Garen purred, satisfied.

This cross definitely contained some potential aura, not the type that was for one-time-use, but the type that continuously flowed.

The surface of the cross seemed to be covered by a layer of shapeless energy as if it could burst any moment.

Garen guessed that this was the type of charm that was used against supernatural beings. If it came in contact with a supernatural being, it would burst immediately to protect baldie.

Baldie's friend was obviously worried about him getting into life-threatening trouble, so he gave him this necklace.

"Looks like your friend is a great guy." Garen ripped off the necklace. His original killing intent towards the two had completely been dispersed. He started to think about how he could manipulate this two to work for him.

After all, his sources of information right now were extremely limited, it was almost none other than the Internet. If he had two people with different identities he could use as his eyes and ears, his understanding of this world would increase even more.

There were many ways to manipulate an enemy, but since he did not have any understanding of the unknown powers lurking in this world, it was difficult to find a way that can guarantee success…

This world was full of vampires and quite possibly witches as well, and possibly other supernatural beings. At the surface level, this world seemed simple, but it was only the tip of the iceberg.

Looking through his memories of past secret techniques, Garen decided to use a stealthier secret technique.

If it was purely for punishing an individual, even the lowest tier skill would do, but to ensure the loyalty of the individual, this was the best method.

Looking at the baldie, he let out a meaningful laugh. Garen loosened his grip on the baldie's neck.

"Thank you for all the information, but as you guys can see, this is not a town that you can mess around in. From our conversation earlier, I felt your sincerity and I applaud you for that."

He paused for a moment, "Since you guys are mercenaries, I have a mission for you guys, I was wondering if you guys would like to accept."

"You're not gonna kill us?" The baldie asked, looking visibly relieved.

"I'm not some bloodthirsty serial killer, why would I want to kill you?" Garen opened his arms, "This mission, if you guys manage to succeed, I might consider taking you guys on as disciples and teach you that powerful Battle Skill you guys saw just now."

There was a sparkle in the baldie's eyes, not only him, even the black-haired lady unconsciously gulped.

Only mercenaries like them who have been in countless near-death scenarios would understand how useful having that kind of battle skill would be in combat. Furthermore, if they could be like this kid in front of them, with that terrifying reach and complete lack of fear of firearms, it was the ultimate killing ability. The opportunity to learn this skill, in the eyes of the couple, posed an irresistible temptation.

"Are you serious?! You're really willing to take us as apprentices and teach us that frightful technique?" Even baldie's voice was audibly trembling. Although what was in front of him looked just like an average looking 10-year-old boy, at this point, he had completely ignored the age of the being in front of him.

The lady at his side was still in shock, she opened her mouth trying to speak, but the words wouldn't come out. She helplessly looked at the baldie, letting him handle everything.

"Of course." Garen smiled. The assassination skills he had accumulated were countless, not to mention that since he was a master in the human body's structure and a Grandmaster of Combat, his expertise in human combat could allow him to create a simple killing technique in a blink of an eye.

Furthermore, a simple technique to him could be considered a top tier ability to others.

"Then sir, what is your mission?" Baldie cautiously asked. This kind of amazing reward must come with a steep cost.

"It's simple actually." Garen raised up the wooden cross in his hand. "You see, I'm very interested in antique items, especially this kind of antiques. I want you to find out the origin and history of this item, and to find out if there are more of these similar items. Of course, it would be much better if you could find them."

At the sight of the two confused mercenaries, he tossed the cross into the air.

"From a quick assessment, this cross has at least 80 years of history, you guys can start from there."

"If it's to find out about this cross, I have an idea." The baldie proudly exclaimed.

"Are you sure?" Garen asked with joy.

"Yes, 100%." The baldie answered reassuringly, "I once saw some information about these crosses at the organization, the number of crosses isn't a lot, but the price isn't too high as well. They are often sold off as accessories."

Garen gave him a strong pat on his shoulders.

"Great job. As a reward, let me give you a preview of what I will teach you. You guys can then decide whether this job is worth accepting or not."

There was a fire ignited in the duo's eyes.

...

2 hours later...

Garen slowly walked out of the woods onto the road, his hands were in his pockets as usual as he walked towards his home.

That wooden cross was in his pocket, and he was gripping onto it tightly.

Hints of an icy aura kept flowing into his palm, slowly moving through his arms, to his shoulders and finally to his brain.

Looking at his skill pane, then once again feeling the total amount of aura the cross contained, Garen estimated that this cross could provide him with at least 3 attribute points, which equated to 300% of potential value, and that was a very conservative estimate.

After such a long, dry period with zero growth in potential value, suddenly earning so much boosted his mood tremendously.

He suddenly started having a much better impression of Arisa and her sister. Upon the sisters' arrival, he'd immediately managed to capture someone who gave him potential points. Maybe even more of the White Phoenix Primary Color or whatever people would come, and his potential points will slowly accumulate even more.

Looking back to the baldie and his wife learning secret techniques.

Garen let out a sly smirk, they were his feeler tentacles, from now on, he would no longer be like before, lacking information on the underground world.

The skill he'd taught them wasn't a complete secret technique. Without the support of a real secret technique, it was naturally impossible for it to be a strong secret skill.

Furthermore, it was a secret skill that Garen had created on the spot; as the name suggested, it was the middle point between a skill and a secret technique. The learning prerequisites were low, so anyone could learn it, but it would cause certain harm to the user's body when using it. It was a skill that sacrificed one's own health to increase one's ability.

Although it could only power you up for a short period of time, it was still an extremely useful skill for the couple.

Garen called this new skill the Shooting Shadow. It was a shooting type support secret skill which could stimulate certain nodes on the user's body, allowing it to double their sight, hearing, and reflexes for 30 minutes. To them, this was the ultimate trump card.

And this was only the 1st level of this skill, there were a total of 6 levels.

The amount of sacrifice for each level was the same, it may even decrease, but its effects would only get stronger as one progressed.

At level 6, this skill could amplify sight, hearing, and reflexes by up to 6 times.

This made the couple pay full attention to Garen, with his support, they finally managed to attain Level 1 of this simple secret skill. After feeling the strength of the skill, the two were completely set on working for Garen.

The side effects of this skill were very damaging; every time it was used, it would cause internal damage to the user's body, but this kind of damage wasn't obvious. Every time it was used, the user would need to rest for at least 3 months, otherwise, if the skill was used repeatedly in short succession, it would lead to irreversible damage to the body, like blindness or deafness.

That was the biggest difference between secret techniques and secret skills. Secret skills came at a huge cost and couldn't be used continuously.

Secret Techniques, on the other hand, had no major side effects and could be used repeatedly. Just like Palosa's 99 Acute Airholes, which gave him his reputation as the unrivaled master he was from the beginning.

The reason the secret skill Shooting Shadow was so strong was that, when Garen was guiding the two, he used some of his own aura as a primer to stimulate a certain amount of change in their bodies, allowing them to master the skill.

What they didn't know was that if they wanted to continue training for this skill and get to the next level, they had to find Garen and have him stimulate their bodies again.

In other words, their growth was all up to Garen.

There was also one other disadvantage to secret skills.

It was they could only be improved and could not be abandoned.

Once you learned a secret skill, it was like walking into a dead end, and you could only continue to train. If you don't get to the highest level but stop your training for a prolonged period of time, you will experience intense pain and your body will slowly deteriorate until your death.

Regarding this point, Garen was prepared to improve it a bit more.

After all, secret skills were just something he created at the moment, he needed time to perfect it.

When he reached home, he started to record all his memories down. At dinner time, his parents were finally home, and so were Jason, Vivien and the sisters who'd spent their day outside playing. Under their parents' invitation, the sisters also joined the family for dinner.

Garen sent Raffaele a text.

The reply stated that everything was fine, the other party did not try any of their schemes.

Now that his two feeler tentacles were sent out, all he needed to do was to wait for their reports. He had also gotten his hands on his first batch of potential points, putting Garen in a cheery mood, and he gleefully gazed at Arisa and his sister.

If this was successful, he could obtain even more crosses, giving him even more potential points. Everything was going according to plan, and with his strength rapidly increasing, he could soon find an opportunity to find out more about the vampires.

It was still early anyway, he was still a lower-secondary student going into upper-secondary next year, and was still young.

Chapter 585: Accident 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Time passed by.

Raffaele's grandmother had rejected Garen's invitation in the end. Raffaele felt very sorry about this and sent a lot of old things to him as compensation.

High school life was no different from Junior High, other than the workload of their studies becoming heavier, but for Garen it was negligible.

After he'd finished absorbing Black Wood Cross, due to the fact that his mental age was too disconnected from the students around him, without Raffaele to accompany him, he would be alone most of the time.

He would go to the music classroom alone to practice, and would also find an empty room to practice his battle skills.

He practiced his battle skills slowly. On the surface, he was merely practicing outer martial arts for his health but as long as he was willing, he could produce a deadly force in an instant from these stretches.

Garen did not have friends other than Raffaele, whereas Raffaele had a lot of friends or rather, subordinates. These two always had one common point, something that maintained their relationship, which was loneliness.

Even if these two were lovers, they had never let each other know their secrets.

No matter it was Garen or Raffaele, they were the same.

Yet, it was due to this, they felt that compared to other people, their distance was much closer.

These few years were plain, nothing big happened in town except that a Mica bear was ‘invited' to leave by the National Zoo.

******************

In the afternoon, the air was warm as the sun baked the ground, and withering leaves were scattered by the errant breeze.

Behind the school outside the music classroom

A slender young boy was standing on the podium in the music classroom and a gentle melodious tune could be heard.

Softly, peacefully as though a person was walking quietly on a boundless field. Moonlight glimmering in the night accompanied by a refreshing cold breeze, stillness in the heart.

The boy had white and delicate skin, a neutral gender face and golden short hair.

Black shirt and slim black trousers perfectly outlined his slender figure.

By the windows of the music classroom were rows of unknown trees. A golden-haired girl was sitting on the windowsill, quietly listening to the melody. The sunlight glimmered on her white dress, leaving patches of white and gold.

"It's Michael Sidd's I Hope?" When the sound of the violin ended, the girl casually asked.

"You got it right again." Garen put down the violin and carefully began its maintenance work. This violin was specially bought by his mother from one of her old friends, spending 200,000 Gallons. If this was on Earth, it would be spending over 200,000 US Dollars, although this violin's greatest worth was in collector's value.

"I don't even need to guess. I've heard so many times." Raffaele combed down her hair with her hand.

"Which school are you going? Your SIT score is over 2300, there shouldn't be any problem for you?"

Garen walked over to the window and rested his hands on the window's side.

"Quite, I'm planning to go to Gullivier. The family's supporting too."

"I don't think I can go there." Raffaele twirled her hair with her finger. "I took the test five times, but the highest I could get was 2000 points. I don't think I can keep up with you. My family's suggestion is the state's university."

"Studying in the state?"

"Mhm."

Garen went silent. After all, they'd been together for so long, affection for her had slowly grown.

He could still remember Raffaele's heart-shaped candles that'd caused a commotion among the students during the night.

Over the years, she'd come to pick him up almost every morning. Occasionally, for a period of time, she would send him a variety of flowers in bouquets of 99. In everyone's eyes, this was incredibly romantic.

Undoubtedly, Raffaele was passionate. Perhaps in her heart, she desired someone to truly understand her and become a shelter for her heart.

"Gullivier…that's the best school in the whole of America. Perhaps this is for the best, you and your family shouldn't have come to this countryside." Raffaele was a bit down-hearted.

"I will be back again." Garen smiled, "My family is not moving, what are you worried about?"

"The outside world is very exciting…" Raffaele was obviously a little moody.

"Don't you think that mentioning to other people that your boyfriend is a Gullivier student, it sounds cool?" Garen put his hand on her shoulder.

"Who knows? After you go there, would you still put ordinary countryside girls in your eyes?" Raffaele was jealous. After knowing Garen's family background, she knew that the gap between their families was too great.

On the surface, his father was a university professor and his mother was a psychologist who had some reputation and Garen himself was talented and beautiful, skilled in violin and cultured, totally different from other students.

This was also the reason she could not take her eyes off him.

As for her, if her identity as a witch was taken away, she would just be an ordinary countryside girl who was a bit pretty and wild. Compared to those enchanting city girls who knew how to put on makeup, the gap was obvious.

Even if she exposed her identity as a witch, it was useless, perhaps it might even scare Garen.

Her first love, perhaps it was really the end…

While thinking so, Raffaele looked up into Garen's eyes.

"You will remember me right?"

"Don't make it seems like a drama where we're separating for life." Garen pulled on her cheeks. "We're not shooting a film. I'm not going to disappear."

Gullivier University was synonymous with Earth's top few universities like Harvard, Yale and so on, one of the best universities in America. The ranks among these top three were constantly interchanging.

This kind of university not only looked at the SIT score but also examined other aspects. Garen's parents were also one of his admission factors.

SIT was like American university's SAT and ACT on Earth, splitting into two parts and using the integrated scores. All American universities used this system. The students could take the tests multiple times or only one time if they were satisfied with their results.

After Garen figured out all of this, he had gone to apply for the examination earlier on and easily got himself a score of 2345 points. This was after his adjustments because the full score was only 2400 points…

Raffaele also went with him. Unfortunately, perhaps because her education was focused not on this aspect but on witchcraft, her results were not that good. The highest score she ever got was only 2000 points.

"After you're gone, nobody will be here to talk to me." Raffaele also pulled at Garen's cheeks, but he immediately escaped, so she went after him.

"After you go to a new school, you will be able to make new friends." Garen laughed. "To be so easily worried at such a young age, you will go bald in the future."

"You're the bald one!" Raffaele was mad and reached out to pull at Garen's hair but Garen still managed to dodge. By the window, one was clawing and the other was dodging.

Du…Du…

Raffaele's phone rang, it only had a simple dudu sound, no music or whatsoever.

She halted her attempts.

"I'm going to get you for this!" after dropping a stereotypical villain's line, she took out her phone and went to a place further away to answer.

Garen stood by the window, watching her answering her phone. She waved at him.

"I'm going ahead, there's something I need to deal with!"

"Okay! I'm also going back!" Garen nodded.

Looking at Raffaele on her motorbike roaring away, Garen smiled. He had not told Raffaele that he was leaving tonight. This mysterious town, he could make out the situation now.

Witches and Vampires both ruled this town. The Witches were guarding something and the Vampires had a certain understanding of them. They were vigilant of outsiders. These two were maintaining a seemingly fragile but solid relationship.

Grano town was not famous among ordinary people, but in the world of Witches and Vampires, it should be a rather important place.

Garen would sometimes catch some foreign Vampires and interrogate them. This basic information, he was familiar with it.

This world's Vampires and Blood Breed had a strict hierarchy which was maintained by control.

High-level Blood Breed controlled low-level Blood Breed unless a special means was used to avoid it.

Garen was not clear about high-level Blood Breed but he knew about the general hierarchy among Blood Breed.

The first one was Death Apostle which was the highest level Garen knew.

The second one was Upper-level Blood Breed, the third one was Middle-level Blood Breed and then Lower-level Blood Breed. The last one was the Vampires.

Vampires were only common cannon fodder which the Blood Breed looked down upon. In fact, they were not even recognized as part of the Blood Breed clan. No matter what method they had, they could not avoid the fate of being under the control of the Blood Breed. Simply put, as long as they met a Blood Breed, they could only be unconditionally controlled.

However, although Vampires were only the Blood Breed's cannon fodder, to ordinary people, they had a control ability which was synonymous with hypnosis.

They called this ability "charm".

Death Apostle, Upper-level Blood Breed, Middle-level Blood Breed, Lower-level Blood Breed, and Vampires. That was all the information Garen could gather from the vampires' mouth.

Lower-level Blood Breed could freely convert Vampires, Middle-level Blood Breed could convert Lower level Blood Breed and so on. Death Apostle could convert Upper-level Blood Breed. This was the source of their absolute hierarchy.

Unlike the Blood Breed on Earth, the Blood Breed here did not fear sunlight, not even the Vampires. They only feared silverware.

The division level among witches was based on the vampires.

Death Apostle Witch, Upper-level Witch, Middle-level Witch, Lower-level Witch and Spirit Seekers. This division was according to their strength. Garen had never seen how Witches fight so he did not know their fighting style and strength but based on this mysterious town, they were most likely very strong.

Chapter 586: Accident 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen focused more on the Blood Breed's position.

The entire Blood Breed was roughly divided into two factions or tendencies: the light party and the secret party.

Light party: Due to the fact that the Blood Breed's origin in this world was human, they regarded themselves as humans that had undergone evolution to becoming advanced humans. Therefore they should be the elite of the elites, the leader of humanity.

This faction's opinion was that they were part of the humans' society. They maintained order and dominated a large part of this world.

Secret party: This faction of Blood Breed had bloody tendencies. They regarded themselves as higher species and humans as food and livestock. Just like rearing cattle and sheep, they could eat the humans whenever they wanted. They belonged to higher species and did not consider themselves as part of the human society. This faction of Blood Breed were terrorists. They destroyed the order and were in conflict with the light party.

However, these two tendencies were only a fad, not real parties. Some Blood Breed might change their way of thinking over time and changed from light party to secret party. Some secret party Blood Breed might integrate with the humans because they fell in love with humans, changing from secret party to light party.

As long as it was not obvious conflicts, there would be no dispute between the two sides.

On the whole, apart from Blood Breeds and Witches, there were no other supernatural forces. It seemed this world was ruled together by Blood Breeds and Witches.

This made Garen feel weird but at the same time, he understood why the towns' women had higher status than men. It was because the women held mystical powers.

Excluding Witches and Blood Breeds, although the remaining humans had advanced technology, in the face of Blood Breeds and Vampires, they were too weak.

They were like predators. Even the lowest Vampires could control humans and even make them commit suicide easily.

The ability to charm humans, terrifying speed and regenerative ability. Even the top Grandmaster of Combat could barely fight against Vampires.

However, excluding a few areas, the number of Blood Breeds and Vampires were very limited. They had restrictions on their reproduction. Even the Vampires were not free of that restrictions.

This was Garen's conclusion after carefully studying the components of the Vampires' blood.

Their core was Blood Nucleus. Although the name contained 'Nucleus', unless the blood was totally dried up, it could not be found. This was the essence of Blood Breed which appeared in their heart when their blood was completely let out.

Blood Nucleus required a higher level Blood Breed to separate a trace of their own Blood Nucleus to inject into a body that was sucked dry of blood, as a foundation to turn them into a lower level Blood Breed.

At this stage, the Blood Nucleus would go through differentiation, this process consumed their own Blood Nucleus.

Blood Nucleus was their root and their source of life. As long as their Blood Nucleus was not extinguished, apart from having their head blew up, they could regenerate and recover their wounds.

When the situation of Blood Breed was roughly clear, Garen began to collect things like Black Wood Crosses.

With the help of two mercenaries, the bald-headed Kaedun and his wife Hera, two more Black Wood Crosses were gathered. Along with the one originally obtained by Garen, a total of three had been collected.

He absorbed 10 Potential points from the three crosses, which was a rather rare harvest for this world.

These 10 Potential points were placed in the Attribute Pane, and Garen was considering how the points should be distributed.

There were no uses for Secret Technique for now anyway. His safety was also guaranteed by Raffaele. In the eyes of other people, he was just a normal high school student and would not meet any situation that was outside of his present ability. Initially, he'd wanted to enhance his strength because he was worried about the Blood Breed invading but after knowing Raffaele's force, Garen was not as worried anymore.

Not to mention the faint tacit understanding between the Witches and the Blood Breeds in the town.

Sitting on the window, Garen took a look at his Attribute pane.

‘Garen Thomas.

Strength 2.4. Agility 2.5. Vitality 2.4. Intelligence 2.1. Potential 1058%. Soul Limit 30.

Seed of Soul: Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique.'

Below, the previous bunch of skills was no longer there except two.

‘Black Claw of Sethe: Second level Insidious Hand. (Total four level)'

‘Violin Mastery: Second level, proficient. (Total three level)'

For other aspects such as education, Garen's opinion was that maybe his subconscious regarded them as things that were not difficult, hence they were not on his list.

His gazed at the two skills, they showed the number of potential points required for an upgrade. Black Claw of Sethe needed 5 points to upgrade a level whereas violin only needed one point to master it…the difference there was too big.

After thinking, Garen still moved his gaze to Black Claw of Sethe. This Secret Technique's origin was not clear. To ascend from the second level to the third level was unusually difficult, and he'd originally thought he needed only a few years to break through. Unfortunately, there had been no sign of breaking through until now, which made him wonder if he needed external stimulus.

Fortunately, Second level Insidious Hand's power was comparable to a fully mastered Mammoth Secret Technique's highest damage from Secret Technique World. The aura also astonishingly covered an area of more than 10 meters.

Finally, he chose to rely on external stimulus to break through.

Garen sighed, watching his potential points drop by 5 points. Then, the Black Claw of Sethe blurred for a moment before clearing up. The whole label of the Secret Technique was faintly covered in black.

‘Slaughtering hand: Third level: Bloodshed. (Can be upgraded to higher level)

This skill originated from Bloody King, Black Sethe's terrifying killing technique. Only after reaching the third level would it truly revealed the information within. One of the Ancient Ender's 42 Demon Kings, Black Sethe had an unspeakable talent for killing. With a glance, souls would be extinguished and legend spoke of his hands that could send anything to the abyss whether dead or alive…

"Gee…I knew it was no common item." Garen's mood lightened. This was the first time he had ever heard that Ancient Ender had 42 Demon Kings.

Black Claw of Sethe was originally something that had been dug out from ancient ruins. From the look of it, the Secret Techniques from the Secret Technique World that Garen had collected, especially those that Garen could not even see through, must have come from Ancient Ender's different level of powerful existences.

Less than two minutes after the Secret Technique was upgraded, Garen felt something cool gushing out from his brain and spreading throughout his body.

In that instant, both his hands became hot and he vaguely heard some kind of raging roar.

In a trance, Garen felt as though he could see a human-shaped murky dark smoke in front of him.

"I wiisll kam!! Wiisll kam!!!"

The human-shaped smoke had a pair of eyes that exuded endless light. It roared furiously and then under Garen's gaze, it crumbled and turned into black dust entering his body through his nose, mouth, and ears.

"Ancient Ender's language?" Garen sat on a window, wobbly.

From other people's perspective, he had been sitting on a windowsill quietly from the start to the end.

Yet, if someone got close to him, they would realize that in the white of his eyes, black smoke was swirling.

The black smoke quickly flowed into Garen's pupils and disappeared.

He did not know what that thing was talking about.

It seemed like Ancient Ender's words but that combination of words made no sense to him.

If he did not guess wrong, that figure should be Ancient Ender's Demon King, Black Sethe but why was he so furious? The secret must be connected to the mysterious disappearance of the Ancient Ender's civilization.

Ancient Ender's civilization was closely related to powerful warlocks. They worshipped death and yearned for death. As one of the 42 Demon Kings, Black Sethe must be among the top. So, what kind of things would make this kind of powerful existence furious to this extent?

Garen snapped back to attention. He felt some changes in his Attribute pane and looked at it.

What he saw shocked him.

The previous human-shaped smoke turned into a shadow with a pair of white eyes in the Attribute pane and charged at the name Garen Thomas.

As the shadow got nearer, Garen felt a chill in his body as though something dangerous was threatening his safety.

"It's trying to possess me?" Garen's gaze turned cold. The Seed of Soul inside his body burst into a bright blue humanoid and pounced on the shadow.

The blue figure was holding an icy blue halberd, his face looking exactly the same as the Garen of his past life.

With his gaze cold, he waved the halberd to fight with the shadow.

Two tiny humanoids were fighting each other furiously on the Attribute pane. It looked like two kids fighting but Garen knew this involved his life's safety.

The shadow was powerful beyond words. Initially, Garen was beaten without any chance to fight back but as time went by, Little Garen who had the continuous support from Seed of Soul finally managed to suppress the shadow.

In the end, with a roar, the shadow collapsed, turning into smoke and was absorbed by the Slaughtering Hand in the Attribute pane.

Everything became calm again.

Garen came back from his trance. Just now he focused his attention on the Seed of Soul and fought a death match with the shadow. Even with Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique, he still got beaten black and blue.

That shadow was obviously not in its prime but with some strange techniques, it managed to suppress an Evil Technique with not a tenth of its strength. Fighting it with its strength fully recovered could truly be very dangerous…

"The Seed of Soul was the condensation of all my power in Totem World. At the soul level, it has the same strength as me at my prime in Totem World, yet it could not even hold a candle to this shadow."

Chapter 587: University 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Ancient Ender Demon King…is really strong…" He spat out a sigh and jumped down from the window.

The sudden threat to his life this time allowed him to understand one of the uses of the Seed of Soul.

Protection of his soul, and the strength which he gathered the previous world inside the Seed of Soul. This meant that at the soul level, he had extra help in the form of the strength of himself at his prime in the previous world.

Garen felt that the Seed of Soul had much more uses than this and the protection of his soul was just a basic function.

Only after checking over his whole body and finding nothing wrong did Garen heave a sigh of relief, pick up his violin case and walk out of the classroom towards the place where he'd parked his vehicle.

Starting his motorbike, he rode the entire way with that human-shaped shadow on his mind.

He vaguely felt that the shadow was not the real Black Sethe but a fraction of him. Black Claw of Sethe had two parts. He got one himself and Andrela got the other. Both had been sealed inside metal cases. Although Black Claw of Sethe was something that Garen could not completely understand, it had appeared in Secret Techniques that were hidden in other ruins. Perhaps this Black Claw of Sethe was meant as a net, and as long as someone could break through to the third level, there would be an opportunity to possess that person.

"Unfortunate." Garen shook his head, "Even with my level, the mutation by the Seed of Soul and training since I was a child, it did not allow me to reach the third level, never mind others. Most of the people probably can't even break through the first level. It would be a miracle if someone manages to the second level after training for tens of years."

Putting aside these thoughts, there was no sense of crisis from Slaughtering Hand anymore. The fraction of Black Sethe should have been eliminated by the Seed of Soul. Garen was much relieved.

He had to pack up his belongings when he reached home. At night, his father Emmer would drive him to the train station and he still had to catch a plane at the capital.

****************

"Brother~~Come back to see me often." Sister Vivien had a talent in acting cute ever since she was small. Even though she was now 10 years old, she still puffed out her cheeks and stretched her arms wanting a hug.

Garen picked her up.

"Of course, we can't forget our cute little Vivi."

At the doorway connecting the living room, his mother Trish in a white shirt with jeans crossed her arms and leaned against the door.

"Alright, that's enough, it's not like you won't meet again, there's still the holidays."

His father Emmer brought over Garen's bag. Inside the large brown bag was an assortment of clothes and shoes.

"It's almost time, let's go. Come back whenever you can." Emmer spoke with a cigarette in his mouth.

"Bro, remember to bring back an autographed poster!" Jason stood in the doorway of his room, unable to hold back his smile. It was apparent that with the pressure from his outstanding brother gone, he was more than a little happy.

"I know." Garen waved at him, "The first year will be more troublesome but I should be able to take out some time to come back once I reached the second year."

Carrying his things outside, Arisa and her sister were standing in the yard. These two sisters were very familiar with his family due to Jason and Vivien. They'd bought a secondhand house near them and had become very good neighbors.

Once Garen was out, Arisa went over to Vivien happily and chattered non-stop while eyeing Garen sneakily.

Apparently, a top university's student still held some weight in the eyes of some children, comparable to some idols in the television.

Isaros was politely talking to his mother Trish at the side, while sometimes speaking a few words to Garen, giving some pointers on her experiences traveling outside.

Garen was quite familiar with Isaros, mainly due to Jason. He had taken the initiative to ask her out but sadly, there was no chance for Jason. On the bright side, the relationship between their two families became closer due to this.

Isaros was somewhat seen as an elder sister in Garen's family.

His parents felt pity for both sisters for losing their parents so early and they were very willing to accept them. They also found a job for Isaros in a bookstore in town.

They walked Garen to his mother's white car and put his luggage in. Garen sat in the seat beside the driver's and waved at them.

"Jason, remember the mission I gave you!" Garen gave Jason a look.

"No problem, leave it to me!" Jason patted his chest.

In the end, Garen still told Raffaele his leaving time. Although he did not saw her, that girl must be watching here at a corner quietly.

Garen got Jason to give Raffaele his violin which was used for practice when he was a child.

Mother drove her car while waving to the back, slowly speeding up and soon there was nothing in the back except streetlights.

The car quickly exited the town and traveled along the winding dark road.

Streetlights gradually became dim. Soon, there were only the headlights from the car shining on the road and their surroundings became dark.

Garen looked towards the front, there was nothing visible except the white line in the middle of the road. Looking back, the town was completely out of sight.

Sometimes, there were cars passing by, though their blinding lights revealed nothing about what kind of cars they were.

The roadside was irregularly peppered with gas stations and motels.

There were only the sounds from the engine in his ears, nothing else.

His mother Trish was driving the car while glancing at her son's condition.

"What is it? Are you nervous? That's right huh, you grew up here and never really traveled outside once. Now that you're out here, there should be some feelings of excitement?"

"I'm alright. Although I looked it up on the internet beforehand, when I really traveled outside, my feelings were truly a bit excited." Garen nodded.

"Remember the route, when you come back, travel from White Card City by train to Feinan and then get a taxi or call me to pick you up."

"Mhm, I know."

"Remember to get along with others at the school, the students there are all not bad, you will be able to form useful connections for your future career."

"Understood."

"Also, when you arrived at school and were in trouble, you can call this number." His mother Trish hesitated before giving him a number. "Call him Uncle Anke and be polite, he should be a professor in your school now."

Garen looked at Trish's expression, it was obvious their relationship was not simple, perhaps he was once her pursuer.

After that, both were silent, Trish focused on her driving and occasionally talked to Garen whenever she remembered something that he had to take note of.

Garen answered casually and focused on looking outside at the road and forest.

Until there were more than ten minutes of silence, Trish pressed the button on the radio.

‘I know you will always miss me~~~if Heaven has a window to look down~~~'

A melodious hoarse male voice sounded in the car.

The gentle melody made Trish hummed along.

Garen got bored of waiting, so he closed his eyes for a short rest but he soon fell asleep.

He woke up still in a daze when the car slowed down.

It was lively outside the windows with the noise from the cars.

Outside their car were different colors of lights from shops, street stalls and cars continuous passing by.

"Almost there." Trish's voice came from beside him.

"What time is it now?"

Half past ten at night, dear."

"I slept for more than two hours?"

"Pretty much."

Garen stared at the unfamiliar street outside. Yellow lights and white lights with the lights from the cars kept flashing by, in front of them was traffic.

A white convertible overtook them from the right, a dark-skinned man wearing an earring whistled loudly towards Trish.

"Hey! Beauty!"

Garen gave him a middle finger and the man suddenly burst out a laughter.

Screech~~

Trish jerked her steering wheel, the SUV sped towards the man's sports car and almost crashed into it.

That man got a big scare and hurriedly sped away, loudly swearing a few words but no longer daring to provoke them.

"When you're outside, don't let people think you're easy to bully and don't hide your abilities until people are on top of you. Show it to them, let them know even if you can't beat them, you still can make them regret. That way, most of the people would not take the initiative to provoke you, understand?" Trish took the opportunity to give Garen a lesson.

"Of course I understand. We may not win against others but we have to let them know that they will have to pay a price when going against us. As long as the price is big enough, we will be able to protect ourselves." Garen nodded.

"Of course, this is only when you encounter a general problem. When there are special circumstances involved, get a lawyer then. I've already hired a private lawyer counselor for you, if you meet some troubles in school, you can consult her in advance."

"Is she beautiful?"

"Of course." Trish laughed. "My senior brother's student and also your senior sister."

Garen shrugged.

"She will contact you when you arrived. She's called Caitlin, don't forget."

"I know, Mom really got everything arranged for me."

The car slowly came to a halt at the train station. At the parking lot beside the train station, both of them got out of the car. Trish spoke a few words with a manager and pulled Garen to the station hall.

Among the crowd, there were security guards and ticket inspectors, then they got to the platform.

Trish was silent all the way. She only kept checking Garen's luggage, wallet, identification card, guidebook, medicines for cold and diarrhea and so on.

"Alright, that's enough, Mom, go home." Garen got on the train, turned back and shouted. "Go home."

Trish waved at him, her face showed a warm smile.

"Bring back a grandchild for me before graduation!"

She suddenly called in a loud voice.

Chapter 588: University 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was stunned and the passengers around him laughed out loud. Among them, one big-bellied man's reaction was the most exaggerated, with him patting his belly while drinking canned beer.

"Your mom is really strong." He clapped Garen on the shoulders.

Speechlessly stared at him, Garen picked up his luggage and walked towards his compartment. The train was wide so there was not much squeezing and shoving. The air-conditioner was quite cold and with the air blowing from below, sometimes he could get a whiff of smelly feet.

Garen quickly found his compartment according to his ticket but unfortunately, a bald-headed guy was lying on both seats with his shoes off, sleeping soundly.

After putting his luggage on the opposite luggage rack, Garen observed the guy. His face and arms were bulged out, giving him a muscular, tough appearance.

He clapped his hand on the guy's trousers but there was no reaction.

"Here, sit by my side." Opposite the seat were a pair of father and daughter. It looked like the father was sending his daughter to the university. The daughter was about 18 or 19 years old and looked quite timid, while the father wore a blue worker's uniform and had gray hair and a kind face.

He smiled at Garen and gestured towards a space by his daughter.

"Sit here, wait until he wakes up."

"No need." Garen returned his smile.

He clapped the man's legs again, this time with more strength.

"What!?" The man finally woke up and narrowed his eyes looking at Garen.

"You took my space, can you get up for a bit?" Garen asked amicably.

"Can't you sit there?" The bald-headed man asked back, a little irritated.

"There are people sitting there." Garen shook his head. "Will please you get up?"

"Let me sleep for a bit longer after that I'll give you space." The bald-headed man complained. "Young man, you're still young. You need to learn to sympathize with adults like us."

Garen was speechless. This time, he noticed that behind his seat, there were two more of the bald-headed man's companions wearing black sleeveless shirts with bulging muscles and black green snake tattoos on their necks.

One was totally bald and the other's hair was cropped short. Both of them were looking at him.

"Come here, sit with me for a while." Sensing the weird atmosphere, the father pulled Garen to his side.

"When we're outside, let's have some understanding towards people." He smiled kindly at the sleepy bald-headed man. The two guys at the back went back to their chat.

"Thank you, but I prefer my own seat." Garen smiled and pushed off his hands.

Then, he stretched out his hands towards the bald-headed man's collar.

"Don't you dare!"

The two guys at the back suddenly stood up. One of them cocked his eyebrows and his hands went for Garen's shoulders.

Peng Peng!!

Two consecutive kicks. Before they could figure out what happened, they felt an immense pain in their stomach and collapsed wailing.

"Why don't you listen when we're talking? You can only regret when it's too late." Garen lifted the bald-headed man by the collar and punched his stomach. The speed was so fast that before he realized, he had been thrown to his companions.

The three guys curled up while moaning, looking like caught shrimps, who could not even straighten themselves.

For small fries like them, he was lazy to spend more effort on them. Looking at the father and daughter's wary expressions, he put on a smile as warm as the sun.

A beautiful smile washed away the violence he'd displayed just a moment ago.

Soon, two guards arrived and asked a few questions. Garen walked up and stuffed some money into the hands of the guard leader, then the three guys kneeling on the ground were dragged away.

The whole compartment had originally been quiet, but when Garen, the weak-looking beautiful guy had settled the three thugs so easily, the attention of the whole compartment had been attracted to them and everyone was checking out Garen. The originally quiet atmosphere got even quieter.

The father and daughter sitting at the opposite were even more curious.

"Child, those three may have more accomplices. You must pay attention when you get off the train." The gray-haired man worriedly advised him.

"No problem, I handled a lot of this kind of things." Garen grinned, baring his pearl white teeth. In his previous two lives, the creatures that had died in his hands numbered at least eight thousand if not ten thousand, especially in Totem World when he needed to farm Potential points. His hands were dyed with blood.

As for those three, he did not even put the matter to heart.

They did not know why but when they saw Garen's shiny white teeth, they shuddered unconsciously and did not mention the three guys again.

For some time, both sides were silent. Garen sat by the window which was his favorite seat. Originally, it was not his seat but that bald-headed man's, but now that man had no way of using this seat, naturally, it became his.

As for whether those three would come back for him, of course, it was impossible.

The injury that Garen gave them would cause them at least two hours of pain until they were totally powerless. This kind of pain would be memorable for them.

The train continued as normal.

With an elbow on the windowsill, Garen took out a CD player with his other hand, insert a music CD and played it on loop.

A gentle female voice harmonized with the melody and crooned in his ears.

Garen's fingers tapped on the table following the beat of the song. There was no sound of his tapping, as he was only gently tapping.

The girl across him looked at him curiously, while feeling embarrassed. She tried to avert her eyesight but her curiosity was obvious. The girl's looks were normal. Short black hair, dark blue shirt, and black jeans with no makeup and a pair of glasses.

Garen smiled at her. She looked down quickly, her face red.

The time on the train passed by quickly. With nothing to do, Garen took out a novel from his bag and began to read.

Originally, he had been planning to buy a berth ticket but it had sold out early. With all the students going to university, berth tickets were difficult to purchase. He was not some spoiled brat, so he gave in and directly bought an ordinary seat.

Travelling from Feinan to White Card City would take about eight hours, and he would arrive after midnight.

Garen gauged the time. When he arrived, he would be just in time to catch his plane so he did not go to sleep.

Sitting there, he observed the flow of people boarding and alighting from the train.

To his surprise, even after hundreds of people, not one of them was a vampire or other supernatural existences. All of them were ordinary people.

This made him realized how rare the numbers of Blood Breeds were in the human society.

As for witches, he could not recognize them. As long as they did not display their powers, they would be the same as any other ordinary person going about their daily lives like working and studying.

Since there was nothing worth paying his attention to, Garen went back to reading his novel. It was rare for him to have such leisure time. Whether he was in Secret Technique World or Totem World, he was always facing challenges and there was not a moment for him to rest. Here, secret techniques could not be practiced excessively. He could only do whatever he felt like in his spare time, and there was a lot of it.

When he was bored, he also thought of the conflict between Arisa sisters and the Primary Colors organization. Ever since the time that bald mercenary had come, he'd covered up the information of both the sisters using some unknown means and now after several years, not even one mercenary had come to kill them.

However, as Isaros' little sister, Arisa grew up, the strange aura that was emitted by her body thickened, and felt even more similar to an aged planet.

He had a hunch that maybe Arisa was the key person behind all these incidents.

For now, all this had nothing to do with him, as he only needed to focus on university and find more things similar to Black Wood Cross.

After the bald mercenary and his wife had left Primary Colors, they'd set up their own mercenary corps. Every member had Garen's approval and learned Shooting Shadow Secret Skill.

The members were originally very talented. Now that they had the Shooting Skill, they were like tigers which have grown wings and were comparable to those high-leveled specialized mercenaries.

Lately, they'd become popular in the specialized talents' circle and even received a nickname, Nighthawk.

Sniper elites with the Shooting Shadow Secret Skill, now they became top killers. Last year in Africa, they achieved noticeably remarkable results and became the top three headhunting mercenary corps which placed them among the top ranking in mercenary circles.

Garen gradually improved the Shooting Shadow Secret Skill and greatly reduced the side effects but the improved version only existed in his hand and was not handed out.

Although to him, this skill was only some plaything.

To others, this was one of the top killing techniques.

As a creator, he had to be as clear as possible on the value of the resources in his hands, using the least cost to obtain the highest profit. This was a principle that Garen had always abided by.

After all, a person could not always get what they wanted anytime and anywhere. Having this habit would help in making the most out of every situation.

All this time while he was deep in thoughts, Garen did not let up on observing the people for any hidden Vampires or Blood Breeds. Apparently, their numbers were very small compared to the humans.

Eight hours of time passed by, and the father and daughter opposite him were still watching a movie on their MP4. The train finally arrived at the White Card City.

Garen took off his earphones, put away his low-powered CD player and smiled at the duo. Taking his bag from the opposite luggage rack, Garen smoothly disembarked at White Card City.

The time was after midnight.

After getting off the train, the air outside was chilly.

The train station was empty except for the passengers that had just alighted and were headed towards the underpass. He could vaguely hear the sound of another train at a distance.

Garen exhaled through his mouth and saw that his breath was white.

He grabbed his bag and calmly headed for the underpass.

The white cement floor, the bright billboard and the voice of a woman announcing the arrival of a train.

All of it looked very normal as if after leaving Grano, the outside was just a world without any anomalies.

No Blood Breeds, no Witches, and no extraordinary powers. It was just a normal world.

Chapter 589: University 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen picked up his bag and followed the flow of people away from the platform. The outside was full of idle vehicles. There were also a lot of unmarked black cars and women soliciting people to check in at their hotels or hitch a ride with them.

One by one, they were like wolves hunting for prey, their eyes sharp and accurate in their search for people who did not have somebody coming to fetch them.

As soon as Garen walked out, he was faced with three or four people.

"Bro, lodging?"

"Looking for transportation?"

"Mine is very near, choose my car."

Garen pushed away from those people and headed for the taxi stand and joined the queue behind the row of people waiting for taxis.

Although White Card City was the state capital and the largest city in the Faya state, the Faya state was the most remote state in America and therefore it was not as advanced and orderly as other states.

Garen took a free tourist map and could not help smiling when he saw the introductions for Grano Town.

On the way here, he did not see even a single vampire. The world outside was surprisingly very normal.

This world belonged to ordinary humans in the end. Blood Breeds and Witches, as long as their luck was not abysmal, the average person wouldn't meet one in their lifetime. Perhaps, they would not be able to recognize one even if they did meet.

Except for some areas, this world was the same as Earth.

Soon it was Garen's turn, he asked for the cost of the fare, then got in the taxi. There were also a boy and girl that were going to the airport. After asking Garen, they got in the same taxi.

The couple wore matching white T-shirts with large cartoon head of a brown bear. Both looked very ordinary. From their getup, it seemed their family was not that well-off. They sat behind Garen exuding a sweet atmosphere.

Looking at them, Garen could not help but think of his ordinary life on Earth. His first love had been the same as these two people, ordinary and sweet. Although they did not encounter any extraordinary things, immersing in their own little world might be a happy thing.

Di Di, Di Di…

At the sound of a voicemail, Garen took out his phone and tapped on it.

"Head, where are you?" It was bald head. This guy was now very successful as the deputy. With the rise of fame, his income also climbed up and made him a millionaire. He also bought a villa at the famous Crosse vacation island.

"I'm still at White Card City. There's no need for you guys to come, I've got someone else to pick me up." Garen said.

"How can this be, it's so rare for Head to come out…Alright, alright, if you need money, it's in the usual account. You can just use it straight away, and if it's not enough just say the word."

The driver beside him heard it and glanced at him. His expression changed and he seemed to be in awe.

From the sound of it, this guy seemed to have some background.

Garen did not know whether to laugh or cry. After reflecting on it, he immediately paid attention to his words. After a few words with the bald head, their conversation ended and the car immediately quieted down.

Apparently, bald head's loud voice was heard by the people at the back. For some time, Garen seemed like the boss of a gang, causing the other three to be afraid of making noise.

"Er…my friend got hooked on movies…you guys should know about it too, that Reborn from Fire." Garen's thoughts accelerated and shrugged it off with this explanation. Reborn from Fire was the latest gangster movie with a production cost of over millions and box office gross of over a hundred million.

The couple was relieved but although the driver was obviously still having doubts, he drove on in silence.

The taxi was neither fast nor slow while traveling from the train station to the airport.

Garen looked at the time on his watch, it was 6.42 in the morning. There was still over an hour of time until the departure of his flight.

"Are you also a student traveling to your school?"

From the couple sitting behind him, the boy suddenly asked.

"Erm."

"Yes, that's right. I'm going to Nottingham. Just finished my SIT this year. You guys too?" Garen asked in passing.

"Yeah, we're also going to Nottingham!" The boy suddenly got excited, "You can call me Mike and this is my girlfriend, Jelal. We just got our notice letters from Scot. Bro, which school are you from? There are five universities in Nottingham."

Garen smiled.

"Mine is Gullivier."

"Oh~~~" The boy dragged out his tone when expressing his surprise. The girl also exclaimed while covering her mouth.

"Amazing!" The girl could not help be said so, "I thought you are from Burlington Music Academy. That place is full of beautiful men like you."

Her words did not finish before her thigh got pinched by her boyfriend Mike and the two went on with their playful antics.

The driver shook his head while giving the back a glance. Looks like he thought of his children at home.

"I'm Garen. Since we're in the same city then let's come out to have some fun when there's opportunity."

Not waiting for Garen to finish his words, the girl immediately agreed.

"This is what you said, give us your contact number and don't make excuses when that time comes!"

Both sides exchanged contact numbers and the atmosphere became closer. The two kept asking about the specifics at Nottingham but found out that he was also someone who never traveled before. They immediately talked about the information they got from the internet and other various sources.

During their heated discussion, the time passed by quickly.

Soon, they reached the airport. Garen paid for the fare and the three of them got off. The couple said that Mike's aunt would come to get them and invited Garen to eat with them.

Garen smiled and declined. He mentioned that there was someone here to pick him up and that after arriving at school, they could pick a time and played around the whole Nottingham.

Both of them promised just like that. Seemed like these two were very naïve and did not have personalities that doubt others.

After getting their tickets using their identification cards, they found out that the three of them were on the same flight so they simply acted together.

It was not time yet so the three of them found some seats and waited for their flight notice while chatting away.

"What's your major? Gullivier's best Worf Business School? Birmingham Medical School? Or the archaeology department?" Mike was very talkative, his topics were endless. Compared to Garen's silent personality, he seemed very lively.

"Why are your guesses only those few?" Garen put down his violin case by his legs and his bag on the seat on the other side.

"Those few are the most famous! Worf Business School is said to have a very powerful alumni association which has a lot of graduated world-class talents like Mastan of Horizontal River Group, who is also someone I admire the most!" Mike was much more informed than the real Gullivier student here, which was Garen.

"Weren't the other two among the most famous places in Gullivier as well? Worf Business School ranked first for three consecutive years on Laplace, which was also the best business school among all universities. As for the medical school, Gullivier holds world-class medical seminars every few years with all kinds of themes, and scholars renowned all over the world will participate in it, so isn't that obvious? And archaeology, the library in your school is enough for the archaeologists to research. There are a lot of books still hidden in that library that have been forgotten ages ago. I don't even need to mention the exhibitions."

"Amazing!"

Jelal gave her applause at the side.

"Talking like you are the real Gullivier student…"

"Hihi, our Scot is also not bad…not bad…" Mike immediately giggled.

"The first year will give me a lot of time to understand all that anyway, there's no need to be anxious." Garen was indifferent to all this. Coming out to study was just a front for him to understand the differences between the worlds. Only by getting out of the small town could he understand the reality of the outside world in a more profound way.

"You're right, during the first year you can choose a club or something to play and the basic courses should not be difficult." Mike seemed to look forward to it. "But you guys seem to have an interview session as part of the examination, are you nervous?"

Garen laughed: "What is there to be nervous about."

"How many points did you score during your SIT?"

Garen instantly put on a serious expression.

"I don't want to deal a blow to you…"

Mike immediately hid his face.

"I knew it…Ala, I need comfort…"

"I warned you not to call me Ala…this brings back unpleasant memories." Jelal hugged Mike while patting his back.

Mike who pretended to be in despair suddenly noticed the violin case by Garen's foot.

"What is this?" When he was getting more familiar and found out that Garen was not easily angered, he became even more open.

"My hobby." Garen picked up the violin case and handed it over.

Mike quickly opened the zipper. One glance at the long shape of violin case and people would know this was some sort of musical instrument, just that the content was unknown.

Opening the case, a dark red exquisite ancient violin laid quietly inside.

"Oh~~~Beautiful!" Mike whistled. "One look and we can tell it's not some cheap stuff. Sure enough, poor families like us can't afford something like this…"

"It's just a musical instrument…"Garen was at a loss for words looking at Mike.

"Just, a, musical, instrument!" Mike held his chest as though in pain, "Just…ten years of my living expenses…no, probably a hundred years of living expenses! My heart…my heart is shattering…"

"Enough of your act, careful of breaking it!" Jelal was obviously nervous. She took the violin away from Mike hurriedly and appreciated the violin for a moment before she carefully put it back into the case and passed it to Garen.

The three of them chatted happily. The flow of people coming and going continued and the attention of some people was attracted to them.

Garen's handsome face and perfect white skin caused even some females to be envious. After a glance at him, there would be some people who would turn back to pretend to look for someone in order to take a second look at him.

The time soon arrived. The announcer read out the number for their flight.

Going through the security checks, after Mike's lighter that had been hidden under the insole of his shoe was found out, his expression was as though he was grieving for a dead relative. Watching him pretending to be sad while hugging Jelal, the young lady in charge of security checks felt a bit sorry.

Garen was completely speechless.

After a while, the three of them got on the plane and found their seats. There was no coincidence this time, the three of them were separated to the front, middle and back of the plane respectively.

Chapter 590: University 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Soon, Mark was tugging at Jelal's sleeve as he begged her to switch seats with him so that he could sit opposite to Garen.

"What a coincidence, we're sitting with each other again." He happily sat down opposite to Garen, in what was originally Jelal's seat.

"Yeah, what a coincidence." Garen sarcastically looked at him.

It was a small airplane which had three seats on one side and two on the other, separating the seats into two columns. They were seated in the three seated column, with Garen opposite of Mike and Jelal. Besides the duo was the young girl who had been swapped out by them. She was an eastern yellow skinned girl and she looked rather quiet. She was in a black shirt with bubble sleeves and a dark red skirt which was at knee length. She even had mature black stockings on her as well.

On Garen's right were two old and pale elders who appeared to be in their sixties. It was surprising that they would board an airplane at their age.

Speaking of which, Garen once had the habit of respecting the elders and adoring the children but as he faced these two elders, he couldn't seem to respect them at all.

Whenever he realized that he was much older than them, what was left inside him was adoring the young and not respecting the elderly. He felt rather sentimental whenever he saw elders being weak and would renew his determination in continuously improving his body.

It was fine that the body got old but what shouldn't get old was the soul. Once your soul felt old then you would be old for good. You would feel gloomy, hopeless and would just pass the days without any motivation, desire, and vigor. Once the soul was old, the body would follow suit.

Hence, Garen never once felt that he was old.

"Speaking of which, this plane is filled with students…" Mike felt bored as he stood up and looked around. "These are all students who're going to Nottingham. Perhaps most of them are our alumni!"

"Are you guys going to attend Nottingham as well?"

The black stocking eastern girl suddenly opened her mouth. Although her American accent wasn't natural, it was rather accurate as every pronunciation was standard, and one could hear it from the anchors on television.

"Yeah… are you an international student? From the East?" Mike was ecstatic, as the most blessed thing that could ever happen to a talkative person like him was someone initiating a conversation with him. "Your pronunciation is very good."

"Is that so? Thank you for your praise." The girl smiled with her eyes. "My English name is Kelly, what's yours?"

"Mike is the name and this is my wife Jelal. Ouch alright alright I'm wrong so stop hitting me!" Mike was immediately grabbed by her. He then pointed at Garen.

"That's Garen. He's been going after my wife for many years but unfortunately, she's still mine. Hahaha!! Ah!!"

As he was attacked at his groins, Mike finally confessed.

They felt more familiar with each other as the four of the exchanged their names.

Garen leaned against the window lazily as he looked out at the airport's ground through the oval window, as though he wasn't interested in engaging a conversation.

On the other hand, Mike, Jelal, and Kelly were happily talking among themselves. Kelly was a student at the music academy, which was the academy Mike mentioned earlier, Burlington Music Academy and she was majoring in piano.

What made Garen happy was that someone had managed to occupy the talkative Mike. Kelly from the East had obviously decided to use him as a sandbag for brushing up on her oral skills. She kept talking to him about everything from the beginning of the flight until the end of it and she didn't seem to be tired of it at all.

About half an hour later, the girl was getting more and more excited and she would even ask Mike about the tiniest detail in his family's lifestyle. Although it was obvious that she wasn't interested in Mike, she was willing to speak to him so that she could try out different pronunciation from different regions…

Half an hour had passed and Mike was now terrified… He felt that he could never be loved for the rest of his life. It was fine if the opposing party engaged a conversation with him if she was interested, but Kelly would always deflate his ego when he got excited, as she would interrupt him by saying she didn't understand what he said earlier.

Then the whole atmosphere went cold…

Although Kelly's pronunciation was very accurate, she had no experience in accent and this made Mike tired as he spoke to her.

After countless times of begging to Jelal, his girlfriend decided to talk to Kelly.

Garen sat at a corner and would occasionally stand up and looked around out of habit. He still had yet to see any Blood Breed or Vampire, as if it was a legend just like how Grano Town only existed in the movie. The world was completely normal. There was no Witch, Blood Breed or Vampire and only normal humans.

Under this environment, he couldn't help but suspect that he had returned to Earth. There was nothing supernatural and he was back to his life where he had no special abilities.

He no longer took note of his attribute pane or the status of his Secret Technique and led his life as a normal person, passenger, student who was sitting on an airplane heading to his school.

This sensation made him feel rather lost.

After an hour or so, the conversation had reached the end, as the plane was about to descend.

The four of them had started to become closer to one another. The eastern girl Kelly, who seemed to be out of her country for the first time, passionately exchanged contacts and KL communication methods via the internet with the three of them. They even called each other's phones to make sure they got it right after they landed.

While the dejected Mike seemed to be traumatized by Kelly, Jelal seemed to be talking to her happily.

On the other hand, Garen didn't speak much but this seemed to have attracted Kelly. Obviously, this introverted personality was something eastern people adored and Garen's neutrally beautiful face and body played a huge role as well.

As their ears popped from the change in pressure, the airplane finally landed with a wobble.

It slowed down and eventually stopped.

After the announcement, the cabin was opened and passengers got up one after another. The passengers who were once strangers had become familiar with one another, and it seemed like they got to know each other better as they talked on the plane, just like Kelly, Garen, Mike, and Jelal. Most of them were students who were about to attend Nottingham.

As they got out of the cabin, four of them went down to retrieve their luggage and walked out of the arrival terminal together.

The terminal inside the airport was teeming with people holding up different kinds of tags, waiting to greet those who just arrived.

Garen sent a message to the person his mother had arranged to pick him up to tell him to not to do so. He then casually glanced around and saw Gullivier University's pickup person. She was a young tanned girl and she seemed to be a senior at the university.

She was standing at the most unnoticeable spot but holding the sign at the corner on the right. There was already a young Caucasian man walking towards her.

Garen bid goodbye to Mike and the others and walked towards her.

"Welcome, new students! The newly arrived studs and beauties!" The tanned girl shouted towards Garen's direction. "This is the pick-up point for Gullivier so all new students, please follow my lead! Don't get lost as we have a transit car!"

A few guys and girls came from behind Garen and it was rather dismal that there were no presentable guys or girls other than Garen. Eight out of ten students were wearing spectacles and one could instantly tell that they did not know how to dress up properly. They always put up a serious face and he could feel the hardcore study aura from them.

"All first years are like that… They're all this way… Didn't we still have one good looking one?" The Caucasian guy who had approached her seemed to be a pick-up personnel and he held the tanned girl's shoulder as he looked at her sympathetically.

"Sigh…"

They then formed into groups and waited for a while as a few more people gathered around. All of them looked like geeks and the tanned girl led the teams out of the airport after no one was left.

Along the journey, no one talked as each and every one of the first years were completely silent. Even those who tried to speak were suppressed by the quiet atmosphere.

Gullivier was the world's most advanced medical business university and was ranked world number one among the schools of business and top ten among the schools of medicine. Naturally, the prerequisite to be admitted into this university was to obtain a very high score on the previous exam. This was the case for the local students. The international students were required to pass their local exams before they could even attend this prestigious university. This meant that they had to frequently burn the midnight oil.

One could say that none of the people here were normal and all of them were the best in their schools. Perhaps, based on their academic records, they were even rewarded for some sort of international record in comparison with the students from the other countries of the same age.

Garen was able to easily enroll into this university not only because of his high score. His parents' blessings played a role as well.

His academic record was the worst among these students. The Gullivier's examiner who came to see him sat quietly as he listened to Garen playing his violin for a brief moment and approved him after looking at his results. He then went to find his father Emmer for a drink…

In retrospect, he was the tall, rich and handsome man among them. He wasn't rich in terms of wealth but knowledge…

The bus was in complete silence as all of them boarded the white bus.

At least ten pairs of eyes were staring at the tanned senior. This made her swallow back her words and sit down quietly.

Only the sound of the bus could be heard along the journey.

It was obvious that not all first years liked to enjoy the silence but this group was a coincidence.

Garen glanced at the man on his right, who had a small beard and had panda eyes, which made him looked like an AIDS patient who was in the final stage. He was very focused on playing the rubrics cube in his hand. It was a pure 4x4 rubrics cube.

The rubrics cube was solved in a very short amount of time in his hand and he would then mess it up again.

"Do you like rubrics cube? You wanna try it?" The guy glanced at Garen as if he was looking down on him. From his perspective, those who liked to dress up and take care of themselves were just nothing but show. And even if they were able to get into a university, they more or less wouldn't make any impact.

It was a given that dressing up and taking care of oneself required time and effort and everyone's time and effort were limited. If one were to spend time on this portion, one would have less time for other places. Hence, they theoretically couldn't handle everything well. Only those who were able to do so were the gifted ones and were called the all-rounders. However, at higher levels, these people were just mediocre and were just a person who was slightly better than commoners.

"I haven't played this before." Garen took the rubrics cube from his hand.

The messy rubrics cube was turned here and there and then it snapped.

"Uhm…"

Garen placed the rubrics cube which was broken into two pieces back into the guy's hand.

"I have a strong hand… This… I'm sorry…"

The guy blinked and looked at Garen before looking back at the rubrics cube in his hand as he gulped. He was thinking that the opposing party would either solve the rubrics cube in high speed, clueless against it or would think about solving it slowly.

He didn't expect that the end result would be like this.

Garen was careless as he turned it twice before his chains of thought clicked. The moment he applied more force to it, it broke into half…

Gare didn't do it on purpose as he had placed himself in a commoner's lifestyle. The moment his thoughts clicked he unconsciously applied too much force.

The rubrics cube was kept back in and both of them didn't know what to say.

"It's fine. It may be because I've been playing it for a long time and it's on the verge of breaking apart."

"I'll get you a new one when you get down from the bus."

"It's alright. I have plenty of them." The guy kept the broken rubrics cube.

Afterwards, both of them was thrown into silence and didn't know what to say to each other.

Chapter 591: Admission 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On the journey towards the university, Garen was sitting by the window.

There was nothing supernatural anywhere but normal people, normal environment, and normal weather. Everything was normal.

Everything outside the window was empty from the beginning. Then, buildings started to appear for a while before they were replaced by green fields once more.

The sky was cloudy as black clouds drifted in the sky.

The bus traveled along the lane at a moderate speed. Bungalows could occasionally be seen along the road lined with green fields. Some had red walls and some were pure white. They could also see a land of black tube trees in between the houses.

"We're arriving soon so please be prepared." The tanned leader stood up and shouted.

Ugh…

As she finished speaking, a girl at the back couldn't resist any longer as she took out a plastic bag and vomited inside it. Her face was pale and she looked like she's in agony.

"Ugh…" The skinny man beside Garen covered his nose as the sour, putrid smell was rancid.

Garen, too, covered his nose as he frowned.

"We're arriving soon so please hold on just a little bit longer." The tanned leader shouted.

Finally, the bus slowed down, took a turn and stopped.

The first years immediately got down from the car and Garen took a deep breath as the people pushed each other to get down from the car.

"Gullivier University isn't located near Nottingham City but its outskirts. The university has formed into an independent town where lecturers, professors, and students gather and live together in this land. We also have all kinds of services as well, which in turn attracted a few citizens to lived here, increasing the trading between merchants. Gradually, it formed into Gullivier town."

A fit girl in yellow T-shirt shouted as she was leading a group of first years in the same shirt.

"Welcome this year's freshies, welcome to Gullivier!" She shouted as she smiled. "We are the Senior Reception Group, pack your luggage and follow me!"

The group of first years followed the group in yellow T-shirts blindly as they passionately helped the first years carried their luggage and filled them in the situations in the university.

The one helping Garen carrying his stuff was a beautiful female senior. However, he mustn't be seduced by her attractive and pure body, as she'd slapped another woman who wanted to help Garen to carry his luggage and became his guide.

Through the senior Serena's introduction of the university, Garen had a rough understanding of Gullivier's overall situation.

The whole compound was a big square and was categorized into three major school districts and many little school districts. These were something he had to be familiar with in the future.

However, the first thing he should take note of as a freshman was to choosing his accommodation.

The accommodation inside the university was slightly expensive but it was safe. He had to observe for himself whether the buildings outside of the university, including the small office buildings, were viable for him to rent as well.

The first year's assignments in Gullivier were hectic hence he also had to take note of his time management.

The crowd passed through the yellow stone arch noisily and entered the university's garden which had no walls.

Their surroundings were filled with green, tall trees and there was even a green field.

There were buildings placed at the side of the hills and some couples were sitting there talking.

"Garen, where are you from?"

"Where? I'm from White Card City so I'm technically a person from the Ghana State." Garen responded.

"You're as rare as those international students from the east then." Serena glanced at him with her chest subtly pushed up.

She was very beautiful. She had shoulder length dark hair, big black eyes, charming, straight nose, pink small lips and her edge of her lips were colorful.

Her eyebrows were especially slanted, giving off a savage yet fresh vibe.

Her chest was busty and her hips were attractive, with her tight black jeans as emphasis.

"If you're from Ghana, then you have to be more careful. People here tend to form gangs from the same states. We don't have many students from Ghana so you might want to consider finding a stronger group with more people."

"Hmm. Thanks for your advice."

As the introduced to each other along the way, Serena asked Garen for his number on her own accord and sent him to his dorm. She gave her a set of numbers and key before leaving.

The dorm was built on a jade green field and was a fully red mountain typed building. It was about seven to eight floors high and faced the public training equipment on the field, such as swings, single parallel bar, bicycle, etc.

Students were walking in and out of the building and Garen could feel many people were staring at him at the entrance.

He picked up his luggage and entered the dorm as he walked along the corridor with white tiles still smelling of detergent. He arrived at the third floor, matched the numbers and opened the door. It was empty. No one was inside.

On the other hand, the corridor was filled with people. Some students were running around in their underwear and some of them were shouting as they ran around barefooted.

The dorm had four bedrooms and each tenant would have their own room. Garen found a room and moved all of his stuff inside. After he finished arranging everything, he noticed four new Gullivier students manual with red covers on the table in the living room.

He picked one up and flipped through it. The cover was hard yet the inner side was as soft as fabric.

As he turned around and closed the door, Garen carried the book to the balcony, reached out his hand and touched the balcony. The cold porcelain tile was completely free from dust.

He could see a forest and a grey tower from the balcony. On top of the tower was a bell.

Between the tower and the dorm was a big green field and running through it were grey lanes. There were a lot of students reading on the field.

The previously cloudy sky had turned sunny. As the warm sunlight shone onto the field, it was even greener than before.

As he scanned the area out of habit, everything on the field was normal and nothing out of place.

The Secret Techniques, Secret Skills, and abilities were something that was out of place and was of no use under this environment. It was as though they were never meant to exist, and should only be seen in a vampire movie or the sort.

In this environment with all the normal people, he had to follow the rules of the university and participate in his university life without cheating.

He took out his phone and made a call to home.

Ring… ring…

"Hello, have you reached the university?" Mother Trish's voice could be heard.

"I have arrived and am currently in the dorm. Everything went without a hitch and I'm going to attend the ceremony in the afternoon as written in the freshies manual." Garen replied casually. "Mum, has Raffaele visited me when I left?"

"She did and was in tears. She left the moment I passed her Jason's item. " Trish's tone was rather melancholy. "It's unfortunate that you're so far away from her, if not you two could've gotten together."

"Perhaps. Where's pops? What's Vivien and Jason doing?"

"Your dad is currently chatting with the new and beautiful researcher. Vivien is currently drawing together with Arisa and Jason had gone out to read some books at the usual spot."

"Alright, I hope he'll succeed. To be frank, I feel that Jason is not suited with Arisa. If he doesn't change his dream regarding his fist then his dream would be just a pipedream." Garen was speechless.

"I feel so as well. The moment you left I heard that Isaros had injured her hands and she still insisted on working in the bookstore. Her injury was quite dire as she bled a lot. The lady was very strong as her expression didn't change at all. With that huge injury, Jason would've cried a long time ago." Trish said hopelessly.

"Isaros was injured?" Garen was stunned. As he had interacted with him for the past few years, he knew how good Isaros was. This person who had decent melee combat skills and a will of defending himself would usually have a good sense of taking care of themselves. It's weird for him to have such an injury.

"Yeah. The city was rather unstable the moment you left. There were a few fighting cases and those thugs from the north were admitted to the hospital due to heavy injury."

Garen was stunned. Perhaps Raffaele had brought a few people to wage war against the Blood Breeds?

He thought of this possibility.

Grano and Nottingham's Gullivier were two different worlds.

He had basically confirmed that the world outside had no supernatural power and they did not have the unique aura similar to the Arisa sisters. Everything else seemed normal as if Grano was the only place filled with supernatural powers.

Everything was gathered there.

Is wasn't just Gullivier, other places where Nighthawk reported had the same results as well.

Even on the battlefield, they couldn't even find any evidence of the existence of vampires or any sort. Nighthawk's team didn't even hear of such a thing before as well.

It was as if the Blood Breed and Witches were in one world and the remaining people were in the other world. And these two worlds were separated by a deep layer.

Garen stood in Nottingham. He could feel that he was far away from the center of the whirlpool. He could feel that Grano, or where ever the Arisa sisters were located, complicated things would happen. It was similar to Sylphalan in the Secret Technique world and Beckstone in the totem world. There were all the main leaders in that generation.

As he was far away from these main characters, he naturally had obtained a normal and peaceful life.

"Mum, if there's anything special related to the Arisa sisters, would you mind giving me a call?" Garen said softly as he thought of it.

"Ah, are you interested in those two? Do you want both of them? You're indeed my most talented son!" Trish was very excited. "I already felt that these two are good girls a long time ago. When Arisa grows older, she would definitely become a beautiful lady and her sister is a researcher at Sadinshi University and would definitely suit you! Don't worry about marriage as you can go to any small country and change your citizenship. It's not a problem at all! You can get a huge bed and play some games during night time as well with those two sisters! Son, you really do have a great taste! Especially Arisa, your mum can tell. She's the type where she would react coldly outside but passionate on the inside. She would definitely won't give up on you. She's definitely a good one! …"

Chapter 592: Admission 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Speechless, Garen hung up the phone. Once Trish got excited, she wouldn't stop talking even if you gave her half an hour.

He looked at the time and noticed that it was still early. The first year's ceremony would take place after lunch time so he took this opportunity to walk outside to get a rough understanding of the university's landscape.

He packed his stuff and as he was about to go out, the dorm's door was opened and three thin and tall men entered. All of them were in spectacles and was talking with each other happily as they pulled their luggage.

The one in the lead who had a crew cut hairstyle dropped his spectacles as he saw Garen inside the dorm. It was as if he was stunned when he saw a handsome man.

"Finally. The dorm alliance finally has hope.." He muttered in an unknown language.

"It's not that we have hope, perhaps we can even find Gina's dorm…" The one at the back with glasses muttered.

"No one would say our dorm is poor and thin any longer! Hahaha!" The last man laughed weirdly.

"Garen." Garen reached out his hand and greeted three of them.

"Messi." "Alexander." "Gattelin."

All three of them spoke in three different accents and this made Garen churn his brain to understand them.

After fooling around, they introduced themselves to one another and chatted for a while.

Alexander, who had cousins living here, went out to find them after the chat. Gattelin had a girlfriend and he had gone out as well. They could see that Garen was distancing himself away from them as he kept smiling at them out of politeness. Although he looked kind on the outside, he was actually very hard to approach. Both of them liked to joke around with their cold jokes. However, Garen didn't know how to react to their jokes but to smile, smile and smile…

Soon, the result of smiling appeared, which was an awkward silence. Whenever a person cracked a joke, no one laughed loudly and it would be very awkward.

Hence, the other two decided to go out.

On the other hand, Messi's personality was rather open as he didn't care about it and chatted with Garen. As he heard that Garen was about to stroll around the university compound, he insisted that he wanted to follow along.

Two of them packed up and went out together.

Both of them changed into T-shirts, jeans and sports shoes. They didn't take the main road as they got out of the dorm and decided to walk across the green field.

They looked at the school district nearby, the Weischer Tower. There were three of these towers and each district had one each. Every day, there would be students responsible for ringing it.

The old bell ring gave the whole university a nostalgic vibe.

"Isn't it cool? It feels like the university in the old days and we're the legendary elite practitioners." Messi said passionately as he would occasionally grab hold of branches along the road.

"It feels alright." Garen nodded.

"I heard from my brother that you can enroll in many clubs Gullivier University as a first year. However, it's best not to join in too many of them as the assignments are slightly more hectic for the first years. If you don't have enough time to study then you might be rejected for the specialized course that you wish to enroll in." Messi then casually asked. "What do you wish to major in?"

"I'm not sure. Don't we have another year to think about it? I'll take it slowly." Garen replied with a smile.

"I plan to major in computer science. I'm fairly decent in terms of computer technicals and one can do anything once one has mastered it. Although Gullivier's computer science isn't the best, it's still much better than the others. He said as he walked and prodded a pimple on his face.

Two of them chatted on the way as they passed by all kinds of old buildings in different sizes. Most of them were decorated with arc-shaped or triangular texture and looked like broken glasses from afar.

Easels were placed in random spots on the field and at the side of the road. These easels of different sizes took up a portion of the field, forming a small exhibition. Students who had nothing better to do could go in and admire the arts.

Students and professors could occasionally be seen holding cellos, accordions or flutes as they played happily.

Other than these people, most of them were normal students who were carrying textbooks as they memorized the medical terms.

A beautiful voice could faintly be heard from one of the buildings nearby, which seemed to be from some clubs organizing a music festival.

Garen and Messi weren't at the center of the attention as they walked slowly on the field.

They messed around until lunchtime. They went to the cafeteria to get some quick bites and paid using cash via their student ID number. Afterwards, they went straight to the hall for the first year ceremony.

The vice headmaster and the persons in charge of the three districts spoke as the crowd cheered.

Afterwards, they gave out the student ID, cafeteria card, documents required to borrow the textbooks and medical cards with numbers on it. Every student would have a dedicated doctor responsible for their health and the information of the doctor such as his name, office location, working hours and phone number was printed on it.

Students would have to make an appointment in advanced when they felt unwell and they would build a medical profile there. However, Garen seemed to never have an opportunity to use it.

After the ceremony, they then started talking about the specialized courses and what to take note as first years.

Garen didn't get to listen to it as Messi had pulled him out of the hall.

There were all sorts of clubs filling up the whole field. It was a simple setup where a person in charge was sitting behind the table and the name of the club written on the wooden signboard. The recruiters were all presentable seniors and the handsome and beautiful ones were in the major clubs. They were using all sorts of techniques to recruit the first years.

There were a few new students who were seduced by the seniors' beauty and were signing up for a club with an unknown name.

Messi had a clear objective. He excitedly wriggled his way within the crowd as he pulled Garen to a secluded corner.

‘Beauty Appreciation Club' was clearly written on a white wooden board.

The senior sitting at the table looked gentle and handsome. He didn't give off a desperate or pervert vibe at all.

"Uhh… I will pass…" The senior immediately stood up and ran towards him when he noticed Garen was looking at him. This made a shiver run down Garen's spine.

"I'll check that place out." He immediately got away from Messi and walked towards the clubs on the other side.

No matter how loud Messi tried to shout behind him, Garen was swarmed by multiple gentle and beautiful seniors the moment he entered the area. They were showing off their clubs as they introduced it to him.

Typically, attractive people were their favorites as this kind of resources were good to use them as a decoration in the club to lure in more people.

It was very obvious that Garen was one of them.

Hence, four or five beautiful seniors came towards him. In Garen's eyes, these beautiful seniors were far less pretty than Rafaelle. However, they were considered above average within Gullivier.

This area's club was coincidentally filled with Sanda, grappling, fighting, fist technique, etc.

There were a variety of styles and some styles were even from fighting games. Here, one could simply pay some fees and rent a spot to form a club. The university would be supportive as long as the club wasn't against human society or the sort.

Garen frowned as his ears were deafened by noisy people introducing stuff to him.

"Junior Garen, why don't you join our combat club?" A familiar voice could be clearly heard among the noise.

Garen looked at where the familiar voice came from and saw his guide, senior Serena. The girl had changed into a set of black tights attire with short lace skirt. She also had white jeans with brown belts and a ponytail as she stood beside a muscular man.

"What do you think? If you join us, you can use my name if people bully you! It's up to you if you want to learn combat." It seemed that Serena had been targeting the first years when she was guiding the new students. No wonder the strong woman didn't fight back when she oppressed her.

"Combat club? That largest one?" Garen noticed the club with the biggest table in the area.

"Yeah."

"Sure," Garen replied. Serena was the only person that could be labeled a beauty in this university and combat was also one of his strongest assets.

With his approval, Serena pulled Garen to the club's registration area, in which she obstructed everyone who tried to persuade otherwise.

He then reported his student number, dorm, and records to register for the foundation class. Under the witness of attractive people, Garen entered the combat club and became one of its members.

Then Serena placed him at the back of the booth and his first assignment was to act as a good luck charm. Everyone who signed up with Garen had seniors assisting him throughout the process.

A few girls who sat beside Garen were interested in him as they kept inquiring him about his interests.

The recruitment lasted until evening hours and ended with the members packing everything up.

The combat club wasn't really that hectic. Occasionally, they would group together and have a sparring session, guidance from the coach and a training session. The sparring session would usually determine their clubs' ranking and they would fight for real when there was a challenger.

Most of the martial art hobbyists would require advice from professionals. Hence the club would often organize advisory activities where the coach would be paid, albeit little, but he could receive plenty when there were a lot of people.

Naturally, there was free coaching as well. They were all enthusiasts within the clubs and would have bits of advice from the professionals. Occasionally, they would send someone to compete outside of the university and the university would reward them whenever they obtained results.

The combat club once ranked third among all the universities internationally in the MBL world combat championship. They also frequently participated in international competitions for freestyle fights. Hence, the had some formidable influence within the university. Naturally, the society's elite members would have special treatments. This was one of the reasons why the combat club became more popular.

He found out from a few female seniors that the club even spent money to invite a coach who once won the RAB international competition. The coach was their senior's senior Casey Bo. They also had invited a few top professionals from the open combat competition. Hence they were pretty confident in this year's competition.

With this setup and system, it was without a doubt, a strong temptation for martial art enthusiasts.

With Garen sitting there for not more than ten minutes, the club had recruited at least ten people. Compared to the other clubs, they were totally in the league of their own.

Chapter 593: Fight 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The recruitment lasted until night time. After Garen had set a time for the activity, he returned back to the dorm with Messi.

The second day of university for new students was the second examination and interview. This examination was just a repetition and those who didn't have any issue previously would pass without a hitch.

Among the crowds, Garen did a set of tests and replied a few questions given by the examiner, passing the examination process with ease.

The next tasks were trivial and tedious as all the materials required for the university had to be prepared by oneself. He went to the bookstore to buy a brand new set of books, which cost him a few thousand dollars. He then contacted his mother Trish to arrange for lawyer consultations and bought some daily necessities.

The university life was considered relaxing but his daily schedule was filled with lectures. However, as long as Garen didn't disrupt the class, the lecturer or professor wouldn't even care if he slept. The lecturers would ignore him after asking him a few questions, which he answered perfectly.

This world's universities were rather similar to Earth's and there wasn't much difference other than the content was slightly more difficult. After some time, they were required to hand in their thesis report, which required a lot of citations and a tedious amount of effort to search, read the materials and travel frequently between the library and dorm.

The remaining three in the dorm soon fell into an abyss of panic, as they were so busy they couldn't even sleep at night.

Within a few months of admission, the thin had gotten thinner and the fat had a major weight reduction. Every day, they could only sleep for four to five hours. The prerequisites of the non-core subjects were high and the syllabus was very detailed, which put a lot of stress on the students.

"I heard Professor Elvin is going to give a lecture at the faculty of medicine. Are you guys interested?" Messi asked loudly as he sat on the living room's sofa as he held onto boxes of food. There was a stack of reference books in front of him and it seemed like he planned to read the books and eat at the same time.

"I'll get prepared. The contents of the last lecture were discussed in detail by professor Elvin. We may get some unexpected information." Alexander was highlighting main points with his pen.

"I have club activity." Garen shrugged his shoulder as he sat on the balcony with a hot coffee placed by the window. He even had a newspaper from Nottingham in his hand as he read it while enjoying his coffee.

Messi looked at him in sadly.

"Don't you think you're a sore eye when your housemates are busy preparing their thesis in agony…"

The other two roommates looked at him in jealousy. When they're studying, Garen was sleeping (practicing Secret Technique). When they're preparing for their thesis, Garen was drinking coffee while reading the newspaper. Now, when they're about to go for a talk, Garen said he wanted to participate in his club activity…

"Is that so?" Garen placed down the coffee. "I did my thesis too. It's just that I'm slightly faster."

"How is that called slightly faster?" Messi shouted. "Sometimes I really do feel like choking you to death!"

Garen looked at him with pity.

"Ah ah ah!!! Stop looking me with that gaze!!" Messi shouted. "Not everyone is like you, where the information you needed was in a book you've seen before."

"Who knew I would be so lucky?" Garen shrugged.

"I'm not sure why, but I feel like punching you whenever I see your smug face." The relationship between Messi and Garen had improved tremendously as they seemed to be okay with each other.

"Alright stop fighting you two. Whenever my hand jitters the arc turns into a straight line." Gattelin, who was drawing complained.

As the three continued to study hard, Garen shook his head, lowered his head as he continued reading the newspaper and would occasionally sip the hot coffee.

He took out a CD player and placed a music disc into it. He then plugged in his earphones and enjoyed it. He enjoyed it so much that he would close his eyes and hummed along with the music.

He looked at three of them working their butts off and smiled.

"You guys are so weak."

"Don't stop me. I'm going to choke this bastard to death!!!" Messi couldn't resist any longer as he leaped towards Garen.

"Good luck!"

"Go ahead! Punch him!!"

Two of them from behind started shouting.

Garen laughed as he ran away on the balcony, escaping from Messi's grasp.

It's very common for these two to joke around like so even though three of them weren't that happy with Garen for this very reason. Garen would be fooling around whenever they're busy and the professor would always praise him instead of them.

Messi then went back to his seat unsatisfied as he realized his time was wasted on Garen. He then shouted that he would skip lunch and focus on studying.

Garen looked at the time and walked out of the dorm. Since the other two had brought lunch with them, he walked to the cafeteria nearby slowly.

In the morning, he would attend lectures if he had them and would search for information for his assignment if there was no lecture. Occasionally, he would go to the music festival, exhibition, play some ball and look at the others training their combat skill. This had been Garen's university life for the past few months.

Gullivier's assignments were hectic and professors had high expectations of the students. This was different from the national university back in Earth, where a thesis could be simply mixed and matched from other documents. The normal assignment would require a huge amount of reference and personal analysis towards the topic in order to pass it. A typical course exam's result was typically determined by the professor. If he liked the essays you've written, you passed. If not, no matter how many lectures you've attended, you would most likely fail.

He went to the cafeteria and bought three standard meals. While he's on the way back, Garen coincidentally walked into Serena with books in her hands, whose class had just ended.

"Today's activity is important, so make sure you attend," Serena said.

"Something important? What is it?" Garen was curious.

"The president is about to leave so we're electing a new president. There will be an interesting sparring competition!" Serena was rather excited when she said so.

"Are you participating?" Garen looked at her strangely. "Or perhaps someone related to you is participating. There must be a reason you're so happy, right?"

"You're right. My sister is participating so you'll need to cheer for her!" Serena smiled.

"Sure." Garen nodded.

The peaceful lifestyle was rather boring to him recently, and now there was an event interesting enough for him to attend.

He went back to the dorm and gave the other two their lunches. He then went back to his room, laid down on his bed, opened his laptop and looked at the records left in KL Chat.

Mike, Jelal, and Kelly whom he met on the way here had left a message for him. After replying him, he checked on his family's situation and Raffaelle wrote a few messages to him. The message was short and had uploaded a recent picture of her on a beach in the evening hours. In a black dress, she was squatting beside a sand castle.

"Remember to bring some gifts back for me." -- Raffaele.

Garen pondered for a while.

"Are you still in Grano?" -- Garen.

He didn't expect to instantly obtain a response.

"Yep. I don't plan to go to university anymore since I don't learn much there." -- Rafaelle.

"Is it your grandmother's wish?" Did she agree?" -- Garen.

"Yep." -- Raffaele.

Garen didn't know what to say as he wasn't knowledgeable in the witch's life. However, it was indeed true that experiencing university wasn't advantageous to Raffaele and it was just a waste of time.

After asking about her situation, he then closed KL.

The afternoon hours were just as usual, where there were no incidents. Garen felt as though he was a completely normal student.

He went to two more classes, had dinner and went straight to the combat field.

It was located in the old university's area, inside a classroom which was once for dancing.

When Garen arrived at the venue, it was already filled with people and a thick layer of mats had been placed at the center of the wide room. The senior members were sitting on one side while the new members were sitting on the other side. The division was clear.

A few senior members were explaining the current situation of the club in details to the new members.

In another corner, two muscular men were exercising, one of them were using the Pec Deck Machine while the other one was doing a sit up.

Those two were the coaches that the club had hired.

"Arrived already?" Serena was surrounded by a group of members and seemed to be talking about something. As she saw Garen entering from afar, she waved her hand.

Garen nodded. Since Serena was the only person he knew in the club, he changed into a black training attire at a corner and sat together with the new members.

The coach for the new members was a qualified senior member of the club. He was currently explaining the rules of the club and once he was almost done the explaining, he started giving the daily training.

"Now, I would like the new members who have combat experience to stand up." The coach drank after a long day of talking.

Among the tens of new members, five or six people stood up. There even were people who looked like in a dilemma.

"Coach, does self-learned combat considered?"

"Of course not." The senior shook his head.

Garen stood up and walked to the other corner with the five or six people.

Serena from the other side looked suspicious and shocked to find out that Garen had learned combat before.

Among the five to six people, two of them were women. One of them was very fit and looked very strong while the other was small and had a ponytail. She seemed to be here to learn to protect herself from the perverts.

She looked very elegant with her small face, pale skin. She looked very serious about it and this made a few men in the club whistle at her.

"You! Come out. You're not allowed to whistle and you can leave the club if you don't like it." The senior member coach shouted without any mercy.

The other three men had a typical face. Nothing was out of place and they were just normal martial art enthusiasts. They'd been observing the training for so long and couldn't hide their excitement when they could finally participate in it.

When Garen was observing the others, he didn't realize the others were observing him.

To the eyes of the new and old members, this new member who had just joined a few months ago had a different vibe compared to the other new members.

He, who had been observing the club's training, was about to officially go into training was not excited or frightened. He was calm as if this was an everyday occurrence to him.

Judging from the tender and pale skin at his hands and neck, one would immediately assume that he was the type who didn't like to train.

Chapter 594: Combat 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"You can choose not to participate in the training" Serena walked towards him and whispered to Garen.

"It's fine. I'm bored anyway." Garen smiled and replied.

As a club member who was one of the few which were good looking, Garen's main purpose was to be a showcase. However, since there was not much news regarding the Black Wood Cross recently, Garen decided to play along since he was bored.

After taking some time to understand the situation, he was still interested in the combat club. There were a few professionals in the club but they were only considered professionals as a commoner. If they were to encounter the lowest class vampire, they could only die and this wouldn't affect Garen's emotions.

The combat club had a lot of special rights in the university as they had obtained a lot of rewards before. A lot of elites could officially skip class during the competition period, even if the class was a core subject. This was what Garen was most interested in.

The new members were then separated into two groups and a senior pulled the new members who had no experience to a corner to teach them the basics.

Another senior pulled Garen and the others to the other side, preparing to test their skills.

Serena was chatting with a few of the members before walking towards him. There was a tall and strong man following beside her. He had a small mustache and was in a black singlet and a camouflage pants.

"We have Xander last year who was at a level to be able to participate in the competition. I wonder how this year's members will be." The man looked at seven of the new members.

"I've already informed Bidaen to go soft against Garen. The club is seriously imbalanced between the guy and the girls and we need him to lure in more female students. We can't scare him off." Serena said softly.

"Are you implying that I'm not handsome?" The muscular man complained.

"Pfft."

As both of them were speaking, the trial had started.

Among them, the elegant ponytail girl and golden-haired Garen had the most attention.

As both of them were very attractive, this had caused a lot of attention to be focused on them.

As the trial coach, Bidaen allowed the guy with an unsatisfied expression to come out first.

Both of them stood against each other and the trial began.

He rushed towards Bidaen and avoided a punch from the opponent. He then collapsed onto his pelvic area.

"Not bad. Next."

Although Bidaen was smiling, he was shaking his head on the inside. Those who followed fully to the rules could only be considered as a beginner with some foundation.

The man got down of the stage and in exchange, a girl went up. Her waist was lean and muscled.

Both parties announced their name and the battle began.

The girl took a step forward and tried to grab hold of Bidaen with both of her hands.

Unfortunately, it was a failure as he evaded it. However, she was able to hold off Bidaen's attack.

"This one's good. She has a good foundation." Serena, who was watching the spar, nodded.

"She can become the reserve of the elite members." The muscular man nodded.

Bidaen and the fit girl fought for some time and the girl eventually fell to the ground. She didn't seem disappointed, and in fact looked rather excited. She panted as she muttered something about finally finding the group for her and went down the stage.

The next person was the other guy. Bidaen had purposely placed Garen and the elegant girl at the back. This was especially true for Garen as he felt like not hitting him as he had such fair and tender skin. How much effort would one require to take care of his skin to such a level?

The remaining few were weak and couldn't even last a hit. They were just enthusiasts with a little bit of foundation. In terms of fighting experience, they seemed to have none.

Finally, it was Garen's turn.

He walked forward.

"Garen Thomas, please to meet you."

"Go ahead and fight me."

Bidaen nodded.

"I may be stronger than the few before me, so be careful." Garen smiled as he warned him.

"Oh?" Bidaen carefully looked at Garen's gaze and noticed that he wasn't joking at all. He then started to feel wary.

As Garen noticed the opponent's gaze, he walked towards the opponent and stood about 3 meters away from him.

"Be careful."

As he finished his sentence, Garen moved and instantly appeared behind the opponent. His hands were as agile as feathers as he gently moved them across Bidaen's shoulders.

Slam.

Bidaen flipped and rolled a few rounds to the front as he fell. He had completely lost control of his balance and he was in shock as he looked at Garen behind him.

It wasn't just him, the new members nearby, together with Serena and the muscular man who were observing at the side were stunned.

Serena, who had been about to place the lollipop into her mouth and the man who was just about to scratch his hand stopped moving and didn't know how to react to this.

All the new members were stunned as they didn't know how to react to such situations.

This corner of the room was in complete silence as no one spoke.

After a while.

"Fuck me! …. You're a professional!!" Bidaen muttered.

"It's alright." Garen shrugged.

"What kind of footwork was that? How did it make me so confused?" Bidaen recovered quickly from his shock and what replaced it was a sense of excitement. He was a combat enthusiast who knew a lot and was obviously interested in the footwork that he had never seen before.

"It was a simple footwork where one moves in the blindspot of the opponent. Add in some unique technique and anyone can achieve the effect of disrupting the opponent's vision." Garen wasn't joking as it was really a very common technique. In the Secret Technique world, even normal martial artists were able to use it proficiently.

It was one of the popular techniques.

This technique could only be used to toy with commoners as typical martial artists had strong senses. Once their vision was compromised, they could immediately switch into hearing and the technique was useless against them.

Garen took into consideration that he would be facing against a commoner so he took out the most common technique in his memory.

However, it seemed to be too advanced for this world…

"It has a very interesting name, called Two-phase extermination," Garen explained. "Combined it with the footwork, one could gently gross over the opponent's neck."

The Two-phase Extermination was a set of martial art that wasn't popular. As it's practically not strong. This was the reason Garen chose this technique to engage with a commoner in this world for the very first time. However, based on the people's reactions, Garen knew that this was too advanced.

"Two-phase Extermination…" Bidaen was excited. It wasn't just him as everyone started to feel an itch in their heart.

Garen's simple motion which involved a few steps and a gentle throw. The posture was very elegant and beautiful.

No one thought that combat would portray such a beautiful posture and so practical at the same time. It's as if this had opened a new world to them.

"Let me try!" The impatient strong man at one side couldn't resist any longer as he walked to the stage. "Bidaen, you take some rest and let me try it!"

"Be careful vice president, even I don't know how I was tricked." Bidaen nodded as he warned softly while walking to the side.

The muscular man smiled as he raised his hands and stretched his shoulder. He then moved to the left and right as he warmed himself up.

"My foundation is boxing. Be careful." He shouted at Garen.

The disturbance raised by the vice president had attracted the attention of the senior members nearby and even the coach from the other side started to gather around.

Even the new members from the other side stopped their training and joined the crowd.

Serena walked behind Garen and said.

"Be careful, that guy is called Jamie. He's one of the captains of the five elite groups. Excluding the president, the five of them are the strongest. Since my sister is competing for the president slot, she has to fight against them as well."

Garen nodded to acknowledge that he heard it.

"Jamie is good at uppercut and the ambushed knee attack. His knee attack is nicknamed as army's pierce. It's very powerful so don't assume that he would only use his hand as a fighter."

"Hey hey hey. Don't sell out your old friend just because he's handsome~~~" Jamie started complaining.

"As for me, I don't have any special technique." Garen nodded as he started to introduce himself.

"Let's begin." Serena became their impromptu judge.

The surrounding started to quiet down. Since the vice president and the elite group captain had decided to spar with a new member, it obviously meant that the new member was very capable and this attracted a huge amount of people to spectate.

Two of them stood facing each other on the stage.

"Since you're a professional as well, I won't be showing any mercy," Jamie said calmly.

"Sure thing." Garen nodded.

Just as he finished his sentence, Jamie plunged forward and attacked Garen from the right.

He got to Garen, who was three meters away from him in a mere instant and attacked him from his right, aiming for his neck. The fist in the air was whistling, just like a drill rotating at high speed.

He had used half of his normal strength in this attack. Under normal circumstances, this fist could easily punch through three to four bricks. If it were to used it on a normal person, his bones would break without a doubt. Hence, he preserved his strength as he was just testing his opponent in case that he had overestimated his opponent. It would be bad for him to severely injured someone.

Out of habit, he attacked his opponent from the side by taking advantage of his incredible speed to attack a person's weak spot. This was Jamie's fighting style. As for the poisonous pierce, which was his hidden ultimate move, he couldn't simply use it at his disposal as it would bring a heavy burden towards his knee.

The fist was going towards Garen's neck and suddenly, a swift sound could be heard and Jamie felt like his vision had gone blind as Garen had completely disappeared. Surprised, he stood firmly and attacked his back.

There was still no one!

Jamie started to feel the shiver down his spine.

He finally understood what Bidaen experienced where the opponent disappeared right in front him and only his footsteps and wind generated could be heard.

Panic, he used all of his might and his speed had increased by two folds.

He even used both of his fists to attack left and right at the same time as he leaped forward.

He tried to catch up with Garen's speed with all his might.

Unfortunately, he could only see the edge of his opponent's shirt.

He, who couldn't even see his opponent's figure, was not able to use his so-called ultimate skill, poisonous pierce, which was only useful when he fought his opponent face to face. Hence he wouldn't be able to use it under this circumstances.

Slam.

A finger gently landed on the back of his neck.

"I give up! I give up!"

Helpless, Jamie raised both of his hands up and admitted defeat.

The crowd cheered.

Chapter 595: Club 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

No one expected that the Vice President would actually lose to a new student.

"A newbie who is even stronger than Xander has joined us this year!"

"It's so strange, Vice President couldn't even reach his shadow no matter how he turned!"

"His stance is so beautiful when he moves."

"He's probably the newbie that Serena dragged into the club. We're going to have a good show soon."

A group of club members huddled together and chatted noisily.

Serena smiled happily. Tonight's presidential election duel would be happening shortly, and she had brought in a powerful fighting force. It seemed like Big Sis's position was now uncertain.

"How is it going?" She looked towards Jamie, who would be taking part in the fight, and asked him softly.

The latter's expression had yet to return to normal.

"Very strong," he said quietly.

"The uncertainty of the situation has increased!" Serena laughed happily.

"He might even be stronger than your big sister."

The smile on Serena's face disappeared slowly.

"The club requirements state that only the strongest member has the right to be the president. Don't forget that," mentioned Jamie.

"No way…" Serena gulped.

"Would it be better if that wasn't the case?" Suddenly, another voice interrupted their conversation.

The crowd dispersed as a tall, slender, red-haired girl walked in. There as a long and yellow-red line on the left side of her face that seemed to be a sword-fighting scar, and she was dressed in tight black leather clothing that consisted of a long sleeved top and long pants, while her loose long hair swayed as she walked over.

"Big Sis!" Serena turned around happily while running towards the other girl's side.

"Participants with graceful movements are always welcomed at the main competitions. During competitions, their appearance and looks are the main factors that attract the audience's attention. If he can really defeat me, I'll give him the president's position during his sophomore year," said the girl in leather clothes indifferently.

Garen walked off the arena with a completely relaxed look on his face.

He smiled while they cheered, and it seemed as if the entire match earlier was just a warm-up. This made it even more puzzling for the newbies and old members that were gathered around him.

As he turned to look around himself, Garen shook his head slightly.

The regular people in this world were too weak. When he looked at his surroundings, he realized that everyone, including that girl in the tight-fitting leather clothes, had pathetically weak auras.

They had even remained at using ordinary people's standards of strength and speed to determine their victors. The individual with the stronger muscles and superior strength, faster speed, and more powerful hits would have a higher chance of victory.

No matter how much time one spent practicing these combat skills, as long as they did not train their body and mind to evolve their martial arts, they would never be as powerful as a handgun. This disappointed Garen because his original aim was to see if regular people had any strengths that were worth his attention. Unfortunately, this was it.

Among those around him, those who were considered as combat experts could never be called martial artists, nevermind Grandmasters of Combat. This made him feel slightly bored. As a high-level expert Grandmaster of Combat, showing off his strength amongst a group of normal people who could not even reach the level of martial artists was like accidentally stepping on ants while standing on the road.

"Are you bored?"

Suddenly, a voice could be heard beside Garen's ear.

Garen was slightly shocked. He followed the source of the voice and looked over, before noticing that it came from the new girl that joined the club with him. Her long black hair was tied in a ponytail and her skin was as smooth as white snow. She also had almond-shaped eyes, pink lips and carried herself in an elegant manner.

She was a stereotypical Eastern beauty.

"You're disappointed in the martial arts here? That's why you're bored?" said the girl coldly. She had not spoken in a loud voice, but everyone had heard the things she had said.

The noisy scene turned silent immediately.

"Don't be ridiculous, an expert like Garen would obviously not be that kind of person," said a random voice, defending him.

However, the girl continued to look at Garen quietly without saying anything.

The smile on Garen's face disappeared and he returned her gaze and stared at her.

Seeing that Garen did not explain, everyone around him stopped talking as well. Since Garen did not deny it, it was now clear that those were his true feelings. This girl was right, the combat club had bored Garen.

A stern look appeared on Vice President Jamie's face. He looked at Garen and glanced at the girl while different emotions appeared on his face, making it difficult to guess what he was thinking about.

Serena and her older sister looked at Garen silently as well while the surrounding atmosphere became tenser at once.

The other club members who were present realized that something was amiss and gathered around them in large crowds.

Garen looked around. Since they had already seen through him, he was too lazy to disguise his true feelings anymore. It was too troublesome to continue hiding his true self from a colony of ants pretending to be humans.

"It's true that it's a little boring, you were right."

The corners of his mouth curled upwards slightly. It was an extremely rare sight that this girl had been able to catch the slight change in his gaze and accurately decipher its meaning as well.

The main point was that he had not detected any signs of abnormal powers within her.

A slight commotion occurred the moment that sentence left his mouth, while furious expressions appeared on the faces of some of the old club members.

"Don't hold me back, I want to kill that guy!"

"Big Sis Quentin is here! Let's beat him up!"

"We'll wait for the President and the others to arrive before discussing it further."

Some of them were emotional while others were calm. On the arena, some people wanted to step forward to fight Garen one-on-one but were held back by their friends. A few other members had taken their phones out and were beginning to make calls, obviously inviting others over.

"Our new member seems really strong, huh…" The girl in leather clothes took long strides as she stepped into the arena and stood on the opposite side of Garen. Although her face was very similar to Serena's, they had extremely different temperaments, making it easy for the crowd to distinguish her identity at once.

She was Serena's older sister, one of the Vice Presidents, Quentin.

"Do you want to spar with me?" Quentin glared at Garen with narrowed eyes while her slender legs bounced slightly. Her whole body seemed to be shaking slightly as if she was a coiled spring that was being compressed slowly.

"Although I feel somewhat rude to say this to Senior Sister Serena, I must admit that the combat levels here are quite low." Garen calmly disregarded her gaze. No wonder the Blood Breeds looked down on the regular humans. If all the regular people possessed the strength of those in the Secret Technique World, the Blood Breeds would not be able to look down on the humans completely even if they were any stronger, as they would end up suffering unexpected failures.

Unfortunately, the regular people here were nothing like the martial artists of the Secret Technique World.

A thought flashed through his mind before a good idea appeared in Garen's mind suddenly.

"You're thinking of leaving?" It was that same voice from earlier again. The new Eastern girl had interrupted him again and was glaring at Garen now. "Even the Vice President is not worth a fight in your eyes, huh?" There were some wrinkles on her brow, and it was obvious that she was somewhat unhappy with Garen's arrogance.

"Oh??" Garen ignored the emotionally charged crowd around him but looked straight at this girl instead. "The first time, I merely assumed that you possessed acute instincts and that it was a coincidence. But since it occurred a second time, it can't just be a coincidence."

A panicked look appeared in the girl's eyes faintly before she evaded Garen's line of sight.

"I'm just not used to your attitude. You seem polite on the surface, but you're actually unbelievably arrogant on the inside."

It was true that she had possessed sharp instincts ever since she was young, and was able to read the meanings behind other people's gazes easily, making it useless no matter how hard they tried to hide it. This was an extremely sensitive talent and was especially useful when she studied psychology on her own and was able to interpret the mentalities of others' easily.

Garen was interested in this aspect because he knew that if this talent was used during combat, one would be able to guess the thought processes of their opponents, making it an extremely excellent combat technique.

It now seemed that the humans were not just a pile of trash. These new thoughts allowed Garen to look at the girl with newfound interest. Suddenly, an impressive idea flashed in his mind.

They were unlike the Nighthawks who were already set in place. Most of the students here had some potential, especially the girl that stood before him who was even more talented than the rest and seemed to already have good basic physical requirements. If he granted them an Ultimate Technique and chose a Secret technique to pass on to them, they would be able to become experts of a certain standard as long as their resolve was strong enough.

They would not be Grandmasters of Combat but would be martial artists at least.

Garen's own power values were steadily increasing each day and were constantly being assisted by his potential points. He would have faced a slight threat if he had been swarmed by a group of Vampires years ago, but now he would be able to single-handedly kill dozens of them.

They were only capable of rough and direct attack methods like simple punching, kicking, and biting. To Garen, they were nothing but an eyesore.

During the time from the first year of junior high to high school, Garen was unable to upgrade a significant amount of potential points. However, he was able to break through to the third level of the Slaughtering Hand quickly. This Demonic Technique possessed a terrifying effect that could seize a living creature's life force, and compared to the two lower levels, the power of the third level did not depend on the evolution of the aspects but was focused on the effects of accumulated power.

As the most powerful Demonic Technique of the Demon King Black Sethe, the most frightening aspect of the Slaughtering Hand was its ability to absorb the life force of living creatures and accumulate it in both of its hands before releasing it when required.

The life force accumulation abilities of the third level were able to increase its destructive power by almost three times. Coupled with Garen's current basic strength, its power was almost equivalent to the peak powers that he had obtained in the Totem World. However, its range of affected areas was not very large.

In other words, his powers would probably be restored completely in a short span of time. Furthermore, he would be able to reach the Form 6 level of the Totem World.

Solely practicing his Demonic Techniques to reach level three would allow him to approach the godly Form 6 powers of the Totem World, and this made Garen slightly suspicious. However, careful research made him realize that the Soul Seeds were one of the causes.

It seemed that the Soul Seeds possessed certain amplification effects that increased his power greatly whenever he practiced his Secret Techniques.

When he returned to his thoughts, Garen realized that it would be troublesome for him to do the things that he wanted to do in this world if he was alone. Therefore, he needed to find a good helper. Perhaps he would be able to find an acceptable young successor among the normal people to be a helper that would be able to support him.

While strength upgrades were an important aspect to consider, loyalty was another matter as well. Both of these were key requirements that had to be considered, as it would be troublesome if they used the Ultimate Techniques and Secret Techniques that he had taught them against himself in the future.

"What's your name?" Garen returned to his thoughts and looked at the girl.

Whoosh!

Suddenly, a whip-like black shadow flashed beside the right side of his face.

Apparently, it was Quentin. There was a cold expression on her face while she raised her right leg up high and swung it forward while turning her body sideways. Her other leg was placed forward steadily while she struck directly towards the bottom half of Garen's body.

She used a great amount of force and by listening to the sound of the wind, one could tell that if she was able to kick her opponent's body, it would certainly be the most undesirable conclusion for a man.

Clap!

Garen caught her leg with one hand and held it with the other, before throwing her towards the left suddenly.

Whoosh!!

A black shadow flew past before Quentin was thrown out of the main door outside the arena at once. A series of screams could be heard outside the door suddenly before the squeaking sound of a body sliding across the floor followed soon after.

Chapter 596: Club 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The arena was filled with commotion while Serena screamed and ran out of the door. A large group of noisy onlookers ran outside and gathered around Quentin's body while she remained on the ground.

Quentin's face was pale while she lay on the ground. She tried to stand but was unable to hold herself up.

She had only suffered cramps but had not fractured any bones. Garen knew not to overdo his actions and had only planned to strike her attack position lightly to reprimand her.

Garen shrugged his shoulders and walked towards the doorway nonchalantly despite the hostile gaze of the crowd.

"You went a little too far." A muscular figure blocked his path.

It belonged to one of the two coaches that had been training them earlier.

He was a white man whose golden hair was swept back in tall peaks. His arms and legs were filled with taut muscles and a short beard grew below his chin. Meanwhile, his eyes were staring daggers into Garen.

"I'm the coach of this club. You can call me William," said the man as he offered his hand to Garen and shook it.

Bang!

A loud exploding noise could be heard suddenly.

Garen and the man crossed limbs, while Garen's shadow appeared before him unexpectedly. Their arms were tangled with each other's while they moved speedily, making it almost impossible to see their physical bodies except for the four shadows that intertwined with one another endlessly.

Bang bang bang bang!!!

Every time the noise rang out, the man's face became slightly paler.

Crack!!

A depression appeared in one of the walls while the man's face was filled with sweat. It seemed to have occurred when his opponent's fist grazed past the side of his face, causing more than half of it to turn numb. Before he could react, another terrifying, storm-like barrage jabbed towards him again, until he was forced to step backward continuously. If he was unable to retaliate in time, he would collapse for sure.

"Pretty good speed. Your rhythm is acceptable too."

Garen's voice echoed softly, causing Quentin, Serena and the others to gulp unconsciously.

"However, your speed and strength are still too weak."

Another explosion followed soon after.

Suddenly.

A cracking noise could be heard below the white male's legs while he sank into the light red wooden floorboards underneath him. He raised both of his arms up high to block the large hands that were pushing him downwards from above.

His face turned pale at first before it was filled with blood quickly, turning into a red mess.

Crack!!

The man's entire body sank into the ground and he was soon embedded within the floorboards from below his knees.

The students were completely silent.

That hurricane-like fight that happened earlier allowed everyone to experience the actual violence and ferocity that was expected in a battle.

This was true combat! This was a hot-blooded match!!

Excitement stirred within the hearts of everyone while they watched Garen pin the coach into the ground single-handedly.

"Abandon all weaknesses and get rid of your doubts, fears, and dreads. All of those things are useless." Garen pursed his lips and glanced around himself. "During combat, there is only one thing that needs to be done, which is to get rid of your opponent."

The arena was completely silent. No one spoke while only the sound of coarse breathing could be heard.

Some of the boys' eyes turned red as Garen had ignited the passion inside them, allowing them to realize that this was real combat! This was actual fighting! Killing!

Cold stares, violent attacks against one's opponents, strength, speed, collisions without the slightest hesitation, and terrifying pressure were the final goals that the numerous combat enthusiasts were headed towards all along!!

Garen looked around at the students whose passion he had just ignited before returning his hands to himself happily and standing up.

He had merely planted a seed inside their hearts so that his reputation would be spread throughout the regular people. After that, those who were interested to pursue combat and fighting would come to him naturally.

Frankly, it was just a temporary moment of excitement. He still felt that this world was uninteresting and other than the Witches and Blood Breeds, the regular people were not worth his attention. However, there was a probability that he would find an excellent seed among them.

Meanwhile, he already had a vague idea for a quicker method to solve the problems regarding the time taken to upgrade his powers and the question of loyalty.

If this worked, he would be able to form a strong human team that he would be able to control fully in a short amount of time.

Garen glanced across the enthusiastic crowd and smiled at Serena, before taking long strides out of the arena and disappearing on the lawn.

Since they were the outstanding students of Gullivier University, he would only need to find a few good quality seeds that possessed both brawn and brains, as these people would be suitable to become the core of his team.

However, the decision regarding those who would engage in actual combat would require the assistance of the Nighthawks.

But he would not rush this, as his ideas still needed to be checked carefully.

After Garen had left, the site of the combat club became silent again.

Although more than a hundred people had gathered here, only the sound of coarse breathing could be heard. The other coach walked forward and pulled the white coach from the floorboards. The crowd then realized that the white coach had exhausted all of his strength and was only able to collapse in a pool of his own sweat as he did not even have enough strength left to stand.

"That young person… is basically a lion!! A golden lion!!" A terrified expression flashed in his eyes. "I think he would have killed me if I was distracted for a moment! I'm serious, Jim! He would have definitely killed me!! Did you see the look in his eyes?! His gaze showed that he was looking at a dead person! I dare say that he's definitely killed someone!"

He lowered his head and ran all ten of his fingers through his hair while his entire body trembled.

"When I collided with him, I couldn't see anything but a golden mess in front of my eyes as that was the most eye-catching color on his body. I couldn't see anything else clearly. The collision sounded like a roar and that was the only thing my ears could hear. I couldn't divert my attention at all. Really…"

Coach Jim held him and patted his back carefully.

"I don't think he can be a coach anymore," said Jim softly while looking at Quentin and the others.

Quentin was completely silent.

"President!"

"The president is here!" shouted someone behind her.

A muscular black male student took long strides as he walked into the arena with an equally shocked expression on his face.

"I saw everything…"

"The new members this year…" Quentin turned around and looked at the black student with a forced smile.

"Give him the position of President then," pondered the black male student for a moment. "It's just a title anyway and it doesn't matter. According to the rules, only the strongest club member has the right to be the president. But now, even the…" Although he stopped speaking halfway, the meaning of his sentence was already obvious enough.

Both of the coaches were actually fierce professionals that possessed strength surpassing that of the students. The club members, and even the president himself were unlikely to defeat either of the two coaches.

"Both of the coaches should go and take a break first." A bespectacled gentle-looking male student walked out from behind the black male student. He was a slender Caucasian male who was dressed in white casual clothes who carried himself with an exquisite air and was clearly not of humble birth.

"Just give him the president's position," nodded the male student while agreeing with the black student's suggestion. "Us four captains and Vice Presidents of the Elite Team will not have any objections. It's fine as long as he's the strongest member, regardless whether he's a newbie or an old member."

Serena nodded faintly. Garen had shown her older sister mercy, allowing her to have a favorable impression of him. Although it looked like Quentin had suffered a serious fall, she had merely been inflicted with cramps but was not injured at all.

The main skeleton of the combat club consisted of the five captains of the Elite Team. Initially, none of them had possessed great strength but were merely masters of rich households that were passionate about combat. Therefore, together they'd provided the funds to establish the combat club. If they had not done so, the funds provided by the university and their meager competition winnings would not have been sufficient for the expenses of such a large combat club.

The cost of equipment, activities, constantly organizing training sessions and external incentive trips were all huge expenses towards the large combat club.

When they were finally confident about their strengths and were ready to seize the president's position from one another, an abnormal newbie appeared suddenly.

When Garen entered the club, the few members that planned to duel for the right to be president were now disheartened.

When the other two captains arrived later and heard about this incident, they were wary of it at first but decided to give up on the presidential duel temporarily.

Each of the five captains belonged to rich families and were also combat fanatics. If that were not the case, they would not have pumped so much money into the club during the past few years.

Once everything had settled down, they began to discuss the matters concerning the new member Garen.

********************

Time flew by quickly.

More than two weeks had passed in a blink of an eye.

The new students had gradually caught up to the hectic pace of their studies, leaving them with less free time for themselves. Meanwhile, the club activities had also started in full force.

Some clubs organized dinners while others held dances. Other underground gatherings that had never been heard of now organized character roleplaying games, causing the students' lives to become chaotic and messy.

Some students moved out of their dorms and rented houses with their girlfriends instead. The hornier ones would unknowingly put on a show for the rest of their university mates in a secluded forest near the university.

But they were only a minority. Most of the new students were still diligently working and resting.

Their burdensome workbooks and papers were constantly being sent back by their lecturers and teachers who asked the students to redo them. Some students were even forced to sleep at two or three o'clock in the morning every day while having to wake up at five or six in the morning.

Garen's roommate Alexander was one of those people. As his papers were not up to standard, two papers of different subjects were sent back continuously and he was forced to rewrite them. Consequently, he'd been unable to get five full hours of sleep for the past three days.

It was already risky enough when one's papers were below standard, but if he failed this course and lacked too many academic credits, it would be even more exhausting to make up for that later. Furthermore, the most important part was that a Gullivier student would be sent packing if they failed more than two subjects.

It was even worse for someone who had been a top student at their old school, as everyone who entered Gullivier had their own pride and self-esteem.

Garen stood on the balcony and basked in the sunlight while drinking coffee and reading a newspaper. He looked over at the red-eyed Alexander and shook his head, sighing. These were the sorrows of a student of a top university. There were many new students like Alexander who would suffer similar setbacks either because they were not used to the lecturers' cursive writing style, or because of other unknown factors that made it difficult for them to adapt to their classes.

These setbacks would cause unsurprisingly immense pressures.

Alexander noticed that his roommate had finished all of his tasks while he was left to fight alone. He once assumed that everyone was on a leveled playing field. However, the papers and workbooks had suddenly created a great divide between them. This feeling was like a terrible attack towards the self-esteem of the new students.

Could it be that he was truly not as intelligent as the others? If not, why were they be able to finish everything so quickly while he took such a long time? His initial confidence would be destroyed by questions like these if he was not careful.

However, these were merely regular papers that were used to calculate their results. When it was time for their end-of-term main paper assessments or mock papers…

Chapter 597: Legend 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"They either went to do their practice investigations or participate in the dance. Why didn't you go, Garen?" Alexander raised his head from his thick notes and asked in a hoarse voice.

"I finished the practice investigations long ago and I have no interest in the dance. What about you? Are you alright? Do you need my help?" Garen put his coffee cup down and asked concernedly.

"I'm fine. I'll be done soon." It was the fourth time Alexander had said this today.

Beep beep beep…

Garen's watch beeped and interrupted Alexander while he was about to speak. He looked towards Garen and smiled before burying himself once more in his work.

"Hello?"

It was an unknown number, but Garen answered it at once anyway.

"Garen? It's me, Serena."

"Senior Sister? What's up?" Garen leaned on his right side on the deck chair and made himself slightly more comfortable while allowing the sunlight to shine on the left side of his body.

"I'm using the club's public phone to call you. You… Are you free this afternoon?" asked Serena hesitantly.

"I'm alright, I'm been less busy recently." On the other side, Alexander turned his head towards him and looked over resentfully.

"Did you know? Everyone in the club has been calling you the Golden Lion Garen after you showed off last time. Golden Male Lion, isn't that cool? A lot of people said that your hair flew around you like a lion's mane when you moved your hands. You were so fierce and wild," Serena laughed charmingly.

"It's quite cool actually. But the club doesn't mean much to me because the people there were too weak," said Garen without holding back, while scratching parts of his face that itched faintly.

The creaking sound of a tightening fist could be heard through the phone faintly. Perhaps Serena had set the call on loudspeaker…

The corner of Garen's mouth curved upwards. Taunting these guys for no reason was a form of amusement to him.

"One of them might be unable to defeat you, but a few of them could advance at the same time though," said Serena seductively in a spoiled tone that even she found hard to believe. "You should come just for a bit. I'll give you a mysterious prize when you get here~~~"

Serena had already planned to trick Garen into coming to the club before saying anything else. This girl was seriously crazy to the point that it was excessive. Although her words were seductive, Serena could hear the crunching noise of her own teeth grinding against each other.

Not once had she ever acted this spoiled, even towards her own father!

"Alright, alright. It's going to be six o'clock in the evening soon. I'll come after I've eaten my dinner. Senior Sister, you are just too cute, haha…" Garen grinned widely while ending the call.

It would be good for him to visit them. The girl with the frightening intuition would make a good seed, and he had yet to get her name.

Garen rubbed his chin and glanced at the state of his Slaughtering Hand before realizing that this Demonic Technique was more abnormal than usual.

Its basic powers were nothing extraordinary, but when the life forces that it had absorbed were accumulated, its power would reach a terrifying degree. Furthermore, it would release the life forces of hundreds of people at once when it exploded.

"But it hasn't been accumulating much life force recently though…" Garen pondered for a moment before taking his phone out and sending a message to Baldy and the others. He gathered information regarding the existence of the Inhuman Beings for awhile.

Baldy and the others had entered the first-rate mercenary circle, allowing them to know more information regarding the Blood Breeds and Witches while becoming a channel of communication for Garen simultaneously.

He had yet to completely release the strongest powers of this Demonic Technique.

However, he had noticed during his normal practice that the Soul Seed's amplification abilities would cause the Demonic Technique's powers to become unusually terrifying. Moreover, it would also cause frostbite-like injuries.

"Although I don't know for sure whether it's a Living Secret Technique or not, I can definitely see that it's not a Dying Secret Technique… Interesting." Garen checked the state of his Secret Technique pane carefully once more before getting up and returning to his bedroom to change into a new set of clothes.

He bundled all of his dirty clothes into a pile before throwing them into a bucket and picking it up.

"Are you going to the laundromat? Take mine with you!" said Alexander frantically while raising his head immediately.

"Alright."

Garen carried both of their laundry buckets and walked out of the door slowly, walking past the bedroom corridor before going down a flight of stairs.

Most of the new students had left for their activities, causing the rooms to be completely silent except for the sound of footsteps that echoed from a few rooms.

The white dorms seemed somewhat empty now.

Dong… Dong…

The chiming of the clock tower could be heard from far away.

Garen carried the laundry buckets and left the dorm buildings before walking on the right side of the lawn. There was a row of little shops in front of the small path that was situated in the middle of the lawn. Students would carry their clothes inside occasionally.

All of these were laundromats. Although there were laundry machines on every floor of the dorms, it was unfortunate that some of their amenities were older. Occasionally, they would only get a pile of damp and improperly washed clothes even after waiting more than half an hour. Furthermore, certain types of clothes could not be washed in washing machines.

Moreover, it was troublesome for them to get their own fabric softeners and bleach. In the end, it was easier for them to just bring all of their clothes to the laundromat.

The students who lived in the dorms were either on scholarship or from wealthy backgrounds. Thus, they were unbothered by these expenses.

There was a simple public announcement board on the wall beside the laundromat, so Garen walked over and stood beside a few students to glance at it.

The board was filled with messages regarding off-campus accommodation. Some of the lists had their phone numbers torn off, meaning that people had already rented those houses. The off-campus accommodation was slightly cheaper than the dorms on campus, but the safety levels and distance were a separate issue.

The further houses were obviously cheaper, but a further distance from the university would obviously bring other problems.

Garen glanced at a few prices on the board before turning around and looking at his watch which read: 1:32.

"It's still early. I don't have any classes this afternoon, so I can go take a look around."

Garen did as he wished and started at the center of the dorm building before walking throughout his surroundings and touring the place leisurely.

There was a leveled area next to the dorm building that was filled with students' bedrooms. Next, the student apartment building was on the right side of the area after a row of shops. These apartments were much more expensive than the dorms and were usually occupied by the research students.

Further on were the teachers' residential quarters where the university bus stop was located. The bus would arrive hourly.

Garen strolled leisurely along the road around the university and saw a couple of students and teachers standing in front of the bus stop sign, waiting for the bus.

The sun became hotter during the afternoon. Some people carried popsicles and ice cream cones in their hands while others held beverages or homemade drinks.

Although most of the students were rushing around, there were others who walked around leisurely like Garen, wandering around the campus aimlessly in their slippers and pajamas.

When Garen walked along the clock tower, he saw a group of people carrying tripods and cameras. They seemed to be either taking wedding photos or filming a drama. A director stood beside them and yelled at the passing students, telling them to mind the camera lens. The two people who seemed like a newlywed couple would break away occasionally and drink something.

After standing on the side and observing them for a while, Garen continued to walk on the path inside the university grounds.

When he passed a large white church-like building, he saw a bulletin board in front of the doorway that read: Lecturer Niconia's seminar happening now — Our Lives. 3 pm — Drama Club's play: Black Swan Velvet.

There were already students who were walking into the church who chatted and laughed as they walked. A student couple was arguing on the side. However, they only quarreled for a while before embracing each other romantically. Some of the surrounding students that passed him whistled to themselves. Although the university was open-minded, publicly engaging in physical displays of affection right outside the lecturer's seminar was something that only brave people would do.

Garen observed them interestedly on the sidelines for a few moments before leaving.

On the other side of a little mangrove forest, there were a few tea houses and coffee shops with dark brown walls. Through the floor length glass windows, he could a few students who were sitting inside and chatting happily. Some of them were even waving their hands around animatedly while trying to convey certain opinions.

A group of youths in helmets rode past Garen on their bicycles with earplugs stuck in their ears.

"Coming through, coming through, coming through!!!" yelled the youth in front loudly while letting go of the front of his bike.

Brazen bike-racing within university grounds was against the rules, but it was obvious that these young people did not care.

Garen and a few other students that were passing by allowed the bicyclists to go first. Once the group had hastily left their line of sight, he continued walking leisurely.

Gullivier was a university that was built in an old area. It was rumored that this university had been established more than a thousand years ago. The university grounds had also survived countless fires and had to be rebuilt many times, making it even older than America.

Garen appreciated the clean, fresh air within the university grounds. While following the path, he ended up near his own dorms unconsciously. Next, he entered a red and white large cylindrical stone door that led to a white road in front. On his left was the library area while a slope that led upwards was on his right. The road sign on the side stated that this was the animal wellness center.

Garen pondered for a moment before going left and following the clusters of people that were walking towards the library.

A little while later, a thirty-meters-tall dark red building towered before him. It resembled a tortoise that was crawling on the ground. The doorway was on the side of the tortoise's body and a simple cobblestone path connected the entrance to the road.

There were numerous zig-zagging cobblestone paths on both sides of the library. Some led to the back of the library while others twisted and turned and extended towards further places.

Garen walked until he was a hundred meters away from the library area before stopping his footsteps and glancing at the notice board beside the road.

‘Library number 13 - 17 to the right side'

‘Library number 18 - 22 to the left side'

‘Library number 4 straight ahead'

The arrows from all three directions pointed towards a tablet that stood in the doorway.

Below it was a white stone sculpture that resembled a page, and introductory messages regarding the Gullivier library area were written there.

There were twenty-two Gullivier library buildings in total, and the largest and most beautiful library with the most books was connected to Nottingham's library website, allowing students to get the information they needed at any time.

The dates of the library's establishment, years of existence, as well as some information about certain people, were all written at the back of the library.

He glanced around uninterestedly. Garen did not enter but chose to walk on the lawn and little pathways between the libraries instead. The clusters of library buildings looked like dark red stones scattered and embedded into the green lawn.

Librarians who were pushing books through the aisles could be seen throughout the library areas constantly. These librarians were in charge of different libraries and were responsible for ensuring that the books were returned to their right shelves. They were also responsible for delivering the books from different libraries to the students.

Other than Garen, there were a few international students who were hanging around the lawn. Some of them carried cameras and took pictures, while others posed happily.

Chapter 598: Legend 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen was strolling through the empty areas when his phone beeped suddenly. He took it out and glanced at the screen before noticing that it was Mike, the chatterbox he had met on the road once.

"Hey, handsome. Where are you? At school?"

"Yeah. I'm just strolling around the school out of boredom." Garen stopped walking and looked at an older female student who was currently practicing her mock interview not far from him while he replied his text messages unenthusiastically.

"No wonder you're an outstanding student… Do you want to come out for some drinks? I have some top quality girls with me here~~~"

"Drinks? Alright, I'm so bored." After Garen had entered the university, he came in contact with Mike frequently. This fellow was naturally friendly and would message or call him randomly to chat about his university troubles. In short, he had thought of Garen as his personal ‘venting machine'.

"Are you bored of girls too? Did you join any clubs? I heard that the music club in your school is not bad."

"That's even more boring…" Garen leaned the back of his head against the library wall and noticed that the senior sister who was practicing her interview now had a frustrated expression on her face before she picked up a notebook thing and read it carefully.

"Hey handsome, why does everything bore you? Your life won't be fun that way. You know Kelly, right? That eastern girl from last time? If I hadn't helped her that time, she would've been tricked into having sex with that pervert. This time, she came out especially to thank me…" It ended abruptly as if the phone call had been cut off suddenly when someone snatched his phone away.

"Please don't mind what he said earlier." A text message came through at once suddenly. "Kelly is pure. She's still pure, I swear!" The other side of the conversation sounded somewhat chaotic now.

Garen smiled silently. He imagined that Mike was being beaten up badly by his wife Jelal now.

"Do you want to go out shopping together anytime soon? To buy some stuff downtown?" Garen pondered for a moment, realizing that it was time for him to buy some clothes.

Nottingham's weather and temperatures would vary greatly at different times. Sometimes, it would be sunny and the temperatures would be thirty-something degrees in the morning, but when it rained in the afternoon, the temperature would decrease. Although his body was physically strong and it was unnecessary for him to be concerned about keeping warm, suitable clothes were still important, as long as he did not have an excessive amount.

Garen was still very much an eastern person to the bone, despite experiencing and living in a western style world twice.

"Alright. My housemates and I were just planning to buy some toilet paper, a microwave oven, and a little fridge. How about we set the date for next week? Michael Selay's concert tickets go on sale next week and I absolutely have to snag one."

"Alright."

Once he finished replying the text messages, Garen waited for a few moments. When there were no more messages, he kept his phone.

He walked past the senior sister who was still practicing and passed the library area before a little zig-zagging, clear river appeared in front of him. It was seven to eight meters wide and flowed from left to right.

Thin shafts of golden sunlight reflected off the surface of the water faintly, while a few old men and women sat on the riverbank and fished quietly while listening to the radio.

There were sloping green lawns on both sides of the river. White granite benches were even placed in certain areas. He could see students holding books while sitting on some of the benches that were further away.

Garen walked by the riverbank, crouched down, and stuck one of his fingers into the water, stirring it gently.

There were a few stalks of aquatic plants that were growing beside his hand that moved along with the ripples that formed when the water was stirred, while shrouds of hot and humid air drifted over the surface faintly.

On the right, an old man who was fishing narrowed his eyes and glanced at Garen before turning his head and resting again. He seemed to be half asleep and was just waiting for a fish to take the bait.

Garen crouched on the riverbank and stirred the water with his left hand slowly before a few bright little silver fish swam over and nibbled his fingers gently.

The moment the little silver fish touched his fingers, it's body stiffened before it stopped moving completely. Its nimble little body froze and it died immediately while it sank into the depths of the river mysteriously.

Garen narrowed his eyes slightly and observed a black crab that was crawling bossily out of a crack between some rocks on the riverbank. The crab waved its nail clipper sized claws at Garen's fingers and attempted to clamp down on them.

Strangely, when the crab's claws touched Garen's fingers, its whole body stiffened before it collapsed and sank into the bottom of the river.

After witnessing this scene, Garen began to ponder deeply.

When his Slaughtering Hand entered level three, the frightening aspects of this Secret Technique began to gradually show themselves.

Most living creatures, especially the smaller and weaker ones, would only need to touch him before their Life Forces would be absorbed. The slightly larger and stronger ones would require strength roadmaps that utilized the flow of Secret Techniques.

The Slaughtering Hand was an extremely mysterious Secret Technique exercise as it didn't possess any specific power or energy. However, it resembled the Form 6 Totems of the Totem World which had a specialized energy because of the Living Secret Technique's fusion powers. On its own, the Slaughtering Hand could adjust the muscles in the user's body, as well as bioelectric currents, nerves, and hormones. It would produce a web of force pathways that were either exposed or hidden, and these forces would form a mysterious, complicated picture or image before finally forming a strange force that would attract Life Forces.

Magical hands.

That was how Garen described both of his hands.

Recently, when the time he spent in level three increased, mysterious powers began to form throughout both of his hands slowly. It had a strange but beautiful charm that he could not resist. He would look at both of his hands carefully from time to time, and would unconsciously be drawn to it, making it impossible for him to tear his eyes away.

This was very odd.

Garen glanced at his Attribute Pane.

‘Garen Thomas.

Strength 2.8. Agility 2.7. Vitality 2.9. Intelligence 2.4. Potential 558%. Soul Limit 30.

Seed of Soul: Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique.'

‘Violin grasp: Second, proficient level. (Three levels in total)'

‘Slaughtering Hand: Level three: Bloodshed. (Four levels in total, can derive and evolve to higher levels)'

Next, he looked at the information regarding Demon King Black Sethe.

‘Black Sethe, one of Ancient Ender's 42 Demon Kings possesses an indescribable killing talent. The soul of anything that he gazed upon would disappear immediately. Legend says that his hands were able to return everything to eternal silence, regardless whether they were living things or non-living things…'

"His eyes and gaze were enough to make souls vanish… Legend says that he was able to return everything to eternal silence. Does that sentence mean that this Secret Technique's roots belong in the eyes and hands?" Garen seemed lost in thought.

Strange changes had occurred in his hands now, causing him to unconsciously make guesses of that sort.

He considered his hands carefully.

He had ten, well-balanced and slender fingers. There were no unexpected water chestnut-like marks on his joints, making them unusually delicate-looking. His hands seemed like they were made of high-quality white jade as they were smooth and glossy, without any blemishes.

Shh…!

Suddenly, the skin on the palms of his hands began to sink inwards slowly, before two pits of the exact same size appeared there as if the flesh of his palms were caving into an abyss.

The depressions grew deeper and larger, and within a few seconds, the depressions on his hands had almost reached the back of his hands.

Whoosh…

The depressions in his palms rotted away until two holes remained. There were now two bloody holes at the center of his palms that allowed him to see the surface of the water below.

However, Garen did not feel any pain in his palms.

He was slightly shocked. Before he could react, new changes began to form throughout his hands again.

Numerous white dots that resembled age spots appeared on the back of his hands slowly. His skin began to wrinkle quickly, before shriveling up and turning old.

Meanwhile, his fingernails turned black slowly while the skin on the spaces between his fingers began to rot, causing small holes that made it possible to faintly see his white bones inside.

A sticky noise that sounded as if someone was stirring slime could be heard suddenly.

Pieces of pulpy rotten flesh fell off Garen's hands before falling into the water below and making whooshing water noises.

Beep beep beep…

A crisp text message notification noise could be heard.

Suddenly, Garen returned to his senses. He was blinded for a moment but soon realized that his hands were perfectly fine and that the rotting sensation from earlier was merely a hallucination.

After moving his hands for awhile, he suppressed the uncertain and shocked feelings in his mind. He took his phone out and glanced it before realizing that it was just a message that his phone provider had sent to promote some services.

Garen kept his phone and checked his hands once again, confirming that there were no injuries.

"These hands seem quite dangerous…" He was on high alert now. If his own mind had almost been stirred up by his hands, other people would definitely fall into this trap easier. The most important part was that there was no way to weaken this strange magic, as this was a special characteristic that these hands naturally possessed.

He vaguely guessed that the principle of the Slaughtering Hand was to constantly decrease and dilute the Life Force in his hands, or perhaps remove it directly to form a Life Force hole in the world, maybe even a vacuum.

This way, the Life Forces in the surroundings of his palms would naturally travel towards an empty space with a lower Life Force density. In other words, it was the same as constantly removing air from a specific area. When the empty spaces in that area came close to becoming a vacuum, as long as a small hole was opened when needed, the hissing sound of flowing air would be heard. That phenomenon occurred when the air from the outer world was naturally compressed and pushed so that it would fill the empty space.

When the same type of substance was in a specific space, the substance would naturally disperse from a place with a higher density to another area with a lower density evenly, before eventually achieving a balanced state.

Garen's mind interpreted it that way, as it was the simplest principle of diffusion.

He did not know how the Slaughtering Hand formed a diluted Life Force region. However, this meant that as long as he continued practicing Demonic Techniques with these hands, he would inch closer to reaching a true Life Force vacuum.

"Perhaps I should find something to cover it…" Garen stuffed both of his hands into the pockets of his pants so that other people would not be able to see them.

He stood up and walked towards the left side of the riverbank slowly.

He walked for a while before reaching the grassy lawn. After browsing through a few little roadside shops, he finally walked out with a pair of black gloves on his hands that wrapped them up snugly. His wrists and even half of his inner arm were completely covered by these black silk gloves.

He found the gloves in a cosplay shop. There were strange dark gold lines on them, and although Garen did not know which character they were made for, he could not deny that they looked very cool.

Garen wore the gloves and hid both of his hands below his long white sleeves to make them less eye-catching.

He looked at the time and realized that he had unconsciously spent two hours hanging around. It was almost 4 o'clock now.

He decided to just turn around and walk towards the combat club's activity area.

He remembered that there was an eastern restaurant there with a menu outside that listed all kinds of eastern dishes, and decided to go there and try it.

Chapter 599: Seed 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

While walking along the road, Garen was also thinking about the recent changes in his mentality.

In a normal world like this, nothing in his surroundings could pose a threat towards him. It was unusual for him to be able to be completely at ease like this.

This world did not have a special dissociating energy like the Totem Powers. Therefore, practitioners and those with unnatural powers could only depend on their own strengths to influence and destroy things. However, there was a limit to destructive powers like these. Moreover, it was also difficult for these powers to be effective in larger ranges.

Although Garen had lived for such a long time, he had yet to clarify the situation here. The density of this world seemed normal on the surface but was actually very high.

This applied to the density of the air, soil, or even the density of the bodies of living things. The effect of higher densities made it rarer for extraordinary individual fighting or destructive powers to exist in this world compared to the past few worlds.

As various materials and environments were hard to destroy, destroying materials and the binding force between particles required an extremely large amount of energy that would be impossible in the previous two worlds. In other words, it meant that the same strength would become much weaker here. However, there was also a beneficial side to this, as it was more likely for stronger life states to appear in this world.

Garen guessed that the higher ranking Upper-level Blood Breeds and Death Apostles probably existed because of this. They were able to live for more than thousands of years without decaying, but an existence like this was extremely rare in the Secret Technique World and Totem World. In comparison to the Totem World, the longevity rates here were clearly much lower.

The concentration of substances in worlds with higher densities would naturally be more susceptible to quantitative and qualitative changes in order to achieve higher levels.

Garen was now even more interested in the mystical elements of this world. So far, he had only come into contact with the cannon fodder level Vampires. As for the true Blood Breeds, he had yet to meet any of them.

While walking towards the combat club's grounds, Garen thought of the Vampire he had caught in Grano and the way he had described the Blood Breeds.

Perhaps his heart's desires would finally become reality.

The beeping noise of a new text message could be heard again. Garen took his phone out and glanced at the screen, before noticing that it was Baldy.

"Commander, I heard some news, or perhaps it's just a rumor…"

Garen's heart stirred and he stopped walking immediately before replying the message quickly while standing under the street light on the main street.

"Tell me."

The other side responded instantly.

"According to our insider, it seems like an internal strife is about to occur within the Blood Breeds."

"Internal strife?!" Garen was shocked. "You mean… The Light Party and the Secret Party?!!"

"Yes, I was talking about them. I heard that the Secret Party had recently gathered a large group of foreign powers in preparation to seize the American Light Party's control. The Light Party's current forces seem very influential, but I personally feel that the old man could just be spouting nonsense." Clearly, Badly did not believe this at all.

However, Garen was in deep thought.

The American Light Party represented the Blood Breed forces that were more inclined towards humans. They had always been relatively amicable with the humans and had even regarded themselves as an evolved version of the humans. However, the Secret Party was different. These Blood Breeds viewed the humans as livestock and a food source. Once they had occupied their territories, the world of the normal Americans would probably be thrown into chaos.

"Besides that, there may be some clues to something that resembles the Cross." Baldy continued sending text messages. "Rumor has it that an antique has been discovered in one of the graveyards in South Africa. The people there call it the Stone Clock of Fortune, and it has been said to bring good fortune."

"Send someone over to try and get it from an auction. Do we have sufficient funds?" Garen replied.

"No problem. There are many of them there, and our group has sufficient money," replied Baldy instantly.

Out of the funds that the Nighthawks' members received after completing quests, thirty percent would be channeled into Garen's account as his coaching fee. Whenever they encountered difficult problems, Garen would obviously come and solve them.

From the perspective of the Nighthawks, a group of people that were bound to Garen because of the Ultimate Techniques, this was a very generous conclusion, because they received an extremely strong commander that they could rely upon. Moreover, they were also able to learn powerful Ultimate Techniques. Therefore, it seemed as if none of them complained, or perhaps if they did, they were too afraid to show it as they could not leave these Ultimate Techniques.

"Besides that, we can start recruiting the exterior organizations." Garen pondered for a moment before typing the words and replying the message.

"Understood."

The core members of the Nighthawks that formed their backbone were almost complete by now. Meanwhile, the skeleton formed with mercenary organizations from the outskirts would definitely amplify their influence and increase their occupied territories. However, this process would surely encounter obstructions from the other territorial forces, and when that time came, the outcome would depend on each side's own measures.

Garen put his phone down and stood on the spot while thinking deeply for a moment.

This was not the first time that an internal strife had occurred between both of the Blood Breed parties. Unfortunately, it would always cause numerous casualties and fatalities among the innocent humans every time.

The Light Party's treatment of humans was more normal compared to how the Secret Party treated them, but it did not mean that they would be concerned about the lives of unimportant individuals.

"However, all of these are still far away from me for now, and I just need to focus on restoring and upgrading my powers." Garen rubbed his chin. "The best way to upgrade my strengths quickly is to search for Potential Points and the Stone Clock of Fortune…"

Garen pondered slightly for a while before putting this at the back of his mind temporarily, allowing Baldy and the others time to find a way before discussing this further.

He continued walking in the direction of the combat club's meeting place.

He walked leisurely for more than half an hour before noticing that a few clusters of people were already standing in front of the doorway of the slightly old, grey hamburger-shaped building. They were all members of the combat club that were dressed in their black uniforms who were displaying notice boards in front of the doorway.

Garen stood beside a school bus stop sign on a faraway street corner and glanced at the combat club's activities instead of going there straightaway.

He waited for awhile until it was almost time for the event to begin before making his way towards the Asian restaurant on the right side of the combat club slowly.

The whole restaurant was white and shaped like a round teacup while the interior was bright and spotless. Some yellow-skinned Asian students sat inside with a few black and white students. It seemed that the business was pretty good.

Garen found a corner seat and sat there before ordering a cup of green tea and a plate of fried rice.

As he observed the entrance of the combat club from the other side of the French window, the memories of the previous plan flashed in Garen's mind once again.

However, it seemed that this plan would now require his power to reach a certain level and be restored completely before he would be able to have the proper reassurance that it would work. Otherwise, his current self would not be able to take on the enigmatic and mystical Blood Breeds and Witches that he would encounter.

Adding manpower was important to ensure the safety of his own people. Sometimes, it was impossible for him to do many things at once, and added powers would be very beneficial in times like these because he would not have to do everything on his own.

His fried rice was served to him quickly. There was a golden fried egg that was sprinkled with pepper and a fennel-like spice on top, making it taste rather odd. However, the green tea made it easier for Garen to finish the large plate of fried rice in a few mouthfuls. Next, he took the napkin and wiped his mouth, stood up and paid the bill, before heading in the direction of the combat club.

A few people who stood in the doorway of the combat club seemed to recognize him at once. Some of them turned around frantically and ran inside before shouting for the others.

Admiration and fear flashed through the eyes of the two remaining members. Looks of disbelief were also present on their faces, but they merely stood on the spot and watched him walk over.

Garen ignored those two club members and walked right past the announcement board before entering the old large dance classroom.

The wooden panels that he had damaged earlier were now completely fixed. Furthermore, a layer of elastic bubble-like soft material had been placed on the surface of the floor as well, turning the entire floor of the large dance classroom black.

A row of people stood in the center of the room and was gathered around a black male student as if they were the stars and he was the moon.

Within the crowd stood the black male student while Vice President Jamie, Quentin, Serena and three other people that Garen had not met the last time stood behind him. There was a total of six to seven people, and behind them was a crowd of club members in black clothes with white spots who stood like a dark mess as it seemed like there were more than thirty of them.

The people that stood in a separate row clearly revealed that they were from a different grade, as there was a serious division between levels now.

When Garen entered through the door, ten lines of sight focused on him instantly. Some of them scrutinized him and others looked at him warily, but most of them were merely sizing him up normally.

"You're here," Serena stepped forward and opened her mouth after receiving the signal from her older sister Quentin. "The President heard about your recent accomplishments and decided to come over and take a look at you personally…"

"I came over today to say that I was planning to quit the combat club," Garen interrupted her suddenly.

"What?!" Serena's face became shocked at once. Other than herself, the faces of Quentin and the others changed slightly as well. Even the black President was slightly shocked and at a loss.

"I have absolutely no interest in a combat club that's made up of weak chickens…" Garen spread both of his hands out and made an impatient face. "All of you are too weak and I don't have the heart to keep defeating you."

"You!!"

The surrounding members exclaimed indignantly but were immediately held back by others.

The entire area became silent. Some of the club members' glares became colder while others began to crack their joints, the crunching sound of bones echoed slightly.

The faces of the President and the five team leaders and Vice Presidents of the Elite Team became unsightly.

"Every day is leisurely to me, so if I were to come over and play house and do some rubbish training, tch tch tch…" Garen sneered contemptuously. "Initially, I arrived with great expectations. I never expected that…"

The anger of youths could be easily provoked. These few sentences caused the sound of the breathing sounds in their surroundings to become more ragged at once.

Only the President and the team leaders of the Elite Team remained as stern as they were before but did not react immediately. However, it was obvious that everyone was extremely unsatisfied by now.

"If I were to let you become the president, how would you train?" The black president spoke suddenly. His eyes were ablaze with rage, but it was obvious that his self-control was even stronger.

"Me?" Garen had never expected him to say this. "The little chicks would not be able to defeat an eagle even if their numbers increased. Only a strong rooster would stand a chance of being a worthy opponent." He had initially planned to provoke the little fellows in the club for a while to see if there were any usable seedlings in the club. However, it was obvious that the other person's self-control was quite good, as he was able to restrain himself from using physical force.

These provocations were probably caused by his evil inclination, but he had never expected that the effect would be different from his wishes.

"Garen, you're saying all of this on purpose, but what for?" Serena spoke suddenly. She knew Garen's true personality because she was the one who had come into contact with him the most.

Garen glanced at her and said: "If I just said that I was bored, would you believe me?"

Serena's little mouth did not know what to say next.

At this moment, the black student stepped forward and walked in front.

"I'm planning to leave the university to go into practice immediately. According to the rules, the president's position must be held by the strongest member of the club. If you're unhappy with the situation of the combat club, you're allowed to come forward and change things as you please immediately. How about that?"

When Garen saw that the president did not get angry even when he was provoked, he was slightly surprised.

"Your patience is exceptional." He stopped speaking in the contemptuous tone from earlier before glancing at the members of the Elite Team.

This group of people possessed above average characters as they were able to suppress their own anger without interrupting the president's speech at all.

Chapter 600: Seed 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"I take back what I said just now, your discipline is not bad."

He walked straight into the empty clearing.

"As we discussed on the phone before, which one of you wants to go first? Come on."

He stood boldly in the area, looking around nonchalantly.

"I’ll do it!!""Me!"

Two of the Elite Team’s members stepped out, they were both boys with clean-cut short hair, one of them wore black leather trousers, and had an excited smile on his face.

"Xander, Candyce, both of them are the club’s strongest rookies, they always train together, and complement each other well, they might even stand a chance." Serena said quietly to her older sister Quentin.

But Quentin just shook her head. "There is a huge difference."

"Hmm?" Serena looked at her sister in confusion.

By then the two boys were already standing in front of Garen, and they exchanged a glance.

Chack!

The two of them took one step forward at the same time, throwing a fist each at Garen from either side. Their shoes made a sharp sound as they scraped against the floorboards.

Bam!

Both of their fists were blocked by Garen on both sides, and he made it look effortless.

They were not surprised at all, and with one on the left and the other on his right, they surrounded Garen and showed off all their strength and speed, swings, hooks, kneeling him, each attack strong enough to break normal bones, but he received each of them easily.

The three of them blurred in a flurry of fists and shadows, Garen not moving from the spot, and the two of them continuously turning around him.

Unbelievably, Garen never even turned around, he just used his gloved hands to steadily receive the fists and kicks coming from all directions.

"Velociraptor!!" Xander finally could not stand it anymore, he leaped back slightly, turned around, and kicked up a powerful shadow with his right leg.

Whoosh!!

This side kick cut through the air as loudly as a whip, and it had a powerful force behind it too, with the sharp-tipped shoes Xander wore as the focused point, it came towards Garen fiercely.

Xander’s oft-trained killer move, Velociraptor, was his strongest comeback maneuver, the key to this move was instantaneously using his explosive and substantial speed.

"Double Lock!" The other person, Candyce, also made his move, pouncing onto Garen from the other side, his two arms acting like a pincer, twisting around Garen's right arm fiercely, while one of his legs was jammed towards the empty space between Garen's legs, trying to trip him.

"Rather interesting."

Garen retreated slightly by taking one step back, and his body instantly twisted, and somehow mysteriously darted behind the two of them, his arms spread wide and flapping lightly, like a flying bird spreading its wings.

"There it is! The Two-Faced Extermination!!"

Quentin’s expression grew tense, and she quickly glanced at Jamie’s direction, last time he had lost to this move, so he was paying extra attention this time.

Right now it was not just him, even the president and some other powerful members of the club who had not seen Garen in action before were all now paying rapt attention to this scene.

There were two light smacking sounds.

Garen's hands tapped the backs of his two opponents’ heads lightly.

The whole area was quiet.

Even if some of the people here were seeing this move for the second time, they still felt as mystified and unbelieving as they did the first time.

What was up with that weird footing and turning? That stance was completely unsuitable for exerting and releasing strength, so how did he display such powerful strength?

With two sounds of impact, Xander and Candyce stumbled forward a few steps, and they finally could not help it, one fell to his knees, and the other leaned on the wall, supporting himself with both hands so he would not fall.

Both of them had instantly gone rather pale, as though they had not recovered enough, and could not speak at all.

Garen put his hands into his pockets, and looked at the others quietly, nobody else dared to meet his gaze, each of them subconsciously avoiding him or lowering their heads.

"How disappointing." Garen looked at these club members who did not even dare to meet his gaze, feeling a hint of disappointment well up in his heart. "It's one thing if you're not strong, but even your hearts are so weak."

He turned around and was about to leave, if there were only such weaklings and wimps in the combat club, he would also have to find another way to carry out his plan.

"W-wait a second!!" Suddenly there was a weak voice from the corner.

It was Xander!

He held onto the wall with both hands, pushing away his clubmates who were trying to help him up, his eyes reddening as he stared at Garen.

"I haven't lost yet!!" He squeezed out the words and propped up his body, this rookie who had just joined the combat club last year was now covered in sweat, the black combat club clothes plastered to his chest and back, his face was pale, and he was obviously dead tired.

"I! Haven't lost yet!!" He repeated again, staring hard at Garen.

Garen turned around, looking at this young man who was at his very limits, and actually had a minor concussion.

It was the first time he had properly looked at a normal person without any unnatural powers in the eye.

His seemingly condescending aura was completely gone, all that was left was a determination to never give up that bordered on madness. He was going to fight to the death!

"Xander!"

Someone was yelling his name, their voice trembling.

"Blood!! You're bleeding!!"

A girl ran up to him and tried to support Xander’s body, but he pushed her away obstinately. The overexertion caused the skin on his right fist to crack, and blood dripped onto the floorboards.

"I haven't lost yet!!" Xander’s eyes were red, as though he has remembered something from the past, his eyes were already losing focus, or perhaps he could not even see Garen's face clearly anymore.

This was a boy with a story.

Garen looked at the black president at the side, his expression was complicated.

None of them truly looked concerned, only a bespectacled boy with a noble aura slowly walked out of the crowd. He walked up to Candyce, who was still sitting on the floor, and helped him up.

"Xander, you've lost."

He pushed up his glasses.

"But even though you've lost, that doesn't mean we have."

There was a cold glint in his eyes underneath the glasses.

"Do it!"

The black president yelled abruptly.

Bzzt, there was a piercing sound of friction from the floorboards, and six shadows flew rapidly towards Garen.

The five leaders of the Elite Team, as well as the black president, all of them attacked at the same time, surrounding Garen.

Bam!!

In that instant, there were several explosions around Garen, several sounds of impact occurring at the same time, stacking into one very loud bang.

Fists, palms, legs, and knees came at Garen from all directions, his arms were like that of a Thousand-Hand Guanyin, countless after-images appearing in that instant, stacking on top of each other, instantly apparating at the places all six of them attacked, and blocked their attacks precisely.

"Not bad, not bad! Hahahaha!!" Garen laughed happily. "You all are not bad!! This is a seed!!!"

Nobody understood what he was saying, right now everybody! All the club members were all looking at the powerful figure surrounded by six others, their blood boiling.

This was a fight for the glory of the combat club, each of the club members gripped their fists tightly, clenching their teeth, wishing it was them out there on the battlefield.

There was the constant sound of flesh meeting flesh, echoing through the room, jolting all the members’ hearts.

"Let me show you what real martial arts are like!"

Out of the blue, Garen’s voice came from the middle of the barricade.

His arms instantly carved out countless after-images, blurring and stacking like the white wings of a bird in flight.

"This is the true, Two-Faced Extermination!"

In that instant, when he waved his arms with the black gloves, everyone seemed to see the spreading of a pair of white wings.

This discrepancy gave everyone an unconscious feeling of disgust, a disgust and nausea similar to dizziness.

The white feathered wings flapped lightly.

Bam bam bam bam!!

There was a series of dull collision sounds. The six figures were each sent flying backward, crashing into the floor and skidding for quite some distance.

All six of them were in exactly the same condition, their faces deathly pale, without even a hint of color, lying on the ground for some time and unable to get up.

The white bird’s wings closed slowly, leaving several after-images in the air.

Phew…

A cold breeze spread with Garen in the center, blowing his golden hair about, as though it was a lion’s mane.

Xander’s mouth hung open as he looked at his six bosses in the same state as him, and for a moment he could not say anything.

Just then it was not just him, even the club members watching in on the battle had their fists gripped tightly, their expression shocked, but they did not know how to react.

"You all… are all not bad." Garen stared at the six people lying on the floor, as well as Xander beside them.

Just then, that Asian girl from before that had left a deep impression on him helped Quentin up quietly, and even though she acted calm, under Garen’s gaze, her body still could not help but shudder.

In that instant just now, Garen’s presence was truly rather terrifying, to these regular students, he had already held back his aura as much as he could, but he still could not help but reveal some of his true presence, it was a quality that made these students feel as though they were facing a natural enemy.

That was the air of a Grandmaster of Combat, a natural enemy to all creatures, the true strength of the ultimate human fighter.

"That’s all for today." Garen held open his right palm lightly, and gripped it abruptly.

Bam!

There was the dull sound of a gaseous explosion from his hand.

It shocked everyone present into a jolt, all the members here were not ordinary students, they were at least straight A students, so when they saw that a human could make a gaseous explosion with just one hand, their eyes opened wide, their bodies going cold, looking at Garen as though he was an alien.

Only then did the black president and the other five understand, they were not at the same level as him at all. But the despair had barely risen in their hearts, before it was drowned out by their even more enthusiastic passion and pursuit for combat.

That was a new level of understanding regarding the human limits, before Garen came here, no one ever imagined that the human limits could reach such a step, such a level!

This was hope!

Garen looked at their gazes, and knew that the seed had been sown.

Indeed, humans could not achieve the level of a martial artist as he was showing here. But Blood Breeds were different, something of this extent was merely child’s play to them.

It was just that these students had yet to come into contact with such a level.

"Welcome to the true combat world…" He looked at Xander and the Asian girl meaningfully, and then glanced at the six strongest fighters on the floor. Turning around, he strode out of the training center.

Chapter 601: Seed 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen left this trip to the combat club with a feeling of mild satisfaction.

That Xander could be considered a good prospect, but his sense of hostility was too overpowering, so he needed more training. And that Asian girl was pretty good, under his presence and pressure back then, she still had the guts to stand up and support Quentin. That was the sort of bravery needed for combat.

In fighting and killing, the most important part was actually one’s heart, those with a naturally decent heart would attack without hesitation, and one-tenth of their power could have the same effect as others’ full power. Those with weak hearts would keep hesitating, and even their full strength would only be as effective as one-tenth.

Hesitation, terror, delay, these were all the most serious taboos when fighting to kill, as soon as you hesitated, your moves would slow down, your actions delayed, and naturally your power would diminish.

Garen did not have the time to train others’ hearts, so he naturally was only looking at their inherent advantage.

Other than these two having talent, the other six from the combat club were all quite promising, although their form had been set somewhat, and they required time to change them, they could still be considered possible potential assets, with a bit of tweaking, they could still become his remote limbs to help extend his reach.

All in all, the harvest this time was not too bad.

Returning to his hostel, as he expected, Serena’s message finally arrived after a few days of silence on the combat club’s side.

That Asian girl with the ponytail, Cece, was looking for him. But she did not know his address, so Serena was asking if she should tell her.

"Tell her." Garen lay on his bed, holding his cellphone. "Tell her, anyone from the combat club who wants to meet me can just come over themselves."

"Is that alright? There might be more people then." Serena asked quietly, she sounded somewhat excited as well.

"Has the word spread? Okay, then, you find a more isolated place, and bring fewer people. Everything else, I don’t mind." Garen considered for a moment, and replied flippantly.

"Alright, then, we’ll arrange everything, leave it to us." Serena replied with certainty.

Garen hung up, his lips curving slightly.

"Although I feel bad for you guys, isn’t it also your fault for being so easy to use?"

He was already preparing to execute his plan on the six leaders from the club, Xander, and that Asian girl Cece.

After some deliberation and time, he had arranged a new special secret skill from scratch, just like Nighthawk and co’s Shooting Shadow Secret Skill -- the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist.

This was the unique secret skill he had invented after taking some inspiration from the White Bird Holy Fist.

Upon activation, matching it with some special skills and moves, would allow the user’s hands to create an intensely powerful internal jolting effect to inflict harm on the enemy.

It was just like how he merely had to move his hands lightly to easily defeat the six top fighters in the combat club. The power of this secret skill lay in the user’s hands, upon activation, they would become a powerful lethal weapon that even he could not control, if the power was not controlled enough, just a touch would be enough to easily incapacitate someone. But at the same time, it looked light and beautiful, the instant it injured the enemy was as light as a waterbird touching the surface of the water.

This secret skill was even stronger than Nighthawk’s Shooting Shadow Secret Skill. After activating it, the user’s speed, strength, and reflexes would simultaneously double, the strongest was the Waterbird Fist’s internal force, gathering in the arms with great destructive power, he just needed to touch the enemy with one finger, and it was very likely he could kill the enemy invisibly. Used well, it could even kill someone easily with the touch of a finger, by making them die to an internal wound like bleeding in the brain. Soundless, everyone none the wiser.

Of course, the side effects would naturally also be more terrifying, it was a shortcut that could instantaneously increase someone’s power dramatically, so naturally there would be a terrifying price to pay.

Anyone who successfully practiced the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist could not let themselves stop, if they ever wanted to stop and give up, then after a certain time, the side effects would manifest, bringing the practitioner an intense and unbearable pain and itchiness all over their body. That sensation was several times worse than a regular skin disease, it was a powerful punishment applied directly to the nerve endings deep in the body.

If the practitioner still insisted on stopping, then the internal force created from the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist would backfire, and the practitioner’s blood vessels would continuously explode and split, the efficiency of their organs rapidly declining, and they would age quickly, their life fading away, until finally they died from a loss of essential blood.

As with the Shooting Shadow Secret Technique, this secret skill also needed Garen’s primer, every so often, Garen needed to give the practitioners a primer, to suppress the internal force of the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist in their bodies that was going to run wild. To use this shortcut to obtain immense power, but without a body that could properly withstand this power, they would naturally need external suppression.

This secret skill was a terrifying technique derived from the Slaughtering Hand Demonic Technique, if they were in the Secret Technique World, this secret skill would probably be a third-grade secret technique, like the Mammoth Secret Technique, but to the people of this world, the power of this secret skill was indeed far stronger than most normal people could imagine.

Since it was born from the Slaughtering Hand, only the primer formed by Garen, the strongest person who unifies the entire system, that was mixed with the aura from his Soul Seed, can properly suppress this internal force. That was why this secret skill was basically a tailor-made power system for him to control his subordinates.

Once the practitioner accepted his primer and successfully trained that skill, then the aura integrated into Garen’s soul could easily affect the practitioner’s life, or even control their body and will.

*********************

A week later…

In a manor in the suburbs outside the school.

Garen sat on a red leather sofa with his fingers laced and his legs crossed, closing his eyes as though in meditation.

The black president, Quentin, Jamie, and that bespectacled boy with the noble aura, six of them in total, stood awkwardly facing him.

The Asian girl, Cece, and Xander stood on the other side. Cece’s expression was calm, but there was a hint of excitement and desire in her eyes. Xander, on the other hand, was somewhat hesitant, his head lowered as he could not bring himself to look at Garen’s face.

Serena sat on a sofa by the side, also looking at them rather uneasily, glancing at Garen and then looking at the president and the other five.

"Please teach us! Those things you said just before you left, weren’t they meant to bring us under your wing?!!" As a girl, and a pretty one to boot, Quentin naturally took the initiative to speak.

"We know, simply asking someone else to teach us your secret techniques, is a very impolite request." The boy with the glasses spoke, "We can pay a price, in exchange. Allow me to hire you as the club’s private coach, how about a monthly salary of five hundred thousand? If it’s not enough, please, just state your price."

"Money?" Garen opened his eyes, the corners of his lips curving. "Do I look like someone who needs money?"

He naturally had no shortage of money, what he truly needed could barely be bought with money. Otherwise he would have long ago used some psychological or hypnotic secret techniques to amass large amounts of fortune. To someone like him, rules were meant to be broken.

"Then what do you need before you’ll agree to teach us combat techniques?" The other vice president spoke, she was also a girl, with short brown-red hair, wearing a man’s white shirt and well-fitting long black slacks. She also had the aura of a noble, which meant her family background must be something special, her only flaw was that she was not all that pretty.

"Whatever conditions you have, just state them, we’re all elites who are here to fulfill your conditions and are determined to learn from you. Why beat around the bush?" A boy with his hair dyed flowery and green crossed his arms and said coldly. By sitting here and posing like this, wasn’t Garen trying to up his price?

Boom!!

In an instant, Garen’s gaze turned, and it was as though the air in the whole mansion’s hall shook, a huge and suffocating pressure pressing down on this boy.

Bang bang bang!!

The vice president who had been all cocksure before rapidly took three steps back, his face instantly reddening, his pupils dilating, staring at Garen as though he had seen a ghost.

His chest rose and fell drastically, like rapidly blowing bellows, and in that instant alone, there was already a sheen of cold sweat on his forehead.

"You…!!" This vice president’s voice was shaking.

And the others around him did not sense anything amiss at all, they just saw Garen look at him, and then he himself was so scared that he had to take three steps back before he could steady his footing.

Quentin glanced at him condescendingly, normally she never really took this vice president seriously, she just thought he had some aura and skill, so she did not really hate him, but to think just a glance was enough to scare him to such an extent.

The club had five vice presidents in total, Quentin herself, Jamie, and Hochman with the glasses, all three of them came from families in the business field, controlling large corporations, whereas the girl with the short auburn hair, Raelan, and the green-haired boy, Dahm had families involved in politics, so they were truly the second generation politicians of America.

Raelan was still okay, she was more introverted, and had opened a bar of her own outside the school, so she kept a very low profile. But the green-haired Dahm was a different story, he was extremely arrogant, and lived a life of vices, it was common for him to have a different sex buddy every day, drugs, gambling, coercion into sex, all of that was normal to him. Earlier this year, he had even personally beaten a schoolmate to death, a young and defenseless girl, and in the end the verdict was self-defense, they claimed that young girl wanted to rob him.

And the rumors had actually been silenced by his old man, the final verdict being they paid a few hundred thousands and called it a day.

This incident made Quentin look down on this guy even more, but since he had a powerful family background, plus he was the only child that his family had gotten after so long, she decided not to break ties with him over an outsider.

In truth, Garen had also bought some intel on the six of them from the black market through the Baldy, the most detailed information about their backgrounds.

As the peak-level elites in an elite school, these people were all the stars of tomorrow for their respective families, the glow of a prestigious school to add on to their families’ own presence, so naturally it was extremely easy for him to get information on them.

Unlike the America he knew, the power in this world was still controlled by the authorities, and he had also seen the great achievements this green-haired boy Dahm had, forcefully killing that girl was just one of his many dirty deeds, there were more that just had not been exposed yet.

The America in this world was also controlled by the large corporations, the power of the public opinion here was nowhere near as strong as on Earth. Of course, perhaps it was the same thing on Earth, and he just never came across that level.

But power sure was a good thing… Looking at the green-haired boy, a hint of a smile flashed through Garen’s eyes.

Chapter 602: Seed 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"There’s an Eastern saying that goes, skills cannot be passed down easily. You’re asking me to teach you my secret skills, but if you don’t show your sincerity and determination, and I just teach them to you just like that, you wouldn’t appreciate something that you had obtained so easily, don’t you think so?" He finally spoke.

Looking at them, he continued.

"I don’t need money, so you can forget about that line of thought. As for how you will demonstrate your sincerity, well, that depends on your own determination, everyone has a different thing that they prize over all else. I’m not asking you to bring out your deepest sincerity, it just has to be something that would hurt you to give away."

His words made them all rather thoughtful.

It was only that green-haired boy Dahm who, after that shock just now, had a hint of hatred flash through his eyes. He did not say anything, but it was clear he had a grudge against Garen now for causing him to lose face just now.

"Sincerity, is it?" The black president frowned, "Sorry, my passion for combat is not enough to make me trade something I prize for it." He paused. "Apologies. Combat is just a temporary hobby of mine, to me, it’s just a way to train my body, this point is a bit too far for me. I won’t participate from here on out."

Garen was not surprised, and even the others were not surprised at all.

The black president was pulled into this to make up the numbers by the other five elite team leaders anyway, he did not have the strong family support the other five did, he still needed to fight for his own future, combat was just a hobby and training method of his, it was too much to really take that step further up, that would already depart from his initial aim.

So although it was unfortunate, that he could not learn that legendary peak-level combat technique, this still was not his final goal.

Shaking his head, he gave the others an apologetic glance, turning around and leaving the hall, and soon they could hear the sound of the door closing as he left.

Garen did not really mind either, he had long since noticed that the black president was not nearly as passionate as the other five.

And even if the remaining five did not want to learn, he did not intend to force them, the ones he truly had his eyes on were just those two, Xander and the Asian girl Cece. Their talents were strong and very suitable for the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist, their wills were pretty good too, once they learned it, they should be able to achieve a very high standard in a very short time.

Of course if the other five vice presidents could make it, that would be even better, that meant he could indirectly influence the wide web of connections they had behind them.

"How about we go it like this." Garen thought about it, "Cece, you start first, what I want from you is very simple."

"What is it?" Cece’s seemingly calm exterior also became slightly nervous.

"Go out for a run, and keep running around the mansion’s grassy lawn, don’t stop until I tell you to stop."

Cece widened her eyes, bit her lip and nodded hard.

Without any hesitation, she turned around and ran towards the door, as soon as they heard the door open, she immediately started running.

Everyone there looked at each other, they did not think Cece would be so serious.

Quentin walked to the window and looked out, and Cece was indeed already running rounds, not stopping at all on the green grass, her gaze dead serious.

Garen smiled. Looking at the six people here, the five vice presidents and one Xander.

The six of them looked at Garen, ever since they saw how terrifying he was when he exploded, nobody suspected what kind of power this soft and weak-looking boy had, he might be abnormally pretty and gentle when he was calm, but as soon as he exploded, his blonde hair flying, that terrifying destructive power could destroy almost anything, that wild and violent extreme offensive power, it was as though they were not facing a person, but a real golden lion. He could run wild whenever and hurt them, that feeling of danger and threat that almost seemed to prick their skin made them all more than a little stiff in front of Garen despite themselves.

"Actually I won’t force anyone either, forget it, let’s just do it this way, you all go run with Cece, don’t stop until I tell you to, how’s that? That’s a simple enough test, right?"

Garen said, smiling.

"No problem, I’m good at running!" Jamie grinned. "When the coach my family hired first started to train me, he asked me to run too."

He was the first to lead the way out of the house again, following behind Cece as he ran.

Quentin and Serena nodded, and ran out as well. After that it was the girl with the short auburn hair, Raelan, the bespectacled Hochman, and Xander.

Finally Serena clenched her teeth, and followed them out as well.(1)

All that was left was the green-haired Dahm, he clenched his teeth and looked at Garen, who was sitting on the sofa calmly, when suddenly he changed his mind, turned around and ran with them as well.

The terror of that moment had also raised in him an infinite craving for power. If I was the one who had that power… it was as though a torch burned in his heart.

It would be too cool!!

He studied combat not only for self-defense, but also because it was cool enough!

That’s right, because it was cool, just for that reason. He had been a genius since young, and was quick to learn anything, the only exception was combat, when he came into contact with it he was pleasantly surprised to realize that it was much harder than everything else, plus the moves were cool enough, and he could train up a perfect figure, so he was instantly enamored with it.

"Wait until I learn up all of your petty tricks, then I’ll get back at you!" Dahm thought sinisterly, and followed the others out to run.

Garen was the only one left in the mansion hall, he stood up, and walked to the door as well, standing in front of the mansion’s hall, he watched the eight of them run evenly on the grass.

How nostalgic…

A hint of remembrance flashed through his eyes, wasn’t he the same when he was small and weak back then, didn’t he also desire for and obsess over getting stronger?

Too bad… The eight of them were no more than lambs to the slaughter in his eyes, none of them knew, that the combat technique they craved so much was actually a demonic secret skill that had terrifying side effects.

Perhaps it was because this world never had anything like secret techniques, so they had no idea that the secret skill could have such an intense side effect.

The secret skill Two-Faced Waterbird Fist was not like the Shooting Shadow, the more they practiced this secret skill, the more they needed Garen to personally give them a primer, to suppress the Waterbird Fist’s internal forces as it grows stronger, otherwise there was the chance that they would die from internal bleeding, pain all over their bodies, and the general weakening of their bodily functions.

In other words, once they started learning this secret skill, they could not stop, if they stopped, they could trigger the side effects, and they had to continuously train in the ways of the secret skill, whether they improve or not.

Even if someone with great talent appeared, and trained to a high level, the effect of the secret skill was precisely that the higher they trained, the more they relied on Garen’s primer, and the more they were controlled by him.

Leaning on the doorframe, Garen watched the eight of them run constantly around the grassy lawn.

Unsurprisingly, after twenty rounds, Garen declared that Cece had passed, and after thirty rounds, after forty rounds, after fifty rounds, everyone had passed.

The lawn was very big, just one round was about six hundred meters.

Twenty rounds equalled twelve thousand meters, Cece ran until her clothes were drenched in sweat, when she heard Garen declare that she had passed, she just slumped to the ground. Thank goodness she had some foundation in martial arts, otherwise she really could not have withstood all that running, and even then, she had basically reached her limit.

The others had much better foundations, thirty rounds or eighteen thousand meters, forty rounds or twenty-four thousand meters, fifty rounds and thirty thousand meters.

The last one to stop was Jamie, he really was the best at running.

By the time they had all finished running, more than five hours had passed.

After all, they did not specialize in long-distance running, such a record was already very good, and they did not even rehydrate on the way.

Garen looked at the eight of them in front of him, all dog tired, and two of the mansion’s servants were serving them water, slightly salty water that had salt added to it.

"Now that that’s done, let’s start."

"N-Now?" Jamie asked, panting. He bent his waist, his hands on his knees, his sweat dripping down his chin.

"Of course…" As soon as he finished speaking, Garen’s figure instantly flashed, appearing beside Jamie, the five fingers on his right hand as though playing a piano, instantaneously hitting several tens of pressure points on his back.

He was so fast that his fingers made just three crisp sounds.

Smack! Smack! Smack!

Nobody could see how Garen’s fingers moved, they just saw a shadow flash past Jamie’s back.

"Close your eyes and feel it!" Garen’s figure flashed towards the rest of them like lightning, and the series of crisp sounds kept coming. "Pay attention and feel the qi pathways in your body!!"

His voice was like a clap of thunder, transmitted straight into their ears.

The two servants at the side were completely dazed, the way they saw it, it was only as though Garen had walked a circle between the eight of them, because it was on their backs, they could not see Garen’s movements either.

Garen purposely avoided the cameras and the servants’ gazes, using a secret hand technique to insert a wisp of his primer aura, creating a wisp of power inside their bodies, and leading it to flow according to the path of the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist.

His aura right now could affect actual things, not like the Grandmasters of Combat in the Secret Technique World that could only affect the spirits of creatures, so he was perfectly capable of triggering their bodies, and channeling the flow of the force.

"Feel the flow of the force, don’t forget it!"

After walking one round, Garen returned to his original position, and watched as the eight of them sat down one by one, their whole bodies stiff, their eyes closed as they tried to feel the changes in their bodies.

It was high noon, the sun at two o’clock unnaturally hot, and all eight of them sweated drastically, but none of them dared to open their eyes or say anything, all of them were extremely cautious, terrified that the movement and force inside their bodies would suddenly vanish.

After a full dozen minutes or so, they opened their eyes slowly, each of them with energetic gazes, as though they had recovered all of the stamina they had just spent.

"Miraculous! This is too miraculous!!" Jamie murmured, he gripped his fist, and released it again lightly, "I feel as though all my stamina has returned. Just in that little bit of time…!"

"Is this the true secret of the Two-Faced Extermination? That stance and move that do not obey the laws of physics at all!?" Quentin’s eyes were full of irrepressible awe. She had never thought that there was this side to combat, that feeling when she closed her eyes, and that sensation when her consciousness was guided everywhere by that icy-cold qi, it was like making love, no, compared to pure physical gratification, this feeling was even more intoxicating!

It was not just her, even Dahm seemed to be drooling, his whole body shaking, that feeling was even more satisfying than taking drugs, so much so that he did not want to leave it at all.

"That felt too good…"

Translator’s Note:

Yes, Serena appears twice; no, I don’t know why. There is literally no one else.

Chapter 603: Calming Down 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen waved his hand, telling the servants to leave on their own.

"What I will teach you now, is an extremely powerful secret skill that I know, a so-called secret skill, is a powerful skill that should be kept secret. The reason why it should be kept secret, and in fact should not be used often, is because it is too powerful, its destructive power is too brutal, and in ancient times it was considered evil or demonic, a terrifying form of martial arts invented specifically to hunt down and kill people. Of course, times have changed, and as the years passed, this secret skill had also slowly cut down on the killing techniques, and become more focused on strengthening the user’s own body, eventually turning into this peak-level skill I have here."

"Killing martial arts… I like it… Hehe." There was a nearly perverse passion rising in Hochman’s eyes behind the glasses. "Isn’t the very fabric of martial arts and combat meant to kill others?"

"That is true." Garen nodded, "I’m telling you all this, just so that you understand the roots, and the strength of this secret skill lies in that it can maximize the potential within the human body, turning it into destructive power."

Looking at the little lambs in front of him, a hint of sympathy flashed through Garen’s heart.

The passion in their hearts had already been utterly ignited by his words, when Garen designed this secret skill, he had sacrificed some of the agility in order to create that intense feeling of pleasure, and now it seemed to be worth it, even the weakest-willed Dahm had instantly thrown away everything else, becoming a rabid fan of this secret skill.

Seeing the hesitation in Cece’s eyes, she seemed to be hesitant towards evil or demonic arts.

"Actually, in the society now, the true power lies in guns, and there’s less and less place for martial arts to survive, as the heir to an ancient martial arts, even if it is evil or demonic, I can’t stand to see it disappear just like that, and be lost forever to history." Garen said, his tone sad and pitying.

"That’s why I plan to break the rule that it can only be passed down to one person at a time, I will pass it to you all, so that this ultimate skill is not lost from my hands." He heaved a long sigh, his glowing image immediately causing the others to idolize him.

"Now, I will officially teach you the basic moves of this martial arts, remember, you must channel that wisp of force in your bodies as you practice these moves, and continuously make it stronger, there’s also a breathing method here to match, you all must remember it carefully."

"What’s the name of this skill we’re learning? Is it the Two-Faced Extermination?" Quentin asked.

"The Two-Faced Extermination is just one of the moves." Garen smiled mysteriously, "It’s called, the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist…"

"Waterbird… The Two-Faced Waterbird Fist…"

Garen waved his hand suddenly.

After two crisp sounds, the two servants at the side directly collapsed on cue.

The rest of them were shocked, and looked at Garen in confusion, they had all noticed that the two servants had merely fainted.

"Don’t worry, I just put them to sleep for a while." Garen’s eyes curved, like two crescent moons, and they seemed to be emitting a unique magic to all eight of them here.

He spoke in a hoarse, magnetic voice.

"Look carefully…"

"This is the basic core of the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist…"

He raised his arms slowly, drawing out two straight lines in front of him, and when he reached his lower abdomen, his forearm suddenly folded outwards, as though he was hugging someone, or as though he was a veiled woman slowly spreading open her arms.

In that instant, they watched his arms move at a speed that was neither fast nor slow, yet it seemed to bring out countless after-images, blurring their eyes, making them extremely dizzy and nauseous.

"Illusory Spinning White Jade." Garen’s voice seemed to come from the distance, floaty and unfocused.

All eight of them watched his movements with bleary eyes, in that instance, it was as though all of Garen’s skin was glowing with a white light, they knew perfectly well that it was a trick of the mind, but they still could not help but hallucinate.

In that instant, the eight of them felt as though time had slowed down, their senses instantly slowing and dulling, as though they were in a dream.

******************

On the grassy field, next to mirror-like privately-owned lake.

There were many grey-white man-made hills nearby, with clumps of green grass amongst them, some dark-green or brown-yellow little trees scattered about sparsely.

Hochman wore white casual clothes, standing quietly by the lake, looking at the surface of the lake, completely void of any ripples.

It had been half a month since the day Garen taught them the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist, and in this half a month’s time, the eight of them did not get any more pointers from Garen, they were just asked to keep remembering the images they had of that moment. The Two-Faced Waterbird Fist was a basic secret skill, it had some strange killing moves, but it was not the full set of martial arts, so it was perfectly capable of absorbing their individual comprehension and combat styles, forming their own personal Two-Faced Waterbird Fist.

Hochman pushed the glasses on his nose, narrowing his eyes as he remembered the core of that perfect stance Garen had demonstrated that day.

"Illusory Spinning White Jade…" he murmured softly, but strangely, no matter he thought of that posture, he just could not picture it clearly. Similarly, no matter how he tried to ignore it, the memory just would not go away.

Like a seed covered in a white veil, it was planted deep in his heart.

For some reason, he only had one impression of that stance in his heart, that of danger, a bewitching danger.

"Interesting… How very interesting, hahahaha…" Hochman could not hold back the excitement in his heart, it was as though there was a brand new world in front of him. That feeling of discovery and anticipation, and that intense pleasure from that first guidance, all of it made him sink deeply into it, as though hooked.

Before he knew it, he began to stand by the lakeside alone, mimicking Garen’s pose from that day. But no matter what, he simply could not trigger the internal force inside his body into moving.

The foundation of the Illusory Spinning White Jade was being able to feel the internal force in one’s body that seemed to channel and flow, but it also seemed to be an illusion, both there and not, after the force was successfully guided, all of one’s skin would glow with a bleary jade-like color.

Hochman stood on by the lakeside reminiscing over and over again, mimicking Garen, and slowly, his stance became more and more similar, more and more strange.

Only he himself did not notice, unlike Garen’s Illusory Spinning White Jade, his stance was less demonic and strange, but slightly more domineering.

************

"Cece, why are you always so distracted these days?"

In the large classroom, Cece sat in the back row, her eyes rather unfocused, when she was suddenly shaken by her good friend beside her.

The lecturer teaching fervently on the podium had already pulled the mobile blackboard to him several times, erasing it and writing again, writing and erasing. She herself, however, had been unprecedentedly distracted, and the notebook in front of her was completely empty, white as it began.

"Cece, what’s the matter with you? Haven’t you been a bit out of it recently, is it that time?" Her good friend Tian Jing asked quietly.

"It’s… nothing, I just haven’t been sleeping that well recently, maybe I have too much on my mind." Cece forced a smile.

After that day, she often dreamed of that beautiful and dangerously bewitching stance. In her dreams, Garen’s face could no longer be clearly seen, all that remained was a blur.

As her mind wandered, the Illusory Spinning White Jade seemed to become to become a white-veiled woman, or a beautiful white bird spreading its wings.

Sometimes, in that instant when she woke up, even Cece could not tell the difference between dreams and reality.

"Cece, I think your skin has been getting fairer and smoother lately." Her good friend Tian Jing gasped suddenly.

"Really?" Cece reached out her hand, and looked at the back of her hand, as expected, her skin had clearly gotten fairer and smoother, there was a faintly familiar feeling about it, like she had seen it somewhere before.

"White Jade…" Cece’s expression waved somewhat distractedly as she murmured.

That was right, her skin right now was just like white jade, emitting a faint smooth and warm glow.

She had not noticed it at all, but as she kept delving into the knowledge about the Illusory Spinning White Jade, the aura around her whole body had also changed slightly.

"I’m so jealous, your skin gets better even when you don’t get enough rest…" Her good friend’s voice came from beside her, but she sounded so very far away, as though she was at the horizon…

Cece’s aura slowly began to become colder, gentle, pure…

Suddenly she felt as though someone was staring at her, and she turned around abruptly, the door behind her was completely empty, there was no one there at all.

A boy who had snuck in after coming in late was caught in her stare, hugging his books to his chest, and looked left and right in confusion, trying to figure out if he was wrong in any way.

"What’s the matter?" Her friend asked beside her.

"Nothing, I just felt as though someone was staring at me just now."

"You think too much, with a beauty such as me sitting next to you, it’d be weird if no one was staring." Tian Jing grinned wide.

Cece smiled, it was true that she was not as pretty as her friend, but she had a rare quiet and pretty air about her.

"Alright, let’s talk later, lend me your notes later after class."

"Come get them yourself."

*****************

Garen stood outside the large classroom, his back against the wall and his arms crossed in front of his chest, quietly listening to the lecturer’s loud voice teaching inside the classroom, and there was the occasional question or problem from the students.

"What rapid progress…" There was a satisfied smile on his lips.

These past few days, he had been occasionally observing Cece’s progress, and he was very comforted to find that even if Cece’s talent was not as good as his, it was not too far behind. It had barely been half a month, and she was already on the way to the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist’s true first level.

He had divided this simple yet overpowering secret skill into four levels, extending from the Illusory Spinning White Jade, they were Jade, White, Illusion, and Spin, the words representing levels one to four in reverse order.

Cece was now nearly entering the first level, Jade. As a normal person who had never learned any secret techniques or skills, her progress was not the result of any verbal teaching, and she had reached this level merely through that one demonstration and explanation Garen had given them that day.

"Truly, a genius…"

Straightening up, Garen slowly left the large classroom, following the mahogany wooden corridors downstairs.

Cece was the most innocent of the eight, and she came from Asia as well, so Garen felt strangely closer to her, and thus he paid slightly more attention to her.

Compared to the others, perhaps this girl was worth putting more effort into.

Garen started to wonder if he should continue releasing the follow-up secret skills that he had invented, so that he could properly train Cece up.

Chapter 604: Calming Down 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The secret skill was only a tool he used to raise his own forces as quickly as possible, it was fast-acting and powerful, but other than the considerable side effect, there was also one inherent problem that he found quite troublesome.

That was, if he disappeared or had to leave for a short while, the people under him would not have a chance to get their primers, and it could trigger an extremely powerful backlash instead.

And as he recruited more and more elite members under his wing, it would also slowly become a troublesome thing to have to consistently apply primers to each of them personally.

Garen was wondering if he should raise some generals that could control the members in his place.

Cece was under his consideration, but he still needed to observe her for a while longer.

Right now, no one in the combat club was fighting for the position of president anymore, the eight leaders had all silently acknowledged Garen as the only president, the true leader.

Leaving the teaching block.

Garen sat on a long bench by a small garden beside him, the flower garden was ring-shaped, and there was a black statue in the middle, of a little boy with one hand raised, pointing towards the distance.

Garen sat behind the statue, taking out his phone and sending Baldy a message.

After waiting for more than ten minutes, there was finally one reply.

"Boss, the Stone Clock of Fortune’s auction items are broken, should we sell them in pieces, or not sell them at all? I'm joining the auction tomorrow."

Garen thought about it, "Continue on, send it to me once you get your hands on it."

"Understood."

After testing for a while, waiting for the bell signaling the end of this class to ring, Garen finally stood up slowly, waking back to the school area he had come from.

*****************

In the time after that, Garen completely put Cece and the others to the back of his head, they would still take some time to successfully achieve the technique, and even if they succeeded, it would take nearly a year before the side effect was triggered, so he was in no rush at all.

Garen returned to that rhythmic and ordinary life he led before that.

He was dragged into joining banquets held by some other clubs, and met more than several tens of people over just a few short days.

They were all acquaintances he could just say a few things to, they might never meet again to chat after that, but nobody really considered that.

The story about Garen joining the combat club began to spread, and many boys came to him upon hearing his name, while many girls would ask him out to dance at the balls. There were even three girls who subtly or not-so-subtly hinted, that they would be willing to be his sex buddies…

To a lot of students, they clearly did not believe that Garen was as powerful as the rumors said. They were just interested in his good looks and well-mannered behavior, so of course there were also girls who did not like him,

The basketball team’s head cheerleader was also a first-year junior like him, she was a pretty girl with long golden curls, and she was utterly not enamored with him, every time she saw Garen, her expression would sour.

Just like this, his life in the first year of university was not too different from other normal university students.

It was just that their studies were heavier, their stress was higher, and there were fewer students on drugs. Of course perhaps that just meant Garen did not come into contact with him, but he had no interest at all in taking drugs, no matter how strong the effect of the drug, could it possibly more intense than the pleasure he got from controlling his own nerves with his aura?

From what he knew, the combat club’s infamous playboy Dahm had completely quit drugs. He spent all day mysteriously researching something, but nobody knew what, it was only when his useless friends saw him occasionally that they felt as though he had gotten somewhat more mysterious.

Garen knew, that the guy had probably learned the technique.

The reason why he classified the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist as a demonic technique, was because others could learn it too fast, and while it was fast-acting, each time one practiced it, it would come with an intense sensation of pleasure, this pleasure was much more intense than making love, it was the direct effect of the internal force stimulating the inner nerves. It made people addicted to it despite themselves, driving them to keep on training and training.

That was the characteristic of a demonic technique, there were fast effects in the early stages, but towards the middle and late stages, it would trigger unimaginable side effects, and be much harder to progress in.

This was something that even Garen could not control or change.

This was the natural law of the universe, for anything at all, it would be divided into thick or thin, easy or hard, and the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist was the same.

All he had done was bring the easiest part to the very front, putting the best in front, and putting the hard parts at the back, that was all.

The natural laws of the universe stated that if you wanted to achieve certain heights, you needed to pay the cost in enough effort and talent, the demonic techniques seemed to be a shortcut, but in truth the only difference they had from normal techniques was the order of things.

Some would prefer pain and then pleasure, while others preferred pleasure over the pain, it just depended on what they chose.

It was the same with constructing a building, to reach a certain height, you either had to spend a lot of time on the foundations, slowly climbing up step by step. Or you could simply make your basics, and rapidly build towards the top.

The former would have strong and stable foundations, if there was no fatal flaw, it could withstand even a more serious disaster.

But things were different with the latter, perhaps progress would be extremely fast in the beginning, and no one would be able to tell the difference, but the taller it was built, the more pressure would be exerted on the foundations, and the floors could collapse with the slightest trouble, much less an actual disaster or tremor.

It was the same with the pinnacle of any profession or secret technique, if you wanted to go higher and further, your foundations would need to be solid enough, that was the proper way. If you followed the demonic way, the higher you went, it would naturally become more dangerous, and at every step, you might collapse because your foundations could not handle the pressure.

This was the most basic law of physics, even Garen could not change it.

Of course, the many revision he had made also had their effect, the reason he could amplify the power of the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist so much, was because he had used the power from his own Soul Seed, and mixed it with the Slaughtering Hand demon technique’s force as a primer.

While this primer controlled his subordinates, it could also magnify and enhance their destructive power.

The price of that was this power was something their wills and spirits could not control, which meant they naturally needed the interference of external forces to suppress the side effects and dangers of it, to balance it out.

In other words, the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist that they were practicing was actually Garen’s demonic-styled Waterbird Fist, although it was much weaker, it still had the same impressive aura-like psychological effect on outsiders and enemies, it could create a seemingly hypnotic effect, and had a special living destructive effect.

As for the complete version of the Shooting Shadow Secret Skill, naturally the price to pay was reconstructing part of their foundations, so the progress in the early stages was extremely slow, it had practically become a proper secret skill, with the same principle as the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist.

If Garen were to teach them the proper techniques, he could, but the problem was it would take too long, by the time they grew up, he would already have achieved a terrifying level on his own, and would not need their help at all. In that case, what was the point of building his seed faction?

So he had no choice but to sacrifice them, at the most he would treat them differently depending on whether they were good or bad.

*******************

Smack.

"Full Lights! Hahaha, I win again!!"

Messi happily splayed the cards in his hand onto the table.

"Pay up, pay up! It really pays to be with Garen! Hehe."

It was not just the four of them in their dorm, there were also the two and three from the next room and the opposite room, they were teamed up in groups of two, playing cards.

The card game was called Full Lights, and it was Garen’s first time as well, it relied more on calculation and memory skills.

But these were undeniably Garen’s largest advantages, his calculation and memory skills were both decided by his attribute points, and right now his secret technique level was about to reach 3, so he was already entering a non-human level compared to the normal people.

Messi, who was teamed up with him, was grinning so widely his mouth went sideways.

The others just kept scolding them and cursing their luck. Even the boy among them who had taught them this game had lost so much his face was beginning to turn green.

"What’s this shit!" One of their black friends threw the cards down, "I’m quitting, I’m quitting, if I go on I’ll lose all my living fees too!"

This friend of theirs was undergoing an intensive language class, it was specifically for international students, but he improved rather quickly, at first he could barely understand any of their slang, but now he could communicate with the people in the hostel freely.

"Cards aren’t that fun, how about we play computer hacking and defending?" One of the young, well-mannered white boys with glasses suggested.

"Forget it, wouldn’t that just be you winning?" The other few looked at him condescendingly.

This guy was a computer prodigy, his short-sightedness was more than seven hundred degrees because he spent too much time on the computer. In high school, he had participated in a national anonymous hacker war, and had been the main offensive power in it. Of course, no one knew if it was his tall tale or the actual truth.

But even Garen’s little bit of hacker technique was nothing to him, he could be taken down in two or three tries, and then he would write ‘weak’ in large font on Garen’s desktop.

Just a while ago, he had designed a new game, it was a hacker game of offense and defense designed to look like an entertaining tower defense game, so even newbies who were not very good at this could play.

Of course, it still required basic calculation skills and imagination, these were necessary to break through defenses and swerve around attacks.

But the result was completely one-sided.

After that, he and Garen were called the Two Great Bosses of their dorm level, the Boss of Cards and the Boss of Computers.

Garen shook his head, bored, as he began to keep the cards.

"You were the ones who pulled me into this because you were bored, don’t blame me."

"Dammit! The move I just learned didn’t work at all!" Alexander said out of pain and frustration.

"Did you get your report to pass?" Messi asked offhandedly.

"Of course, who do you think I am!" Alexander patted his chest, even though he had evidently lost quite a bit of weight recently, and all they could hear was the sound of him hitting bone.

"There’s a lecture in the afternoon, it’s an economic research talk by that Professor Milo who just won a prize, any of you going?" A blonde boy asked from outside the dorm.

"The Milo who just won the McDermis Prize?" Messi was instantly interested.

"That’s right, he’s going on a guest lecture tour of universities all around the country, a few days back they said he was coming to our school, didn’t you see?"

"I was busy with social practice survey, see how I forgot about it?" Messi patted his head, "I planned to enter the School of Economics in the second year, I can’t miss this lecture!"

The remaining few yawned and began to scatter, while Messi discussed some economics-related topics with that boy excitedly, constantly spewing some complicated specialized terms.

Garen was not interested in this whatsoever, he was planning to study medicine, Gullivier’s two strongest aspects were economics and medicine, he had already settled on his direction of study, if he studied the medical field here, maybe he might reap some unexpected results.

Chapter 605: Startup 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Whoosh…

The heavy downpour tossed the trees back and forth in the wind, clumping up in some areas and growing sparse in others. The rain beat down on the grassy field, creating a choir of splattering noises.

Garen sat alone in a coffee shop on school grounds, lightly stirring the thick aromatic coffee in his white porcelain cup, looking at the bleary rainwater flowing straight down the windows beside him.

"Are you alone?" A pretty girl with blonde hair walked up to Garen’s table.

Garen looked at her, and reached out his hand to give her a wave, telling her to suit herself.

"The famous combat club president, Garen Thomas, ascended to the throne of the number one combat club’s president as a first-year student, and you convinced all the club members as well, tsk-tsk…" The girl said, her tone sounding appreciative.

She had a pair of thin willow-leaf brows, her eyes shining with a naked sense of penetration when she looked at someone, with none of the shyness women tend to have.

"Are you interested in joining our kickboxing club?"

She was wearing a pale yellow dress, her collar pulled down slightly lower, revealing a deep cleavage.

Garen ignored her, picking up his coffee and sipping it slowly, he was still more used to drinking tea, drinking coffee made his mouth feel sour, and really uncomfortable.

He was wondering if he should get Baldy and the others to bring some Asian tea leaves specifically for him.

"The combat club may have a few more people, and a bit more money, but the true strength lies with our kickboxing club. Our kickboxing club’s cheerleading team is the prettiest cheerleading team in the whole school, it’s jammed full of pretty girls, no matter what your type is, you can find them in there, and you should know, a lot of the members have already admired you for a long time."

This girl was practically a pimp, when she said strength, she seemed to actually mean the number of pretty girls in their cheerleading team.

"Give me a mocha, thanks."

She tilted her face and told a waiter who had come over.

"Will do, please wait a moment."

The waiter was actually also a student of the university who was working here part-time, he looked at this couple strangely, the blonde girl was a famous third-year school beauty, he knew her as well.

"Other than that, I noticed you have the same problem as a lot of first years, your social skills aren’t fitting in that well, are you too focused on your studies and not your social connections? No problem, our club will also passionately help out with a member’s personal life, are you still worrying over your social skills? We can help you find a perfect clique that will belong to you alone. It’ll be a perfect bridge for your social skills."

She was very confident, the kickboxing club’s cheerleading team was not made of just girls from their school, there were also the elite beauties from many schools nearby, as a top-ranked prestigious university, many girls were proud to have a boyfriend from this famous school, even beauties had their idle pride and ambition, what was more when it came to someone who had both looks and ability like Garen, if he wanted to be a playboy, a lot of times it was just a matter of intention.

"The way I see it, if you want to be a social butterfly loved by all, if you want to handle all sorts of awkward situations and problems easily, you have actually already fulfilled most of the conditions, you just need a little…"

"Too weak."

Her voice was suddenly interrupted by Garen.

The girl looked at him in shock as he picked up his coffee and sipped from it.

"I just don’t like to stay with a bunch of weaklings."

Garen glanced at her, and so the two of them instantly fell quiet, the girl stammered and tried to say something else, but she had no idea what to say. She had not imagined that it was not that he was not good at social relations, he just did not like to communicate with weaklings.

But she had her ways to deal with such prideful types as well, her eyes turned, and she was instantly smiling again.

"True, lions never like to stick with rabbits, but our kickboxing club has exchanges will all sorts of clubs from other big-name schools every year, sometimes we even get the strongest stars of the combat world, such as Graham Christine, Gadar, the Savage Tank Rowden…"

These names she mentioned were all famous Boxing Kings with titles in freestyle fighting, and they were even more impressive than the ones the combat club invited.

This was no longer a matter of money, the kickboxing club naturally was no match for the combat club in terms of finances, but the girl herself came from a family that ran a fighting club, these titled Boxing Kings were actually elites under contract with her family’s club, so they would naturally show face at her own club.

Garen looked at her, too lazy to say anything else.

"Uhm… my name is Terri, I’m now the president of the kickboxing club, if you’re willing to come to our side, I can give you the position of president, this is not like the combat club where the president has no real power, I have the whole kickboxing club in my hands, whatever you want to do, I will support you."

The blonde girl Terri had long since found out from her informant that back then, Garen had beat the combat club’s coach into submission, she was desperate to get such a powerful first year, with such a first year on board, it was not impossible for them to surpass the combat club as the number one fighting club on campus.

"I have the strongest kickboxing club behind me for support, we have the most complete and professional team of coaches, a professional team handling logistics, nutritionists who had worked for champions, a medical team, and equipment team, all of these are things the combat club cannot match."

"Waiter, bill please." Garen stood up and waved at the water nearby.

"Sir, this lady here has already paid your bill." The waiter walked over to them and replied politely.

Garen glanced at Terri.

"Then I’ll be on my way, you can stay here longer, the ambiance is pretty good."

"What a coincidence, I was planning to go too." Terri stood up with a smile, picking up her handbag and walking beside Garen. Looks like she was determined to stick to Garen.

"It’s raining right now, and you didn’t bring an umbrella, wanna walk with me?" She propped up her rack, and looked at Garen teasingly.

"I’m fine." Garen walked straight out of the coffee shop, and the heavy rain outside was actually rapidly lightening, and as soon as he walked into the rain, the heavy downpour just stopped completely.

Terri, who was just preparing to open up her umbrella, was completely struck speechless as she watched Garen walk out nonchalantly, surprise flashed through her eyes, and she quickly kept the umbrella, rushing out after him.

Leaving the coffee shop and walking down a small path, going across a slope, they saw a row of cafes and restaurants in front of them, there were several university patrol cars stopped at the side, and a few of the university police were chatting as they ate.

There was also a yellow-skinned female student with her parents, just walking out from the mini mart opposite the restaurant after buying something.

Garen walked to one of the patrol cars and stood there, his black-gloved-hands in his pockets, as he looked at the girl at the mart opposite.

That girl had long hair tied into a black ponytail, and wore a white dress, her features pretty and pure, it was the girl from the combat club that Garen had the highest hopes for, Cece.

Every few days, he would come to observe Cece’s progress, and each time he would receive a small but pleasant surprise.

Just like Dahm, this girl did not seem like much at first, but she got faster and faster as she went, her speed increasing tremendously.

He was not wrong, Cece and Xander were the most suited to study the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist.

"You like that type of girl?" Terri walked up to him, following his gaze, and instantly saw the girl Cece buying things with her parents at the mini mart opposite.

She looked at the girl’s chest, it was much smaller than hers.

"So you like this kind of little dumpling?"

"Little dumpling?" Garen could not help but curve his lips slightly.

"Isn’t she? That yellow-skinned girl’s chest not even half of mine! Why don’t you touch and see?" Terri leaned her body closer towards Garen.

"Unfortunately, I do prefer little dumplings." Garen returned her words exactly.

"Hmph." Terri crossed her arms in front of her chest, and watched Cece opposite them quietly, together with Garen.

The two of them did not speak for a while.

On the other side, Cece had not noticed them there, she was just taking her parents, who lived so far away, on a rare trip around to look at this internationally-acclaimed school, to see the place where she usually lived and studied.

She was not a self-sponsored student, and her family was not that well off economically, she was truly reliant on her scholarship, and was an excellent student who had worked her way here from her home country. As for her family situation, her family only had basic jobs, and they did not have much in the way of a family background or savings either, they were simple, honest normal people.

Every time she saw the pride on her parents’ faces, her heart would be filled with a sense of achievement and joy. She felt as though everything she had sacrificed up until now was worth it.

Since young, she had been independent, and every time she saw how hard her parents had to work so that she could live a normal life like the students around her, her heart felt heavy. This time she had finally entered a famous school, and her fees were all paid by the scholarship, plus she even had enough for living costs, so she could finally let her parents relax.

"Wait a sec." Just as their family was about to leave the store with their items, a white store staff ran out after them, frowning as he stared at them.

"Could you cooperate with us for a bit? We misplaced something from the store."

"Misplaced something?" Cece frowned. "You have sensors at the door, won’t the alarm ring if something was misplaced?"

"There are ways to avoid the sensor, please cooperate, please bring out your bags so that we can check again."

It was not just them, there was another white couple, and some other customers who had bought things had been politely stopped, but what Cece could not stand was how the staff had only checked the others’ shopping bags, whereas they insisted that Cece and her parents open their school and handbags, allowing their personal belongings to be checked.

"What’s the meaning of this? There are so many people here, why are you only checking our personal bags?!"

The two of them started arguing, both trying to reason it out, neither giving way, and both attracting more and more attention as they went.

After arguing for some time, she saw that her parents’ expressions were somewhat awkward, with more and more people gathering around them, until the elders’ faces were so red that their original color could barely be distinguished.

The father held the mother’s hand, but since they did not know the language very well, they could only watch as their daughter tried to debate with the staff member, until her face was completely scarlet.

"Filthy chinks!"

The father did not understand the foreign language at all, so he could only force out a friendly smile.

That scene instantly caused a few people gathered around to burst into laughter.

Chapter 606: Startup 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"You!!"

Cece felt the frustration pent up in her heart that threatened to overspill, she tried her best to control herself, but she still could not stop her chest from rising and falling hard.

She looked around her, there was a student that she had met before in the crowd, but sadly that person just stood there watching, with no intention of helping, and even took out a phone to film the scene.

"All of you!!" Her personality had always been on the cold loner side, and she only had one good friend in her circle, she barely contacted the rest of them, so she was not close with any of them at all. Friends who were not even in her circle were even less likely to help her.

In that moment, she suddenly felt all cold, she was surrounded by so many people, but not one of them could help her, it was as though there were only herself and her parents in this world, and everyone else was their enemy. They surrounded them, laughing, rejecting. Without a single hint of friendliness.

She had encountered racism before, but this time, when it happened in front of her parents, and she saw how her father and mother were watched like animals in a cage, terrified, Cece felt as though there was a sharp knife digging away at her flesh.

"Take out the things you stole! Or else we’re calling the cops!" The staff member pulled her hand, refusing to let go.

The university police officers opposite them had also noticed something happening there, but to Cece’s despair, they just gave the situation a few glances and fell quiet, eating their own food there, with no intention to interfere.

Quite a few people had taken out their phones to record the whole thing, just there for the show.

These even included the white people who had their shopping bags checked just now, in an instant, they were also in the crowd, playing the role of audience.

Smack!!

Suddenly, one of the students who had been filming was knocked hard from behind, and the phone instantly fell to the ground.

A black boot stomped right on it, grinding it down nonchalantly.

Ker-chak.

The phone instantly disintegrated into shards.

With a few more roars of commotion, some people in the middle of the crowd were shoved aside by a tremendous force, falling to the ground.

Two tall and slender figures walked out from behind them.

One man and one woman, both blonde-haired students, the boy pushed out both hands, stubbornly shoving aside the crowd.

"My phone! Bastard!!" That student yelled.

"Hmm?" Garen threw him a glance, and his voice was abruptly cut short.

That student was like a choked rooster, his face instantly turning white.

Phew!!

"What did you say? Just now?" Garen picked the student up by the collar, and suspended him in mid-air, his height of over a hundred and eighty centimeters was more than enough to pick the other person up with one hand, like an adult manhandling a child.

That student just happened to be the white classmate that Cece knew, he gulped down hard, waving his arms and legs about to try to touch the ground, but to no avail.

"A bunch of wimps."

He tossed this person aside carelessly, and glanced at everyone around them.

"What are you looking at, scram! Weaklings!" He looked at the crowd condescendingly, his body emitting a terrifying air like a male lion.

"You motherf*cker!!" A stout white man rushed out, aiming a fist at his back.

Bam!

He grabbed the man’s arm with one arm, straight as an arrow, and let the man flail his arms uselessly, while Garen’s own arm was as motionless as a steel pillar.

"Trash should act like trash." Garen pinched his head and flipped him backhanded.

The stout man immediately slid a distance away, his head colliding into the shop’s door frame with a bam, and he instantly fainted. Dots of bright red leaked out from under him slowly.

Some people had been spooked, and were about to run.

"Your phones." Garen looked around at everyone.

"Allow me!" Exhilarated by Garen’s display of violence, Terri rushed over and quickly took one round around the crowd, grabbing all of the phones that had been filming, throwing them to the ground, and stomping on them mercilessly.

With the sound of crisp cracking, there was also the sound of glass shattering, and five or six phones were all ground into powder. Terri even crouched down to check carefully if there were any memory cards left intact, if she found any that still seemed whole, she would add on a few more stomps, just for kicks.

There were people cursing in the crowd, but she just caught them and gave them a kick too, so soon enough everyone who had gathered to watch promptly scattered.

The university police seemed to know her as well, so they just all pretended not to see anything.

"Pres… President…" Cece looked at Garen with moist eyes, looking as though she was going to burst into tears, and her father walked up to her in a fluster, hugging her lightly.

"You’re still too weak." Garen looked at her mildly, and turned to leave. "Do your best to get stronger."

Looking at Garen’s back, Cece’s tears finally overflowed, and she nodded hard in that direction.

Terri whistled, and looked at Cece with pity.

"Poor Little Dumpling." She turned around and hurriedly followed Garen, walking directly towards the restaurant where the university police were sitting.

"Little Dumpling?" Cece could not comprehend what that meant.

She could only look on in confusion as the two of them entered the small restaurant opposite.

"What are you doing!? Assaulting the police!!"

"Subdue him!!"

"Requesting for back-up! Back… Bleurgh!!"

Soon, there were the sounds of crashing cutlery coming from the restaurant opposite her, as well as human cries of pain and anguish.

In no time at all, Garen and Terri walked out without a care in the world, Terri even looked excited, continuously working her reddening fist.

As the student passersby and Cece’s family watched on in a daze, they slowly disappeared down a distant grassy slope.

For some reason, Cece suddenly felt a wave of hot blood rush to her brain, she suddenly sort of idolized Garen’s back, that tall figure was just that suave, that powerful and broad, as though it carried a golden corona like the sun, so blinding you could barely open your eyes.

******************

"It feels great to cause trouble!!" Terri giggled as she followed beside Garen, her face full of excitement and exhilaration.

From the very first moment she saw this man, she sensed that he was no ordinary man. And she was right.

Just two minutes ago, not only did she beat up the gathered onlookers with this man, they even beat up the university police and security personnel who patrolled the school, and it was practically like beating up kindergarteners.

That dominating aura, to be able to give no shits and forgo all the rules, made Terri feel as though she was going to orgasm.

"Are you worrying about the consequences?" Terri giggled as she rushed in front of Garen.

"Consequences? What consequences?" Garen retorted.

"Not only did we hit innocent bystanders, we even beat up the university police, you should know that these are officers sent from the town police station, they’re not just here for security. Aren’t you worried?" Terri was so excited that he face was blushing.

"I’ll leave it to you, any problems?"

Terri shrugged helplessly.

Garen ignored her, assaulting an officer could be trivial or serious, but naturally his methods were beyond the imagination of normal people.

Forget his parents’ connections, just those Elite Team leaders from the combat club all had powerful families, this little bit was nothing. Since they all wanted something from him, these people would stop at nothing to settle matters for him.

Even if it got a little more complicated, he just had to make a trip to the police station himself, there were many secret techniques that had a hypnotic effect, although the control was only temporary, but once the matter blew over, who would still remember these few tiny officers who were beaten up by students? Perhaps by then they would be unemployed, for all he knew those tiny officers would have been fired by then.

To him, this problem was not even a problem.

To his slight comfort, this incident might have sparked a new thirst for power in Cece, even if things did not go that way, at the very least it would have ignited her spirit and determination.

She had good talent and a good heart, she just lacked a heart that desired to grow stronger, she lacked a strong enough motivation. Perhaps this incident would give her the push she needed.

On the other hand, he had been an Asian as well, so he did not really like this racism either, this was one of the key reason he had gone straight up and used violence. Right now, he could do as he liked, no one could hold him back, or stop him,

But this world was like his breathing space, he did not really want it to end up like the past few worlds, where he was just killing and killing all day without rest. He would still need to summarily obey some rules, otherwise he might change his peaceful life irrevocably.

"What are we doing now?" Terri was dead-set on following Garen from now on, it was just too fun, compared to any orgies or crazy parties, this was much more exciting.

"Going to a fixed location with the combat club, it just happens to the promised time." Garen replied offhandedly.

"Promised time? I’m going too!" Terri did not shirk back in the slightest. Right now, her desire to pull Garen into the kickboxing club was growing stronger and stronger.

The two of them took twists and turns on the school’s grassy fields, until Terri was growing dizzy, but she noticed that Garen was not looking at the signs at all, he seemed to be simply turning about, carefree.

After quickly taking out their phones to get someone to help settle that incident, they soon reach a small grassy field next to a little river.

There were people from the combat club on guard here, one glance would tell you that they were not students, each of them thick and burly, they were evidently the bodyguards the Elite Team leaders had invited here personally.

This field was surrounded on all sides by barren hills, it just happened to be in a sunken swamp, like a small mountain valley.

There were already several people standing on the grass, they all wore the neat black combat club attire. Dressed all in black, they had a black belt tied around their waists, and were dressed very neatly.

Quentin, Jamie, Dahm, Hochman, and that auburn-haired girl Raelan.

All five vice presidents were here.

Garen brought Terri past where the bodyguards stood, the guards glanced at Terri, but probably because Garen was the one bringing her, they did not stop her.

The two of them walked down the slope slowly, standing on the field where the others were.

"Today we begin the first official training." Garen looked at the five vice presidents in front of him and said calmly, "Are you all ready?"

The five of them exchanged glances, said nothing, but nodded hard towards Garen one by one.

The five of them had truly become fanatics of the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist, after experiencing that unbelievably intense pleasure, their previous lives had lost all their color, non-stop training was the only rhythm in their lives.

Feeling themselves growing in the midst of the pleasure, was a sense of addiction several times more intense than drugs!

"President, you brought Terri here because…?" Quentin asked.

"She’s just here to observe our regular training." Garen smiled ever so mildly.

In this time, in order to have the five of them keep up with Cece’s and Xander’s progress, Garen had used a special skill, allowing them to keep up with the two prodigies while in a certain state.

Under this special training, even Dahm, who always harbored hatred towards Garen, had utterly given up on getting revenge, and was instead unbelievably terrified. Of course, this was also well within Garen’s predictions.

"Special training?" As expected, Terri was instantly interested. "Can I join as well?"

"Unfortunately, your body has yet to reach the bare minimum requirements." Garen shook his head slightly.

Chapter 607: Startup 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"The bare minimum requirements?" Terri asked in confusion. "Is this training very powerful? Shouldn’t you keep it a secret from me, your rival?"

"That’s not necessary." Garen had no intention to chase her away, he just smiled slightly. This person had an innate sense of madness and recklessness, he just needed to provoke her a bit, and that might create an unexpected effect. She was also a princess-type with a considerable family background, once he controlled her, she might still have some uses.

Looking at the other five on the field, all five of their faces were looking vaguely pale, they had all become quite nervous, their bodies all demonstrating how uptight and aware they were.

"Are you ready?"

"Let’s do it!"

Jamie clenched his teeth, arched his body and posed as though ready to pounce.

Whoosh…

A slight breeze blew past them.

Garen raised his right hand slightly, opening his palm, as though trying to catch the breeze as it went past.

"Go!"

Someone yelled out, but nobody knew who.

The five people on the field all pounced abruptly, rushing towards Garen. The six figures were instantly entangled together.

Bam!

Garen’s arm crashed into Jamie’s abdomen hard, transmitted out some force, and instantly sent Jamie flying two meters away. He turned around, grabbing with his hands, and precisely catching Quentin’s and Raelan’s legs flying towards him, and sent them bending down.

Ker-chak!

The two legs instantly emitted a crisp sound, the bone evidently broken. The two of them gave a scream, stumbled back and nearly tripped.

Smack!

A fist hit Garen’s back hard, but it was as though he had hit a wooden plank, it just sunk in slightly. The fist was immediately caught by a hand, which pulled it forward, and Hochman’s body was pulled towards Garen, until suddenly he felt a pain in his chest.

A knee to the chest.

Hochman flew out far, and fell onto the field hard.

He could feel his chest cracking, his muscles in agony as though torn apart.

The last one, Dahm, kicked hard at Garen’s abdomen, taking the split second window when Garen was tossing Hochman aside.

But unfortunately, the last thing he saw was Garen’s turning around and sweeping a kick at him, his long leg becoming a black whip that flew at him at high speed.

Bam!

His waist was directly hit by that leg whip, and he flew out abruptly as though he had been broken in half. With a splash, he crashed into the stream beside them, triggering a huge explosion of water.

Garen took a few steps towards him, pulled him out of the river with one hand, and landed a vicious fist in his stomach.

Bang! Bleurgh!

Dahm’s body arched as he vomited in agony, after Garen released him, he fell kneeling by the riverside, and did not get up immediately, even his pupils losing a bit of their focus from the pain.

"Hah!!" Garen was about to pick up Dahm and continue beating him up, when suddenly there was a bark from behind him, and Jamie flew up to stomp down hard on Garen.

With a dull wham, this kick landed perfectly on the back of Garen’s kneecap.

This was the angle that made it hardest to apply any force, any normal person would not be able to resist bending their leg when hit in that position.

But unfortunately Garen did not react at all, as though this kick had not stomped onto his body.

His mouth split into a grin, and he turned around, his right arm smashing towards Jamie hard like a stick.

After getting that kick in, Jamie reacted extremely quickly, shielding his chest with his arms, and his whole body in a completely defensive stance. As soon as he steadied his stance, he felt as though a train had collided into his arms, and his bones had a painful sound of cracking and breaking, his whole body flew out backwards as though riding the wind, and everything around him moved at breakneck speeds, so that they could not even be seen properly.

Splash!

"Ahhh!!!"

He was the second person to be knocked into the river.

On the field just then, the two girls, Quentin and Raelan, were locking Garen’s neck from either side.

Their four arms were crossed like a lock, tying down his neck hard, the girls’ faces were blushed red, they had evidently used all the strength they had.

Bam!

Blood leaked out from the corners of Hochman’s lips, but he held Garen’s right leg tightly.

At the same time, Dahm was also hugging Garen’s left leg with all his strength.

"Ahhhhh!!!" Jamie crawled out of the river, standing up and rushing like mad towards Garen, lifting one leg and stomping down hard towards his stomach.

"You’ve improved." Garen’s face split into a grin, his cold white teeth making the others feel cold even under the sun.

Just when Jamie was about to hit him.

All of Garen’s muscles and features abruptly shone with a hint of black, and bulged up fiercely and instantly.

Boom!!!

The four of them were blown away by a huge explosive force at the same time.

Garen’s fist crashed into Jamie’s leg.

Bam bam bam bam!!

After four consecutive explosive sounds, Jamie screamed out in agony, hugged his knee and knelt onto the ground, tears and snot flowing everywhere.

In that instant, Garen had landed four consecutive hits on the sole of his foot. Each of the four punches had landed in the same place, the same spot.

Everything fell calm again.

Garen stretched his neck, making it crack.

With him in the center, the four vice presidents were lying all over the floor, only Jamie was half-kneeling, crying in pain.

"You’ve improved since the last time, but when you try to gang up on someone, you still need to consider the difference in power."

Nobody around him replied, the five vice presidents either had broken bones, or they were in too much pain to stand.

"I give you half an hour to recover."

He began to walk towards the five of them respectively, his fingers instantly becoming a blur, after he dotted one of them on the head a few times, he walked to where the next person was.

Sometimes he would kick them impatiently, eliciting a moan of pain from the patient.

Beside them, Terri’s whole body had gone numb after watching them, her previous excitement shocked away to the ends of the world.

"This… this is training?!" She felt as though this was no longer a brawl, but an attempted murder! A blatant attempt at murder!

Look at Quentin, one of her legs had been broken, her right arm was twisted at an unnatural angle, no matter how she looked at it, this was a serious injury, right?

And there was Jamie, his chest had sunk in slightly, are you sure he can still move?

And the worst was Dahm, that legendary playboy had his head hanging loosely from his neck, as though his neck bones had all been pulled out. His eyes were lifeless, his mouth foaming. Terri had already pulled out her phone and was going to call the cops…

And then, a shocking scene unfolded before her eyes.

The casualties who were dotted by Garen with his fingers, actually seemed to be able to stand in just a dozen seconds. Although they were all grunting in pain, it was already much better than before.

"Are you an idiot? You’d call the cops over something as trivial as this?" Hochman walked past her, looking at the number she had dialed, and his tone was instantly condescending.

Terri’s phone dropped to the ground, pointing at Hochman. Her face looked like she had seen a ghost, her mouth only stammering you you you but not getting a single word out.

She had obviously seen Hochman pass out from the shock, just like Jamie, Hochman had broken at least two ribs!!

And now??

"It’s just a tiny injury, don’t blow it out of proportion." Quentin also continued, shaking her head.

The others all seemed used to it, although they were grunting in pain, none of them were angry in the slightest.

"Could it be that I really am an idiot?" Seeing this scene, Terri was shocked. She was beginning to wonder if something had gone wrong with her worldview.

Those injuries just now were obviously very serious, right? Obviously, right?

And then she saw that Dahm, who was bordering on life and death just now, was now looking at her condescendingly.

"Alright, that’s the end of our daily training." Garen stood up from beside the last person, Raelan.

"Daily training…??!!!"

In that moment, Terri’s world finally collapsed.

The five of them were acting as though it was nothing, all of them standing obediently in front of Garen, right here and now, they did not have even an ounce of the arrogance and cockiness they had outside. As though they really were regular students being taught.

Just when Terri was on the brink of breaking down, Garen was looking at the progress of the five of them in front of him with some satisfaction.

They were at the same level as Cece and Xander, having entered the second level one after the other.

There was one other benefit of the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist, other than the ability to cut with one’s arms slowly developing, the practitioner’s own body would also have faster agility and reaction speeds, this increase was not limited to activation of the secret skill, it was applied to the changes in their everyday body.

But the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist had a fatal weakness.

Which was that it did not have a strong resistance or defense.

The reason Garen gave the five of them such a daily training, was to increase their resistance to being beaten up like this. It stimulated their bodies to continuously grow stronger muscles and bones, while at the same time increasing their bodies’ regenerative abilities.

Of course, the cost was they needed to use up their life energy, or their life force, and with the little bit of life force they had, under such brutal training, they probably would use up their life after a few times, and age rapidly before they even grew old. But Garen was using his advantage with the Slaughtering Hand, to absorb some life force from animals, so the five of them could completely withstand this level of training.

When they first started, the five of them were shocked out of their wits, but after Garen showed off his special healing later, their injuries actually recovered extremely quickly. And Garen knew where to draw the line, when it looked like their bones were broken, they were actually only dislocated, so they just needed one crack to push them back in place and the wound was completely fine again.

This allowed the five of them to move from their initial terror until they slowly became used to it.

At first normal people would not be so masochistic, taking one beating was one thing, but they surely would not go for a second round. However, they did not expect that after enduring one beating, their speed and pleasure when practicing the Two-Faced Waterbird Technique actually improved. And perhaps it was because there was that pain to act as a stimulus, but the pleasure they felt when training their secret skill had actually become a lot more intense than before.

That was the key reason why the five of them seemed to revel in the pain.

Pain and pleasure, that was their true portrait right now.

After resting for a whole half hour, the five of them stood up one by one, and other than their bodies being a bit dirtier than before, they were not too different from when they started.

They had already undergone this training a lot of times recently, just as Garen said, it really was only one of their daily trainings.

This was the first official training now, so even they did not know what other training methods he had, their hearts somewhat full of anticipation, and of terror.

Garen’s figure loomed in front of them, he was not too much taller than them, but the pressure was as though there was a huge mountain pressing down on them.

"The training after this must be kept secret." Garen turned around to look at Terri.

Terri pointed at herself, looking confused.

"?"

"That means you can go now." Raelan said offhandedly, with some impatience. "Either that, or you join our training as well. You can even join the combat club!"

Terri gulped, picked up her phone, took a deep breath, turned around, and tried to walk away calmly.

But without her knowing it, her legs just seemed to walk faster and faster.

There was some laughter from behind her, it seemed to be Raelan, or it might have been Quentin, those two never saw eye to eye with her, but right now Terri was in no mood to mess around with them, she just wanted to go back and search this up, she wanted to see if something really had gone wrong with her worldview.

After Terri was well and truly out of sight, Garen turned back around, looking at the five of them.

"Looks like you’ve basically grown used to that level just now, now we shall undergo a series of special trainings."

"I want to ask something." Hochman put the glasses he had taken off just now back on.

Chapter 608: Startup 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"What question?" Garen moved his gaze to Hochman, and instantly made him tense up.

Hochman resisted the shuddering feeling in his heart.

"I wanted to ask, do we really need to undergo such high difficulty training? President, you’ve already achieved such a high level, is it still necessary for you to use such high difficulty training on us?"

"Good question." Garen smiled. "I will put this question aside for now, but you will understand it yourselves in due time."

"Alright, pretend I never asked." Hochman lowered his head.

Garen looked around, making sure there was no one else, and the guards were also very dutiful, so he paid them no more attention.

"The training in the second level is mainly a more focused battle-style training. I am the attacker, you need to do whatever you can to deal with me. Of course, you will win once you hit me three times. Any questions?"

"Of course we have questions." This time it was Dahm, "What do you mean by hitting you? Does even a touch count?"

"Guess so." Garen thought about it, and nodded nonchalantly.

"And by three times, you’re referring to the total sum for all five of us, right?" Quentin spoke.

"Of course." Garen spread open his arms, "You can use the secret skill you’ve been training all you want, no matter what you do, as long as you can touch me, hit me three times…"

His body suddenly retreated abruptly, his speed slowly growing faster, faster and faster, faster and faster!

In an instant, his figure had somehow become a flitting shadow, he was moving at a speed much faster than his usual speed.

"From now on, I’ll bring my body’s qualities down to your level, I will just move faster than you do, and all you need to do, is hit me three times before I take you down!"

Garen’s voice came and went, as though it was constantly echoing around them from all directions, so that they had no idea where he was at all.

It was just a small grassy field, and the five of them stared hard with their eyes wide and their mouths hanging open, trying to pin Garen’s location down, but all they could do was see a hint of his shadow.

Even their eyes could not keep up with his shadow!

"Is he f*cking for real??!!" Dahm was completely shocked, "Is this still human? Can someone please tell me we’re shooting a special effects film?"

"No… These aren’t special effects, I’m thinking this is one of the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist’s true essences, he’s moving in our blind spots!" Jamie said in a deep voice, "Do you remember the time the President defeated me?"

The others grew solemn, they had evidently all recalled the day the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist first left a lasting impression on their hearts.

Their eyes could not catch any trace of his movement as well, at first they had thought that this movement method only worked against one person at a time, but to think, this strange step was even effective against multiple people.

"Watch out." Garen’s voice came from the shadows around them.

"The left!!" Jamie roared loudly.

It was their left side, a fair palm peeked out lightly, and tapped Raelan on the back.

Raelan stiffened where she stood, as though electrocuted, and then that palm caressed the right side of Raelan’s neck, as though touching a lover’s skin.

Smack!

With a soft sound, Raelan crumpled to the floor. Her whole body shook intensely, as though she was shivering, and her eyes rolled over into her head, it was like she had instantly gone insane.

Jamie and the others were still too late to intervene, that palm was like a poisonous thorn, darting out and pulling back, all in an instant.

By the time they reached her, it was already completely too late, Raelan lay on the floor, unconscious, her condition unknown.

"Behind Quentin!!" Hochman yelled, and pounced over there, he had leaped up before he had even yelled out. His body seemed to blow up a current with it, pouncing down like an eagle.

Smack.

Softly, there was another light sound.

Quentin had just lifted her leg, trying to turn around and do a side kick. But she was still too late, that palm tapped her waist, and she instantly crumpled to the ground again, her eyes also rolling back, her whole body shaking, her consciousness lost.

Hochman was so close to touching that palm, but unfortunately he was still too late.

They had lost two people in such a short time, the remaining three boys stood together, back to back, forming a triangle, their expressions anxious as they looked around them.

"The opponent is even faster than you, and you’ll fall unconscious as soon as he touches you, so what will you do now?" Garen’s voice came from around them.

Hochman’s Adam’s Apple bobbed up and down.

"He’s going to make a move eventually, we need someone to act as bait, the rest stick close and get ready to move!" He pressed his voice down low, just enough for the two whose backs were pressed against his to hear.

"We can go to the water, that way we’ll see him coming!" Jamie suggested.

"It’s no use, the river is too small." Dahm rejected him.

"As for the bait, I’ll do it!" Dahm took one step forward.

Just then, that palm appeared again. Just like it a shadow, it shot out instantly from behind him, grabbing for the right side of his neck.

"Here he comes! Go!!!"

The other two did not wait for his signal, rushing out rapidly.

Four arms crashed towards the figure behind that palm at the same time.

"It’s over."

The palm did not move to tap Dahm’s back at all, instead it was pulled back instantly, and taking advantage of the moment when all three swung their fists in the same direction, he tapped them all from the side.

"It’s over." Garen’s voice drifted into their ears. And then there was the sound of multiple people collapsing to the ground, all three of them were touched in the neck, crumpling down, their conditions exactly the same as the two girls.

Garen’s figure appeared on the grass behind the three of them, watching the five bodies sprawled over the grass silently.

"This was just the first time, you guys need to properly think about this, pay more attention to exploring the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist’s force paths, different force pathways in different limbs create different effects. Let’s end it here today."

He checked his gloves, they were not damaged, and only then did he slowly walk into the distance, his body soon vanishing into the grassy horizon.

Simulation battles against high-speed opponents, this was absolutely necessary.

There weren’t just humans in this world, the Blood Breed moved extremely fast, and had powerful attacks, as well as resilient lives, as long as they continued growing stronger, it would be a matter of time before they encountered them. Rather than getting ambushed later as a lesson, it was better for them to get used to it with suitable training starting from now.

In this world, the Blood Breed was undeniably close to perfect.

Unlike in the legends from Earth, they were not afraid of sunlight, they just did not like extremely bright surroundings. They moved fast, had terrifying destructive power, and had the natural ability to hypnotize and control humans, plus they had tremendous regenerative power, they would not die as long as their brains and Blood Nuclei were not damaged.

If they had to have a weakness, there would only be one, which was that their defense was not that strong. Of course, this was relative, faced with Garen’s offensive power, the Blood Breed’s and vampires’ defense was extremely weak, when destroyed with a jolt of force, they were no different than a thin sheet of paper.

But to normal people, the Blood Breed’s defense was still much stronger, about the same as a stout man wearing a thick leather coat. If they wore a piece of leather armor or the like outside, they would really be impervious to regular humans.

Garen planned to have these five take on certain missions, he did not work so hard to train a bunch of cannon fodder. Of course he could not let them die so easily.

Training with a high-speed opponent at this level was one thing, they still needed training to get accustomed to hypnotic secret techniques to build their resistance to the Blood Breed’s hypnosis skills.

He had plenty of time to kill anyway, other than some specific places in this world, everywhere else was just like Earth, there was no hint of any unnatural power at all, Garen was waiting for Baldy’s side to come up with something that contained potential points, so for now he was just killing time, and beating up some little kids in his spare time was a decent exercise. Otherwise, if he lived and studied like normal people all day, every day, his bones would start to rust.

Not long after Garen left.

The five people lying on the grass woke up one after the other.

They all looked awkward, the boys holding the tents between their legs, the girls covering the wet parts of their pants.

This was undeniably harming the perfect image they usually kept up.

Only Dahm was completely unfazed, sticking his pole up as he got to his feet.

"That’s too strange…" He murmured, "He just touched my body, and I instantly felt so good I shivered, then I fell to the ground immediately, as though all the strength had left my body, then I came. It really was f*cking weird."

"Same here." Quentin and Raelan exchanged glances, both the girls were feeling awkward, they were not as free-spirited and promiscuous as some girls out there, they were usually very conservative with their bodies, but that feeling just now, was even more intense than masturbating, their bodies felt completely weak.

That hand seemed to have some demonic magic, they never noticed it before, but to think that once Garen took off his glove and just touched them lightly with his palm, it was enough to destroy their defenses.

"We either make sure he doesn’t touch us, or we get over that feeling of pleasure! Otherwise we’ll never be able to overcome this level of training."

Before they knew it, they were all treating their training as the most important goal in their lives.

None of these five were idiots, they were all elites, in fact, one could say that they were the cream of the crop.

They could all see how precious this stuff Garen was teaching them was, this was not a world normal people could reach at all. Money and power, their families had those in bucketfuls, but something like this was not something any family could simply provide, this was their great fortune, and only an idiot would let this chance slip away. So no matter how Garen’s attitude was when he taught them the secret skill, they did not think too deeply into it, perhaps they might pay the price for that, but how much could a student make them pay? Be it money or power, or just beauty, they had a limitless supply of such material riches. As heirs and heiresses political and economic empires, they were not lacking at all in this department.

But it never occurred to them, that the price Garen was asking from them, was never as simple as they imagined.

This training, this stimulation of pleasure, was also a method of attack that Garen had improvised from the Blood Breed, this was how the Blood Breed attacked humans, when their fangs pierced into human skin and veins, they injected a stimulating poison, that made humans feel numb and intense sexual pleasure, by dulling the human’s senses and defenses, it made it harder for the human to notice that their blood was being sucked away, and they would not retaliate even until their blood had been sucked dry. This was the most terrifying aspect of the Blood Breeds.

Garen wanted to use an even more intense stimulus to ensure that these five could withstand such attacks, that way, even if they were careless and got bitten, they would be able to escape at the first opportunity.

Chapter 609: Change 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bam!!

Garen smacked Jamie’s shoulder with his palm, and sent him flying out mercilessly, falling hard onto the grass nearby.

"Too weak."

He shook his head, sweeping his gaze over the five people lying on the floor.

"That’s how much you’ve progressed over the past week?"

The disappointment on his face was plainly evident.

Too scary…

Quentin tried her best to prop up her body, but her legs kept shaking, as though cramped.

That figure in the middle of the arena was like a demon god, completely unbeatable!

They had lost track of how many times they had pounced at him, but the result every time was exactly the same, the agonizing, cramp-like shivers had become an image to represent Garen’s reputation.

Even Dahm, whose nerves were the numbest, lowered his head and refused to look Garen in the eye.

"Do you guys think this is training?" Garen’s voice reached their ears. "Of course, this is indeed training, but I hope that you will come at me with the intention to kill."

"This is just a regular training, is that necessary?" Hochman lay on his back as he asked. The sweat all over his body had drenched his clothes, and his muscles were bulging slightly, he no longer looked as gentlemanly and weak as he did before, only his glasses showed the last traces of his scholarliness.

"We don’t have a choice…" Garen held his hands open, "Because you’re too weak, so weak that I don’t even want to hit you…"

His voice had a matter-of-fact air of complaint, for some reason, the others all had the urge to beat him up.

"You can get slightly stronger like this, I was thinking..."

Garen buttoned the top few buttons on his black shirt.

"Forget it, we’ll call it a day, don’t disturb me unless there’s something important."

"Since you’ve said that." Dahm suddenly said, his voice stopping Garen in his tracks. "Then what about this!!?"

He pulled a black handgun from out of nowhere, aiming it straight at Garen, his voice turning abruptly louder.

Suddenly the other four around them exclaimed softly.

"Dahm, what are you doing!!? Put down the gun!" Quentin barked sternly.

Hochman pushed up his glasses, saying nothing.

In truth, all five of them were already thinking of Garen as their teacher and master, the five of them were also treating each other as siblings in training.

When it came to Dahm’s thoughts, he understood it somewhat, and was not too surprised.

Of the others, Jamie and Raelan were another duo who were closer to each other, the five of them had split into three circles, Jamie and Raelan, Hochman himself and Dahm, and Quentin was actually alone. The three circles actually had Quentin as the belt between them.

Nobody understood Dahm as well as he did…

Hochman looked at Garen with a hint of anticipation and apprehension in his eyes.

"So, what will you do?"

"How will you deal with guns? Guns and cannons are the main themes of this era that you so admire…" Dahm’s face was slightly pale due to the training, but he gave a slight yet vicious grin. "You can’t blame me, you’re the one who said we need to come at you like we want to kill you! That way, something like this counts as well, right?"

Garen suddenly chuckled softly, then he turned around, lifted his chin slightly, and looked at Dahm with an unprecedented gaze of contempt.

"This is getting slightly interesting…"

He pointed his finger at his temple.

"Here, shoot here. Don’t worry, just fire."

His gaze, as though looking at a bug struggling under his feet, instantly triggered Dahm’s fury, the vicious grin on his face immediately turning dark.

"You think I don’t dare to?"

"Do you?" Garen’s lips curved slightly, "Do… you dare?" He said slowly, with pauses between each word.

Bang!!

There was the sound of a gunshot.

At almost exactly the same time, Garen’s figure appeared in front of Dahm, and he kicked Dahm’s stomach hard.

Bleurgh!

Dahm’s eyes rolled back in agony, and he instantly sprayed blood and vomit from his mouth, the gun falling out of his hand and to the ground. His whole body curled up like a shrimp, and he was kicked far and away, plastered onto the wall nearby.

Garen went over and grabbed a fistful of his hair, lifting him up.

"How does that feel like?" He asked with a smile.

"Real… real good…" Dahm forced out a few words weakly, his bloodied mouth still trying desperately to smile.

"Don’t move!" A voice came from behind Garen.

It was Hochman!

He held a sharp knife in his hand, pressing it hard against the back of Garen’s waist.

"We need to come at you with the intent to kill! That’s what you said." Hochman held the knife, but there was a constant sweat on his forehead.

He did not really notice it when he was so far away, but now that he was in close proximity with Garen, he could clearly tell exactly how terrifying the pressure coming from Garen was.

The psychological trauma from these past few days of being beaten up and the terror in the depths of his heart kept pricking his nerves, telling him to get away as soon as he could! Get away from this unbeatable man.

"I won’t lose just like that!" Hochman kept yelling at himself in his heart.

"Hochman?" Garen threw Dahm aside with one hand, turning around, and nonchalantly blocking the sharp knife at his waist. "To be able to attack me from behind soundlessly and tracelessly, you’ve improved."

Although he had lowered his body’s qualities and abilities down to the same level as these people, his own level as King of the Century was not something he could change, this was a state of his heart that had a far deeper understanding of and experience with secret techniques than normal people.

Under these circumstances, the fact that Hochman was able to hide himself and sneak up on Garen, was already a tremendous step forward.

"Stab me." Garen’s left hand moved upwards, pressing his chest, "Stab me here."

He smiled.

"Do you dare?" The same words that he had given Dahm just now, he was giving them to Hochman now.

Whoosh…

An invisible breeze blew in from the distance, blowing past the grass, and turning all the cold sweat on Hochman’s body into an icy chill.

"I’m standing right here." Garen stared at him calmly, "Just stab me. Weaklings have no right to hesitate."

The sharp knife was shaking.

The sweat on Hochman’s body was about to utterly seep through his clothes.

He lowered his head and did not dare to meet Garen’s eyes. He could feel his hand shaking, he was scared.

Ahhhh!!!!!

In that instant, the sharp knife stabbed forth.

Hochman howled madly, the veins on his face bulging, using all the strength in his body to stab Garen.

Bam!

It was completely quiet on the grass.

The five of them stared at Garen’s right hand in a daze, nobody believed that this was real.

The knife, was flicked away and snapped!

Just as Hochman stabbed forth with all of his strength, Garen flicked his fingers, and his gloved right hand touched the knife lightly, the blade snapping on cue.

Everything happened in an instant.

Bam!

A palm smacked Hochman on the right arm, and he somersaulted like an acrobat, flying into the air, and just happened to land beside Dahm, who was nearby.

The two of them were covered in wounds, this time the injuries were not like before when Garen was holding back, these were truly internal injuries.

He did not hold back, the power Garen used was not what he had been using for training.

So the two of them were actually grievously injured.

Their bodies were broken, bones snapped and blood clots everywhere, their organs were hurting intensely. Both of them could not help but bite down hard on their lower lips, so that the pain would not make them cry out.

Garen grinned, glancing at the remaining three, Quentin, Jamie, and Raelan, all three of them did not fully comprehend what was happening as it happened so fast. Right now, they were still staring at Garen blankly.

"Let’s end it here today. But not bad, you have some understanding of it now." He tossed them a few words, and strode away from the field.

This was behind an abandoned garden, the grass that had once been neat was now completely a mess, there were dents and holes in the wall next to them, and the cement was still falling even now.

After Garen left, the few of them did not move for a long time.

A group of medical personnel rushed over, as though used to it, and checked all of their bodies in a familiar manner, collecting data, giving them recovery drinks, and handling their wounds.

"These injuries are very serious!" A doctor checked Hochman’s and Dahm’s bodies, his brow instantly furrowed deep. "Internal bleeding, many shattered bones, unnaturally high blood pressure, accelerated heartbeat… No! Inject some antihypersensitives stat!"

"We have some here!"

"Send them to the main hospital! Now now now!"

A group of people pushed the two of them hastily and left in a hurry.

"This time, President was not holding back…" Quentin fell to the ground, sitting on the grass, and releasing a long breath.

"Doesn’t it feel like Hochman and Dahm are going crazy?" Jamie sat down beside her as well, smiling bitterly. "Especially Hochman, his changes are making me wary, he seems to be becoming more and more like the president, but not quite the same. I don’t know if it’s just me."

"He and Dahm, they’re both getting stronger. It’s not just you." Raelan stood beside them, saying deeply. "I don’t know what the president is planning, by training us like this, but I do know, that Dahm and Hochman might be getting closer to what the president is hoping from us…"

Jamie and Quentin looked at Raelan, the red-haired girl was beginning to leave her hair long, they had not noticed it, but there was a sharp and decisive air about her now, especially between her brows, there was a sense of invasion that made others look away. The feeling of that piercing, arrow-straight gaze was a bit like President Garen’s darkly feminine side, and it began to appear on her face slowly.

Dahm and Hochman used to be their familiar companions, and Raelan as well, but now they were slowly becoming more unfamiliar, that unnamed air of mysterious danger was slowly seeping from their bodies day by day. All this made Quentin and Jamie feel more estranged.

Not just from this world, but from the companions that they used to know so well.

***************

"Faster, faster, faster! Send them to the ambulance! The patient’s heartbeat is not coming down at all!"

"Switch to matandol(1)!! Max concentration!!"

"No… no! It’s no use!"

"Switch again to antherin!!"

"No, the needle can’t go in!" The nurse was about to cry.

Just then.

Hochman opened his eyes abruptly, his eyes seeming to light up with a white light in the dark night.

Smack!

He yanked the oxygen mask off his face, and actually sat up,

While the ring of doctors and nurses around him stared in shock, his gaze had a trace of joy, satisfaction, and violence buried deep within.

"The terror that surpasses death… So this is how it feels like…" He murmured softly, all the powerful muscle on his body shivering and twisting like flowing water, expanding and turning black.

Chapter 610: Change 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"This feeling… It’s amazing…" He closed his eyes, as if he was completely immersed in this indescribable realm.

Whoosh!!

With him as the center point, a gust started to wildly whirl in all directions surrounding him, knocking even the doctors and nurses in the ambulance he to their feets.

Almost at the exact same moment, in the ambulance carrying Dahm, a strong figure silently sat up on the stretcher, ripping out all the needles stuck to his arms.

"This feeling…. Feels way stronger than before…" Dahm’s eyes were glowing with indescribable joy, although his body was covered with ripped muscles, there was still a hint of femininity radiating from him. Raising his arm, he unconsciously remembered his memories of the state he was in during Illusory Spinning White Jade.

"Level 3… Hahahaha… This is level 3! Amazing… Stop the car!"

The doctors and nurses around him were completely stunned as if they were a bunch of small animals standing in front of a ferocious beast.

******

Feeling the two auras slowly building up from afar, his face unconsciously showed a hint of surprise and astonishment.

"Interesting… How interesting…"

Who would have thought that Hochman and Dahm, in this time’s training, would be able to conquer the fear of death and successfully enter the third level of the Illusory Spinning White Jade, which was the turning point.

The Two-Faced Waterbird Fist was only a secret skill adapted from a normal martial art move, infused with the Aura and Qi from the Soul seed.

What surprised Garen the most was that Hochman and Dahm, when entering into Level 3, managed to trigger his Qi from the Soul Seed and Aura hidden in their bodies, using it as a core, forming their own type of Aura-esque creation.

This creation was not as strong as Auras, formless, as if it was purely a boost in the mental state, but still somehow managing to trigger the movement of Qi.

"Not everything will always conform to your own plans, huh?" Garen was standing on the sloped fields outside the abandoned garden, looking at the directions the ambulance left in. That was where the two’s aura was starting to form.

He could feel how the two’s auras were different from each other.

Hochman’s felt like a ferocious lion, with a cold surface restricting the wildness within, ready to burst against any opponent who tries to go against them, ripping them to shreds. It had a forceful nature to it.

Dahm’s was much more suppressed, his aura was like a slithering cobra slithering in the depths of the river, almost similar to a silent, hidden, and venomous needle, ready to poison and kill the enemy at any time.

To Garen, the most interesting thing about this was, the two’s aura seemed to have a sort of natural attraction to each other, through mutual interaction and clashing, allowing them to stand against each other, yet, at the same time, conform with each other..

The two portions of aura originally from Garen was used to trigger the formation of two completely new and distinct auras. This kind of new creation definitely opens up the possibilities of even further fusions.

"Two seeds that were produced individually, yet still able to fuse together… How exciting… When we mix the two together, I wonder what’s going to happen?" Garen grinned as he looked over to the direction of the two auras.

With the support of his primer, the two were starting to make their way towards becoming a Grandmaster of Combat. This had already far exceeded his own expectations.

"Unfortunately, this immense strength lacked a good enough foundation… How unfortunate…" Garen sighed, if the two had more time, energy, and willpower to properly and conventionally train the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist, the results would be even better. However, regrettably, they did not have the opportunity. They were using Garen’s strength as their foundation, so from the start, their strength were destined to be limited by that.

"Let me see if you guys can escape this fate…"

After gazing at the direction of their auras for a brief moment, he turned and walked off the field.

The two primers independently absorbed the two’s Qi and Life Force, maturing into unique and polar opposite seeds. For some reason, Hochman and Dahm’s seeds have a sense of hostility towards each other, they both feel that if they manage to absorb the other’s seeds, they will be able to achieve an unimaginable strength.

This was a natural attraction by the seed, it was intuition.

Maybe they did not know it, but Garen was very clear, as their abilities become stronger, this kind of attraction would increase, If one of the two manages to absorb the other, they will come full circle and attain an almost unrivalled level of perfection. Even Garen didn’t know what that level was, or how strong it would be.

He was only the one who planted the seed, under different conditions, the seeds managed to mature and bear two different and unique fruits, that was outside of his control. This was only his 1st experiment.

He just wanted to see how high can two of the most masculine and elite people can eventually achieve. What kind of result will they bring…

Now, the seed has sprouted, there is no longer a need for his guidance.

******

South Africa

On an empty loess plain.

With wilted bushes scattered scarcely all over, a few zebra were slowly galloping on the plains.

On the ground, right next to a bush,the rays from the twilight sun revealed a man, covered in dirt.

He was lying flat on the ground, one leg covered with blood splatters. From afar, there was the sound of a whimpering wild dog, it sounded almost as if it was a crying child.

"Whew…" The man took a deep breath. He turned to his side looking at the other body at a bush some distance away.

"Bane, you okay?" He licked his cracked lips, but even his saliva was dried up, he had no way of wetting his lips.

"Still alive…" A feeble came from afar. "No more sleeping! We need to leave this place! I had enough of this!"

"Agreed." Using his arms to support his body, he stood up as he surveyed his surroundings. "Hurry up and come over! We need to leave!"

He saw a few zebras speedily galloping away in the distance.

"My leg is broken." Bane shouted. "Call someone for help! Kenna! Use your satellite phone!"

The man tried to reach for his backpack behind him, but then started swearing like a sailor.

"The phone’s gone, so is the bloody backpack!"

"F*cking Levi!!" Bane cursed out loud.

The two moved towards each other.

Although one of Kenna’s legs could no longer mover, he still limped his way over. The other guy was in an even worse condition, 3 of his limbs have been rendered useless.

"We need to think of something… Levi surely already sent his men to look for us! This is my business, I didn’t want to get you wrapped up in it." Kenna muttered. Sitting down on the ground, he tried helping the other guy up.

"I also didn't want this, but since I’ve got dragged into this predicament I don’t really have a choice. Let’s try to solve the issue at hand for now, our blood would attract the attention of the African Wild Dogs, they are one of the most dangerous predators in Africa! They will eat us alive!"

The wild dog packs will hunt down their prey and devour them in a frenzy. The prey would struggle, looking as their body gets ripped into shreds, not even leaving bones as the dogs feast on them.

"I’ve already spread news about the Stone Clock of Fortune, the men in black must be scrambling all over right now, there’s no way I’m going to let Levi get the Stone Clock of Fortune all to himself." Kenna let out a short cackle.

"He won’t let you off easy, back at the where we found the relic you almost got buried alive. He even has his tens of minions ready to strike at any moment." Bane frowned, this middle-aged man in a white cowboy head was slowly applying some medicine onto his leg.

"Before I came out, I already heard the news, Europe’s Titian, Asia’s Rasta, I even went to the pub that the mercenaries frequent to gather some intel, hehehe…"

"You talking about the NIghthawks? If they’re gonna take action, this is gonna be fun, hahaha… cough cough!!" Bane laughed a bit, but due to the dryness in his throat he ended up coughing.

"What I’d do just to see Levi’s expression when he hears about this, hahahaha…" Kenna laughed out loud.

Howl!!

The laughter suddenly stopped.

"I think we need to focus on this task at hand for now…"

******

"Garen Thomas, your parcel."

At the post office, a black courier handed a palm-sized box to Garen.

In a crowd of students, Garen took the box and proceeded to check it. The courier then took a picture of it, before he left.

Tearing of the receipt on the box, Garen opened the box, taking out a smaller box made of a black-colored metal.

Opening it, in the middle of the black packing foam, lies a small white fragment of something, with somewhat visible signs of wear and tear on it.

This piece looks like it’s been made quite some time ago, it was broke into a triangular shape, and was only the size of half of his palm.

Taking it out, Garen walked towards the bench at the side of the field and sat down. He took a closer look at the fragment.

"This looks like the fragment of some porcelain chinaware."

Inside the box was also a folded note, he took it out and opened it.

‘Commander, I’m sorry, this is all we could afford to get from the auction, there were too many competing bidders from other antique collectors organisations, please check to see if it is up to your standards.’

It was the handwriting of the baldy.

Garen smiled as he continued on observing the fragment.

He knew this was the fragment of the Stone Clock of Fortune or something that the baldy said he found.

Closing his eyes and closely feeling the fragment, it contained a small hint of an unknown aura.

"There seems to be some effect?" He let go of all his self-control and unleashed his senses.

Whoosh… The shape of the fragment instantly got imprinted in his senses. Even without using his sight, he managed to reverse engineer the fragment from scratch in his mind.

Bzzt!

In an instant, something similar to a white spark flashed on the fragment. Garen’s eyes sparkled.

"There is! Maybe because this fragment was so small, there isn't much potential aura left in it… Using this as a basis for hypothesis, the real Stone Clock of Fortune, although wouldn’t contain a lot, it would definitely still have potential value."

Taking out his phone, he hastily sent a text to baldy.

Almost immediately, he got a reply.

"Understood. Then, please wait for our good news, sir." Baldy obviously understood what he meant.

Chapter 611: Fate 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Keeping his phone, Garen held on to the fragment tightly as he put it into his pocket. In a distance there was a red building that looked like a research lab, there was almost no people around that area.

Walking through the field, the building looked like 3 rectangular wooden blocks stacked together, Garen walked in from the left entrance, entering a rustic-looking corridor.

On the walls were circular stone windows, sunlight was sieving through the layers of leaves outside, shining onto the corridor. A few students were sitting by the window panes reading or studying something.

Garen slowly strolled through the corridor, walking through the sunshine, feeling the changes in temperature as he walked in and out of the sunlight shining through the windows.

"I wonder how long will this kind of lifestyle last…"

He walked up to one of the circular windows and sat down, the window was almost 2 metres tall, from the inside it looked gray, but under the bright sunlight, it was splashed in a warm beige color.

He looked at the clock, it was almost 10 in the morning.

His life has once again back in peace.

Everything with Baldy, with the Combat Club, with Blood Breeds and Witches, were all momentarily tossed away from his mind.

Sitting with one of his legs raised up, he leaned on the window pane, basking in the sunlight. The warmth of the sunlight was caressing his body, giving him the urge to laze around.

"It’s been such a long time since I had a good night’s sleep." A girl said out loud from somewhere behind of him, she had a thick Dorian accent.

"Then why don’t you just sleep a bit more?" Another girl laughed.

"I don’t have a choice, if only I had the time, I would even sleep till the next night if I could!"

The two left the corridor while cheerfully bantering.

Garen did not look over, he just silently listened to the conversation.

"How long has it been since I had a good night’s sleep?" Garen asked himself.

He had been training his Slaughtering Hand since he was young, this was a demonic technique from one of Ancient Ender’s 42 Demon Kings that bestowed upon him a mysterious power, but it also made him unable to have a good sleep for all these years. Even back when he was in the totem world, he still had a somewhat regular sleep cycle, but now, it seems that it’s impossible.

He was spacing out at the window pane for almost 2 hours, only snapping out of it when he was awakened by the sounds of people exiting the building.

His phone suddenly beeped, he had received a text message. He whipped his phone out.

It was by Messi.

"Wanna have lunch? We’re planning to have a group lunch with the babes from the girl’s dorm, we’re gonna drive out and have a picnic, how about it, wanna come?"

"You guys enjoy yourself, I feel like going back to the dorm to have some rest." Garen answered directly after thinking for a brief moment.

He already attained Level 3 of the Slaughtering Hand for quite some time, but it seems like the progress hasn’t increased since then, in fact there seems to be no signs of progression at all.

"Rest?"

"Yeah, I’m feeling a bit tired."

"Alright, then I’ll be heading off."

"Enjoy yourselves."

Garen put down his phone and looked to the distance. Across the field, there was a teapot-shaped red building, with students walking around, mostly walking towards the canteen or out of the school grounds.

A peaceful life, without any extraordinary powers, surrounded by nothing but normalcy, he enjoyed this kind of life quite a bit.

Buying a sandwich and a juicebox, he had a simple lunch. Garen then went back to his dorm. Since it was the weekend, the dorm was quite empty, with barely a few people in sight.

On a bench beside the entrance, there was a guy in a white T shirt and a pair of jeans, he had a guitar on his lap, silently playing it.

The music was clear and moving, he was completely concentrating on his music, completely ignoring Garen and the few people gathering around him. After listening for a bit, everyone could feel that their feelings have become more calm and tranquil.

Having nothing to do, Garen lazily walked upstairs, he could hear the sizzling of a guy frying eggs in the communal pantry, the was also a scent of its fragrant aroma slowly radiating from the pantry.

Using his key to open his unit door, he walked in. It was empty as he had expected, closing the door, he walked to his own room and grabbed his violin case, walking to the balcony.

From the violin case he took out his violin, carefully applying rosin on the bow then tightening it. After placing a shoulder rest on the violin, he moved the violin to his shoulder and rested his chin on the chinrest.

Zing...

A short and crisp note could be heard.

Slowly turning the pegs, he tuned the strings one after the other, and finally doing some fine tuning when he was done. It was better to loosen the strings slightly when it’s not in use, only tightening it when you’re going to play.

"What should I play?" He was thinking back to all the songs he knows how to play. Suddenly, he felt some inspiration and started playing.

In an instant, the melody of "Walking in the Rain" started flowing out of the violin.

The music was elegant and clear, with perfect dynamic expression and timbre, almost like a stream calmly flowing through the mountains, continuously flowing with no end.

Ting!

Out of the blue, a piano was being played from somewhere else in the dorm, creating a sort of harmony, softly latching on the the violin’s rhythm.

Garen closed his eyes, the violin on his shoulder almost seemed like it was crying, as his bow swiftly moved, he unconsciously yet naturally unleashed some of his strengths.

His music started to sound more mysterious, devilish even, affecting even the piano. The piano’s melody started to lose his own style, becoming the pure accompaniment of the violin.

Garen snapped out of it, suddenly stopping his violin.

He held his violin at rest and looked up at the reflection of the sunlight.

This was a melody with demonic powers…

Death Waltz.

Tang tang tang tang!!!!

The sound of the piano also came to an abrupt stop, leading to a sudden silence.

Soon, a commotion could be heard from afar, the school infirmary ambulance sirens could be heard getting closer.

Garen walked up to a window, looking down at a long-haired girl being stretchered off into the ambulance.

The sunlight was shining on his face, revealing his complicated expression.

This was the reason he started playing the violin less and less. It was as if his hands had some sort of demonic power, anyone who gets engulfed in the music he played would go through intense suffering and pain.

Garen held up his violin, staring at it, when suddenly, at the center of the backboard he could almost see a red eye.

It was a fierce demonic eye, completely white, yet covered in blood capillaries.

It was his eye…

"So even this violin has been infected by me?" Garen helplessly caressed his violin.

This violin was a present from his mother of this world, it was priceless and even said to be the one used by the great musician Richard Wagner.

Now, this exact same violin has been infected by the aura from his demonic techniques.

"The 42 Demon Kinds huh… They’re so hard to master." Garen muttered as he kept his violin.

Lying on the reclining chair at the balcony, basking in the golden sunlight, he felt warm.

There was a warm breeze on his face, Garen opened his eyes, noticing that he fell asleep on the balcony for quite some time.

He stood up and walked to the sink at the balcony, splashing some water on his face.

The water was warm, with no cooling feeling.

He raised his head to look at the mirror.

"Hey brother, you said you’ll bring me to play."

A charming voice could be heard from the living room.

"Where’s Papa? Mama’s not here, didn’t you promise that you’d bring me out to play?"

It was a small girl’s voice, it sounded very familiar, but Garen couldn’t quite remember who it belonged to.

He wanted to turn his head, but for some reason, at this moment, he couldn’t even execute such a simple action. His neck was as stiff as a statue, nable to be moved.

He used his limited vision to look over at the living room with the corner of his eyes, there was a black shadow over in the living room. The shadow was slowly moving towards him, coming nearer and nearer.

"Brother, you promised to bring me out to play."

"Papa is not here, Mama is also not here. Brother, you promised to bring me out to play…"

The girl’s voice came from the shadow.

Garen felt that the shadow was approaching him even more, getting closer and closer. An indescribable fear of the unknown started to gush into him.

He could feel the shadow’s closing presence, but he wasn’t able to turn his head to look, only seeing it in the corner of his eye.

He felt that the shadow was right behind him, the voice was right behind him. His skin started getting goosebumps, almost as if it was hit by a sudden chill.

"Brother, you promised to bring me out to play…"

Garen didn’t understand why he was scared, he could feel it, something getting closer and closer to him. He didn’t know what it was.

"Garen… Garen…"

It seemed like someone was calling out his name.

"Garen… Wake up, Garen!"

He was right, someone was definitely calling his name.

"Brother, you promised to bring me out to play…" The black shadow was right beside him, surrounding him, he could feel something getting closer and closer to him.

"Garen! Wake up!"

Garen forcefully opened his eyes, he saw a white Caucasian face right in front of him, with a pimple on his nose, brown eyebrows and short hair.

"Messi…"

He noticed that he was still sleeping on the chair, lying alone on the chair, with his head tilted off to one side.

"I fell asleep?"

"Of course." Messi was in a somewhat formal black tuxedo. "I’ve just returned from a dinner event and I see you sleeping out on the balcony."

"Really?" Garen stood up and rubbed his face a bit.

That was a dream just now…

"What’s up with you? Had a nightmare? Want me to call a chick over to comfort you?" Messi grinned while blinking at him.

"Screw off, I’m fine." Garen jokingly said, he felt that his face had a weird sense of numbness, he didn’t know why.

"Well, you take care now, to be honest, you look terrible." Messi said with a concerned look.

"Really?" Garen was surprised, he stood up once more and walked to the mirror, looking at his appearance.

A pale white face entered his vision.

"You should really get some R&R. I’ll be using the bath if you need me." Messi shook his head, Garen looked a bit off today. Well everyone has their own issues and privacy, it’s better not to dig to deep in other people’s business.

"I’m fine." Garen used his secret technique, manipulated his blood and qi, returning the colour to his face by hastening his blood circulation.

Listening to Messi’s footsteps as he walked away, Garen opened the tap and used some water to wash his face. He felt much more awake, the water was cool, gushing out of the tap.

He grabbed a towel and wiped his face and looked down from the window. On the field, there were various couples sitting under the street lamps.

A white car slowly approached the dorm, it was driven by a girl in a white shirt, who was waving happily at the guy who was coming out of the car.

Chapter 612: Fate 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The black clocktower in the distance looked like a gigantic upright pencil, with only a faint light flickering on the tip.

The orange-yellowish light of a plane slowly gliding through the night sky could be seen.

Through the open window, a gentle breeze blew, bringing a cooling sensation, along with the fresh scent of grass. There was also a hint of perfume from somewhere in the distance.

The chirping of the crickets plagued the night, along with the occasional calls of birds. A faint semblance of singing could also be heard from afar, gentle and harmonious. It was almost like a chant of some sorts, and it was all the voices of children.

Garen now felt more clear-headed than ever.

Thinking back to the dream he had just now, his mind was completely hazy.

He couldn't remember the last time he'd felt this type of fear. Was it 10 years? 20 years? Or even 50 or 60 years?

That feeling came almost naturally and he had no control over it, almost as if it was his body's reflex action. He definitely didn't encounter anything he could have feared recently.

"What a strange dream." He used a wet towel to wipe his face as he slightly shook his head.

Taking a deep breath, Garen hung up the towel, grabbed his violin, and returned to his bedroom. He glanced over at his laptop, but he had no intention of turning it on.

Without even turning on the lights, he sat at the edge of his bed.

Checking the condition of his body, as he found nothing out of the ordinary, he had no choice but to disregard it as something unimportant and pushed it to the back of his mind.

In the upcoming days, he would only head for class, train his secret technique - Slaughtering Hand, observe Cece's development, and train his 5 vice presidents.

The progress of the 5 vice presidents was extremely impressive, especially the 2 - Hochman and Dahm.

The two have started showing signs of becoming top-tier martial artists, one domineering, the other suppressed. The two have also developed their own fighting style and ideals as martial artists.

******

A few months later.

Bam bam!!

4 arms were interlocked with one another; Hochman and Dahm were furiously grappling with each other. Their feet pounded loudly on the ground, even causing the dense spiderwebs to shake.

Garen was clad in a white gi, silently observing the sparring from the sidelines.

Hochman sacrificed his defense for more offensive power, putting immense power behind every hit. His body was getting stronger every day and he had his hair trimmed into a buzzcut. When he removed his glasses he looked even fiercer, emitting the aura of a lion. Every attack was infused with fearful killing intent and aura as if he wouldn't back off before utterly destroying his opponent!

On the other hand, Dahm focused on defense more than offense; he would stall for time as he waited for opportunities to strike. Every strike of his was deadly, they were definitely loaded with the intent to damage Hochman.

This was not sparring, it was pure combat!!

Jamie, Quentin, and even Raelan were looking on from the sides, completely terrified, occasionally glancing over at Garen. The president seemed to have no issue with it, it even seemed like he had a look of satisfaction on his face.

They could only hope that Garen could stop the fight in time before any major damage had been done.

In the empty gymnasium, multiple bodyguards of the five vice presidents surrounded them. They'd bought the entire gymnasium over as their personal training facility.

At the middle of the gymnasium, Hochman and Dahm's blows were creating shockwaves through the Gymnasium, pushing back even Garen, Jamie and company who were watching on the sidelines.

Bam!

Hochman swung his right fist, causing his entire body to whip around. His attack was as like a cannon firing, landing a devastating blow on Dahm's left arm.

With that blow, Dahm flew back through the air, spinning to a distance away.

"Die!!"

With a roar, Hochman lunged forward, putting all his body's strength into his elbow.

Crash!

A hole was created on the thick wooden floor.

Dahm dodged away just in time, but the right side of his forehead had been split open with a small trickle of blood. Yet, his cold gaze was still fixed on Hochman.

"Hehe…" He suddenly let out a cold cackle, his 2 index fingers tapping lightly on his chest.

"Spinning Moon…"

Suddenly, with a flash, he vanished without a trail.

"Up there!" Quentin loudly shouted.

The other two followed suit and looked up, just as Dahm leaped down, not making a sound. Both his index fingers aiming for Hochman right at his eyes. His fingers looked like it was wrapped with a layer of white air in the form of sharp claws, looking extremely mysterious.

"A Level 3 Ultimate Spinning Technique? Don't think only you have such a skill…" Hochman laughed. He raised his right arm, suddenly his muscles started expanding, becoming darker and larger, covered with numerous black and blue veins.

"Dragon Spin!!"

Bam!

White gas billowed out of his arm, and almost as he was propelled by a cannon, Hochman catapulted towards Dahm who was flying right at him.

Roar!!

It was as if a ferocious beast's roar was ringing through the air, from an unknown beast of the same ferocity as an enraged lion.

"Enough!"

With a loud shout, Garen appeared between the two.

The two shockwaves were immediately negated as Garen caught both of their arms at the same time, separating the two from each other.

The facial muscles of Hochman almost seemed to start concentrating on his brow, forming a ferocious frown.

His right arm was being held by Garen's single hand. Although Garen's arm looked normal and a lot thinner than his, with just one grab, Garen managed to negate all of his arm's strength.

Hochman's skin on his entire body started to flush red, ever slowly turning darker. His body felt like it was boiling, the white air radiating from his body was his sweat being instantly evaporated from his body.

On the other hand, Dahm's two fingers were held tightly in Garen's hands while he stood firmly on the ground. The killing intent in his eyes suddenly got suppressed, his facial expression returning to his gentle smile. Although he was a burly man covered in muscles, at this moment he had a gentle feminine smile, giving people around him goosebumps.

"Well since master insists, let's end it here for today, I have some stuff I need to do, so I'll take my leave." He took back his hand, narcissistically rubbing his own fingers.

"What a heartless guy, I can't believe we used to have such a close friendship."

Hochman pulled back his arm as well, his facial muscles returning back to usual.

Behind them, the bodyguards of the two started helping them wipe off their sweat and treating their wounds.

"I also have some stuff to do, so I'll be heading off as well," Hochman said as he put on a black windbreaker handed to him by one of the bodyguards.

The gymnasium door was opened by the guards, revealing a snowy weather.

"Master, I'll be taking my leave then."

Garen nodded. Ever since he'd initiated the primer, the duo's potential had increased rapidly, far exceeding the other three who were training together with them. They were infinitely better than Cece and Kaedun, whom Garen had placed high expectations on in the beginning.

At this point, the duo had created their own styles of combat methods, and even after participating in Garen's training, they'd hired top-tier experts to help further hone their skills.

Hochman had even fought Polar Bears and African Lions with his bare hands.

Dahm on the other hand, there were rumors of him often going into primitive tropical forests, sometimes losing contact with the world for tens of days, or even more than a month, then suddenly reappearing while dragging crocodile corpses, scaring his family.

Both of them also set up their own Black Organizations, and the entire Nottingham underworld was dominated by their two factions, their power spreading to even other nearby states within a short period of time.

Ever since Garen noticed that they managed to initiate the primer and create a seed, he'd stopped forcefully controlling them, most of the time only meeting them to teach them new skills. To be honest, at this point, they don't even need that anymore, most of the time, because of the power of the seed, Hochman and Dahm would engage in lethal combat.

They both felt that, if they manage to kill the other, it would let them attain a whole new level of strength. That sheer power would make them invincible!

As they train more in the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist, reaching the highest levels, the more they truly understood how absurdly powerful this secret skill was.

They had extreme levels of energy and as a result, they could support faster and clearer brain functions. Originally already elites, this allowed them to get even better results and more respect as people of higher importance within the family.

They haven't even graduated, yet they were already slowly taking charge of their households' internal affairs.

Walking out of the training facility, Hochman raised his head looking at the snowy scenery.

"Dahm… Hmmph."

His ten bodyguards followed silently behind him.

The row of people walked through the snow-covered grounds and entered a few black cars, the motorcade slowly leaving via the road.

After a while, Dahm walked past in a red windbreaker and a fluffy white and brown scarf wrapped around his neck.

His hands were casually placed in the pockets of the windbreaker as he was being surrounded by the same men in black. The only difference with Hochman was that his men had a red armband on their right arm. In the sea of these tall men, all standing at almost 2 meters tall, he was standing out even more in the middle, with his short stature.

Reaching his hand out, one of the men immediately handed him a custom-made lipstick.

Applying the lipstick naturally, Dahm took out a small cosmetic mirror to check his appearance. After making sure that he looked perfect, he kept the mirror with a satisfied look.

"Hochman left in such a rush, I wonder why? Did something happen to that little apple of his?" Dahm placed his finger on under his chin, making a thinking pose.

"Maybe there has been some problems with his business." A man in glasses suggested to him.

"Oh? Then what about that little apple he cares so much about? His dear cousin?" Dahm raised his eyebrow.

"It seems like she fell in love with a guy outside, a North European."

Dahm nodded, revealing a bright smile.

"Do you think I should add some spice? It sounds like it'll be fun~~~"

"In my humble opinion as your servant, now is the best time to strike at Hochman. Hochman loves his cousin, but this type of love is too overbearing and selfish, he doesn't let her go out for activities, not even for work. All she was allowed to do was to wait patiently at home for him, this kind of life is naturally miserable and suffering. It is only natural for her to want to get out."

The man in glasses replied gloomily, as he adjusted his glasses.

Chapter 613: Battle for the Treasure 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Great point." Dahm smiled, "What a poor child… Let's create an opportunity for her then. If we could lure out Hochman that would be even better."

"As expected of Marshall Dahm! Your plans never fail to amaze this humble servant!" The bespectacled man praised.

"Recently the Primary Colours sent a representative on wanting to merge with our family. Since there's nothing much happening these days, why don't you follow me for the meeting?" Dahm nodded.

"Thank you, Marshall!" The bespectacled man burst out in joy, not trying to hide his happiness at all.

A row of people, similarly, walked towards a white motorcade, almost indistinguishable from the from the snow-covered ground. The motorcade slowly drove off into the distance.

At the entrance to the gymnasium, Garen stood with his hands behind his back, gazing at the leaving motorcade, his face unconsciously letting out a satisfied smile.

"Master…" Raelan said with a concerned look on his face.

After all this time training under his wing, they noticed that despite his appearance, his mental age has far exceeded them. With all his teachings to them, the five had unconsciously started calling him "master" as a sign of respect.

"Don't worry." Garen raised his hand, motioning for her to stop.

"This is their fate. I cannot stop them, and they know they can't as well."

"Fate? We're only average students, how can this kind of thing exist?" Raelan looked at Garen's back, she had never truly understood this man he called her master.

"Average?" Garen smiled, "Do you really think that those two are ‘average'?"

Raelan opened her mouth to argue, but she reluctantly lowered her head.

Up till now, she was still stuck in the 2nd level - White, and no matter what she did, she could not progress towards the 3rd level - Spin, whereas the two have already achieved the final form of the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist, with the 4th level - Illusion.

This kind of difference was comparable to Heaven and Earth, and with just a flick of a finger, they could easily kill the three of them.

Quentin and Jamie were in the same boat as well, not able to exceed Level 2. Although their bodies had attained a certain degree of strengthening after training in the Secret Techniques, it was underwhelmingly little as compared to Hochman and Dahm.

"Master…" Quentin walked up to him, looking at Garen, "What is your goal for all of this?"

They all had a copy of Garen's information and notes which he'd prepared, which were intricately detailed yet extremely simple. However, when comparing what's written in the notes and what she saw, the difference was unreal.

Was there truly geniuses who were just born talented in this world?

"Goal?" Garen turned around, looking at the three. "All of you are my pupils, but all of you are from different types of soil, you would bloom into different types of flowers and bear different tasting fruits. This is not my goal, I am but a teacher, an observer. Everything is left up to fate."

"Fate?"

"Hehehe…" Garen didn't say another word. He slowly walked out of the training facility, disappearing into the snow.

Quentin and the others looked on as he left, no longer saying anything.

They had a gut feeling, that the clashes between Hochman and Dahm would become more and more intense.

The two's strengths have already far exceeded their imagination, it was unlike Garen's inscrutable and unapproachable strength.

Hochman had a type of sheer ferocity and force! Anyone who stood in his way needed to be annihilated! He started to treat even Garen with less respect.

On the other hand, Dahm looked gentle and polite on the surface, yet his body was emitting a chilling vibe whenever they look at him.

After a long while…

"I asked Hochman the other day," Jamie said as he leaned on the wall. "I asked him, what happened between you and Dahm?"

"What did he say?" Raelan looked over to Jamie. Quentin also walked up beside him.

"He told me to ask Master."

"So it was Master's doing after all!!" Raelan tightened his fists.

"Though Hochman said that he does not regret a thing. Master allowed them to become stronger and stronger, even achieving greater heights of the future." Jamie sighed, his breath visible in the frosty climate.

"Yeah… They have become stronger and stronger." Quentin nodded, you could see a hint of jealousy in her eyes. They were all training under Garen's guidance, what made them so much stronger than the others, whilst she was still stuck at her level?

"When I was talking to Hochman, he told me a statement that I couldn't wrap my head around." Jamie continued.

"What statement?"

"He said, ‘This world is far more complicated than you imagine.'"

"What does he know, and what has he experienced?"

"Who knows?" Jamie's said expressionlessly, "He's become like a stranger to me."

******

"The seeds have already sprouted…" Garen was watering the potted plants in his room.

Drops of water were flowing out of the white watering can, splashing onto the leaves and dripping into the soil.

Hochman and Dahm's bad attitude towards him was no longer important. What's important was that their clashes have reached the point where they could no longer hold back.

To Hochman, those who submit to his will would prosper and those who resist would fall. In the areas under his rule, even the government servants had no choice but to submit to him. His family has widespread influence, and along with his monstrous physical strength, they'd become an influential superpower in the area.

On the other hand, Dahm used Nottingham as a base of operations, controlling the other areas through his family's influence and connections. Almost like a giant snake hiding in the depths of the sea, ready to kill at any moment.

"They've probably already noticed that I was the one who planted the primer in the first place…" Garen laughed. "But so what? The power created from the primers merging is not fake, it is an actual strength that one can feel. The two of them should understand that the most."

He felt that he could probably leave this circle at this point as Hochman and Dahm no longer needed to be under his manipulation.

Beep beep… Beep beep…

A clear notification tone rang.

Garen looked at the sunlight shining through the balcony for a brief moment, then walked into his room and grabbed his phone located on his bed.

******

South Africa

Smash!

A beautiful oriental porcelain vase was shattered on the ground, fragments flying all over the place.

Huff! Huff! Huff…

The baldy had one of his eyes bandaged up, his facial expression was twisted to the extreme.

"Trash! Bloody trash!" he wheezed in the ward. The doctors and nurses were at the door, too scared to even go in.

In the pure white ward, the group of men and women clad in black stood with indifferent expressions. The atmosphere of the entire room was gloomy, everyone inside was radiating a chilling vibe.

"That was a trap…" A younger girl said softly.

"Yeah… It was a trap." The baldy nodded.

Bam!

He angrily kicked at the metal table in front of him, knocking it to the ground.

"That Black Uniform, Levi." He roared in a low voice, "That sly, disgusting piece of shit! How did he manage to reduce the numbers of my, the African Hawk's men down by four?"

With two smacks, the doctors and nurses outside the ward were knocked unconscious and were dragged away, preventing them from hearing the confidential conversation.

The ward was completely silent.

"That pest that I could've killed with one strike! How dare he! How dare he!" Baldy was thinking back to what happened before, getting even more furious.

"Leader, I don't think that's the most important issue right now, Levi had a lot of schemes prepared, we were careless this time and fell into his trap. Under normal circumstances, we would have easily defeated him." A short-haired man with a beard said.

"No…" Baldy took a deep breath, "This is no longer about getting revenge. It's too late… It's already too late. The mission has failed. The Stone Clock of Fortune has been sold by Levito and the Vincent Organisation. Our mission has failed."

He paused, "I just sent a text to the boss."

Suddenly, the expressions of everyone in the room changed, their faces turning white and losing their calmness and indifference.

"You're crazy! We haven't failed! No! We still have a chance! We can still take back the Stone Clock of Fortune!" The young girl frantically shouted.

"No…" Baldy shook his head, "This issue is out of our hands, if we hide this loss from the boss, he'll definitely kill me."

"Damn it!" The bearded man furiously punched the wall behind him.

Thinking of the mysterious and torturous punishments of the boss, he couldn't help but tremble in fear.

******

Garen picked up his phone and looked at the text message, his expression instantly changed.

"Failed? The Nighthawks lost 4 men?"

Garen put down his phone, his eyes glowing in anger.

He immediately called Baldy.

The call went through in an instant.

"Boss…" Baldy now longer called him Commander, Baldy would only call him that in extremely formal situations.

"I'm coming over personally."

After saying this, Garen immediately hung up and turned off his phone.

Originally Garen didn't care much about the Stone Clock of Fortune, it wasn't important to him, the number of potential points it contained was too low. It was something that he did not need, but having it was better than not having it, that's why he sent the Nighthawks to get it.

Who would've thought the Nighthawks would fail? Even to the point where they suffered casualties. They were elites, all personally trained by him himself.

"Damn… It's been such a long time since I've taken a life." Garen squinted his eyes.

******

The data was sent over from the Baldy, directly to Garen's phone.

He vaguely understood everything that happened over in South Africa.

There were 2 key players.

The boss of the Black Uniform Organisation, Levi, and the archeologist Kenna.

Kenna was an adventurer and an archeologist who was being pursued by the Black Uniform Organisation, which specialized in auctioning antiques because he knew of the whereabouts of the Stone Clock of Fortune. This led to a series of mutual grudges between him and that organization.

The pursuer, Levi, somehow survived being buried alive by the rubble from the tomb collapsing that was caused by Kenna. Due to his grudge against Kenna, and also his greed for the secrets locked within the Stone Clock of Fortune, he decided to start pursuing Kenna. Kenna's sister and cousin have both died at the hands of Levi. Levi also suffered multiple heavy hits from Kenna's traps, with grudges piling up, Levi's goal shifted from the Stone Clock of Fortune to the sole purpose of killing Kenna.

To remove Levi from the picture, Kenna decided to stir the pot, spreading rumors and information about the Stone Clock of Fortune to the public, attracting the attention of other groups and elites.

This was the moment the Nighthawks decided to step in.

Baldy, with his immense strength and powerful henchmen, gave out killing orders on Kenna and Levi, thinking of finishing the two off.

Thus, after destroying various interfering parties, they fell into a trap. With Levi's scheming, he managed to get the other interfering parties to cooperate, defeating the Nighthawks.

Chapter 614: Battle for the Treasure 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In a custom suite in a South African hotel.

"Idiot!!" Garen furiously slapped the Baldy across the face.

Baldy's body flew across the room, crashing through numerous tables and chairs in the process. With his body still half-lying down on the floor, he didn't dare to stand up. Neither did he dare to wipe off the blood dripping down from his head.

"Thinking you had enough strength to fight everyone at once, it's because of your arrogance and pride that caused this small issue to spiral into so much trouble!" Garen said coldly.

The Baldy looked down, not daring to make a sound.

The remaining members of the Nighthawk were all petrified, the room was completely silent, with the only audible sound being the rapid heartbeats of the people there. All the members were soaked in cold sweat, their muscles twitching every so often, some even started bleeding from biting their lips, yet no one dared to move even a muscle.

"Can't even complete such a simple task, bloody useless fools!" Garen was furious, although he didn't teach too much to this group of elites, no matter what, they were still one of the best groups in the mercenary world, with the addition of the secret skill - Shooting Shadow, they should be considered the elites of the elites. Yet they were still defeated by a bunch of humans with no supernatural abilities whatsoever.

This completely tarnished his pride.

While the punishment had already been given, but there was still the matters at hand to be taken care of.

"Prepare a list of the organizations that participated in the effort of stopping you guys for me."

After saying this, he walked out of the room with his arms crossed.

"This is no longer just about the Stone Clock of Fortune."

Garen moved his fist around, it's been such a long time since he had to take matters into his own hands, he wondered if he was rusty.

He went back to his own hotel room, looking down at Noordia city from his room window.

The numerous red and yellow lights were placed closely, and when linked together it looked like a river of light, outlining the long road. From afar, at the center of the road, there was a huge red circle of light slowly moving forward, it was a large number of cars slowly moving along the roundabout.

Standing in front of the window, Garen gently took off his new custom-made black gloves, revealing an eerily white pair of hands with a perfect complexion.

They were pale white and thin, almost as if they were intricately carved out from Jade. The palms and wrists had no signs of any flaws, to the point where even hair follicles couldn't be seen, it was truly perfection. Under the yellow room light, it looked mesmerizing, as if it had a demonic attraction.

That was the soft glow from his hands.

"Slaughtering hands…" Garen slowly felt the effects of this demonic technique on his body.

He did not resist it, allowing it to merge with him. He'd tried to completely manipulate the demonic technique's innate nature, but the prerequisite for that was to allow it to merge with the wielder. He could feel the changes of his mind and body through the influence of the demonic technique. However, if he wanted, he could reverse the change, though he wasn't against this kind of change.

He noticed that the secret techniques of the Ancient Ender's 43 Demon Kings were the complete opposite of the Living Secret Technique.

We could say that the Living Secret Technique used the practitioner as a base, and would change itself to become more compatible with the practitioner's body and form a completely unique secret technique.

On the other hand, Demonic Secret Techniques would be making the practitioner's body more compatible with the secret technique, slowly adapting the human body to the best possible conditions for the secret technique.

The two were completely opposite but were two of the possible ways secret techniques could evolve.

What was different from normal secret techniques was that normal secret techniques did not have the ability to change. If it wasn't appropriate, there was nothing you could do about it.

Compared to a normal secret technique, a demonic technique had so much more advantages and strengths, with high practicality and a low prerequisite.

As long as it wasn't a body that was extremely incompatible, it could be transformed by the demonic technique, allowing one to successfully train and attain its potential.

However, this kind of potential would lead a person with a weak will to lose their mind, eventually falling under the control of the demonic technique and becoming nothing but a mindless slave, a killing machine.

Hence, although Demonic Techniques were the easiest to attain for beginners, it was the most dangerous secret techniques to learn. The changes in one's will can't be easily changed by other parties, and it has to completely rely on the practitioner's perseverance, only then can one guarantee that they won't lose their way.

This was definitely one of the most dangerous secret techniques.

Garen gave a definition to the Slaughtering Hand in his mind.

When he was merging with the secret technique, he took note of the innate nature of the technique. This type of completely different path was extremely beneficial for its style of martial arts and his development.

"Stone Clock of Fortune, give me a surprise."

Looking down at the night view of the city, he slowly shifted his focus to his secret skills.

******

In another high-class hotel in the same city.

A few young people dressed in office attires were gathered around, playing cards. The table was piled with dollar bills, with more being thrown around from time and time.

Under the warm lighting, a bespectacled man in a grey suit was puffing on a cigarette, exhaling whiffs of smoke into the room.

"What now?" He said in a weird French accent.

"What do you mean?"

"We spent so much effort to damage the Nighthawks, removing one of our biggest rivals, we should at least get some benefit out of this, right? We even suffered countless casualties." The bespectacled guy said with the cigarette still in his mouth.

"Levi from the Black Uniforms isn't here, if you want benefits, go talk to him about it." The office lady in the black skirt sitting across him replied.

"How long have our two groups been waiting here? Has it been 10 days? I think it definitely has. Why has there been no updates?" The black man on the side impatiently said.

"Aren't we just waiting for the updates? What's there to rush? No matter if it's Kenna or Levi, if they want to find out about that secret, they will eventually have to come here. Our men are already stationed everywhere in this area, there's no chance they can escape." The office lady answered.

"As long as Vincent hasn't left, we just need to keep our eyes on him. Levi definitely already gave the stuff to him." The black man said.

Bam!

The room door was suddenly knocked open.

A burly white man walked in.

"I think we have a problem."

He looked at the 4 people in the room.

One of threw his cards on the table and stood up.

"Trouble? We even defeated the strongest group in this area, the Nighthawks, what other trouble would there be?" The black man asked, leaning on the leather chair.

"Unfortunately, it is the Nighthawks." The white man replied softly.

The atmosphere in the room suddenly became chilly, although some of them were still forcing a smile, their eyes show that they were on high alert.

"I just got the latest news, the real boss of the Nighthawks is here." The white man slowly said.

"Real… Boss?" the bespectacled man placed his cards face down on the table. For some unknown reason, the people in the room felt chills down their spine when they heard this statement.

"If I remember correctly, the Nighthawks should be the strongest mercenary group in South Africa, right? Their leader had always been the bald guy, the one they call the African Hawk." The man adjusted his glasses, "Now you're telling me, after all this time, that they had another boss? A boss controlling everything behind the scenes? Will, please tell me you're joking."

His hand pressing on the cards of the table started to turn pale without him even noticing.

Under the cooperation of their mutual groups and Levi's scheming, through multiple sacrifices, they'd finally managed to defeat the Nighthawks, even blinding one of the baldy's eyes.

The Nighthawks lost half of their men, losing a lot of their power, finally coming down from their throne as South Africa's strongest mercenary group. All their enemy and rival groups of the past would definitely take this opportunity to strike them while they're down.

It could be said that at the moment the Nighthawks got defeated, they were at their weakest and while in that state, in the world of mercenaries, it was a death sentence.

But now, a guy just came in and said that the Nighthawks had another leader all along, the real boss, someone who was the mastermind behind them.

"How funny, isn't that right, Casey? The Nighthawks were the strongest mercenary group in Africa, who has the authority to be their boss? This has got to be the joke of the century!"

He did not notice it, but his hands were trembling uncontrollably, his face turning paler and paler, even his voice started to shake.

He started to laugh, trying to lighten the situation.

No one else in the room laughed.

Seeing that he was the only one laughing, he slowly stopped and sat back down.

"I think we're in a lot of trouble…" The office lady said softly.

"We need to first work together to get some information on the guy's background."

"My recon team couldn't get any info on him." The white burly man walked through the door, then turned around and locked it.

"Work together?"

"Yea, work together."

Everyone took out their laptops or their phones, moving swiftly.

However, the bespectacled man kept pressing wrong keys, he felt that his fingers were so slippery he couldn't even type properly, so he looked up at the others. The office lady was acting calmly, but her beads of sweat from her forehead leaked her current feelings.

The black man had a calm look on his face, but his feet was uncontrollably shaking.

"Got it!!" The black man suddenly yelled.

"You got the info?" "Come on, spit it out!"

Everyone immediately started glaring at him.

"N-no… I mean I've got a plan!" The black man softly uttered.

"What plan?"

"Get Vincent and work together! The groups that defeated the Nighthawks wasn't just us. Even if he's a person from ‘that world', he wouldn't dare to take on so many people at once, right?" The black man said.

They all understood, in "that world", those who had power and influence were frequently not your average person. This kind of being wasn't something they can fend against.

"Vincent himself no longer has much power, but rumor has it that there's still a being standing behind him from ‘that world'. A very strong being."

"I found it…" The office lady said, his face showing visible signs of relief.

"It's still fine, the person is not a being from ‘that world'. He's just a martial artist, a normal human."

Whew!

In that instant, the entire room breathed a sigh of relief.

Chapter 615: Tangled 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A few red and yellow hot air balloons floated around in the sky. There were symbols and words that were written on them with certain meanings.

Garen raised his head and glanced over while standing on the street corner. He could not see properly because the sun was too bright and the hot air balloons were too far away, blinding his eyes and making him slightly uncomfortable.

He was wearing a normal long-sleeved white T-shirt and dark black jeans. His muscular frame and golden tassel-like hair constantly attracted the curious gazes of the little black children in his surroundings.

There were white communication lines drawn on some of the dilapidated streets that extended towards him in a straight line. A few dirty cars drove past slowly, before yellow-grey and black colored lines appeared and covered the floor, while heat waves radiated off the illuminated, scorching ground.

When he glanced over at a nearby area, he noticed that this place was filled with tall old buildings. Most of them had faint yellow stains that showed their age on the surface while other areas were obviously damaged.

This place called Caora was neither a bustling African city nor a famous tourist town. Instead, it was only a normal and unexciting little town.

A group of black women who were balancing baskets of fruit on their heads walked past the doors of the little roadside shops. They were clad in their unique long, bright yellow local dresses and wore noisy bone bracelets on their arms while laughing and chatting.

Garen could not understand their language at all, but this was unimportant. He glanced at the sun in the sky before getting down from the train and thinking that it was probably only twelve o'clock in the afternoon now.

The whereabouts of Kenna and the Black Uniform Organization were probably close to this town. Furthermore, the few remaining representatives of the Relic Organization had allied themselves with Vincent, and a mercenary group called Black Knife had invited the Primary Colors local representatives who were still on good terms with the Nighthawks, in hopes that both sides would be able to reconcile in this town.

The mediation could either be real or fake, as this was also an opportunity for them to check out the Nighthawks' hidden powers.

Garen agreed and asked them to come over, as the Nighthawks' members had already been concealed completely. However, he had never made it a habit to hide anything because he had always done everything openly to crush his enemies directly. Hide? Only the weak would do that. As someone who possessed sufficient power, he would only choose to hide if there was a possibility that he would encounter a threat.

As the row of people strolled through leisurely, Garen put on his black sunglasses while his gaze drifted from the roadside advertisement banners to the signboards.

A few black fellows rushed forward and tried to sell him some cigarette lighters and other little knick-knacks.

"Five dollars! Five dollars!" They yelled in fluent English, but it was possible that these were the only words they knew.

Garen glanced at the other people around him. He realized that the sellers would not call out to the other black people, while other outsiders who were obviously tourists would encounter the same situation as him.

He was unfamiliar with this town and did not like it because it was filled with wild animals. Moreover, wild cats and stray dogs would scurry through the streets occasionally while other animals like snakes or colorful birds were carried on people's shoulders.

Garen even saw a leopard with golden patches sitting inside an expensive car when it drove past him.

This place was extremely hot, and most people were clad in short-sleeved clothes and short pants, singlets, or even long skirts that were almost transparent.

When he walked towards the front of the street, Garen quickly stopped in front of a bar. There was a strange arc-shaped green sign that looked like a portrait in front of the bar, which was flashing with colorful red lights even in broad daylight.

The door and doorway were shabby and it seemed as if no one was entering or exiting the place except for a fellow who walked out of the side door with a pail before pouring the water out of it and down the drain.

Garen stood in the doorway of the bar and waited for a few moments. Two black men in white shirts walked out and nodded at him politely before pulling open the main door of the bar at once.

The interior was pitch black, making it impossible for him to see anything, as though it was merely an endless black hole.

Garen glanced at the men before noticing that both of their mouths were wide open and they were exposing their pearly white teeth as if they were smiling.

"Sir, there are people waiting for you inside," said one of the black men softly in English.

Garen smiled faintly before taking long strides into the bar while the door was closed behind him quickly. The inside of the bar was completely dark because all of the doors, windows and other places that allowed light to enter were all covered with black cloth. However, it was still surprisingly cool inside.

Bang!!

Suddenly, unimaginably bright light exploded throughout the entire bar at once. Instantly, the area was neatly illuminated with white light, allowing the whole place to light up.

"Welcome. Welcome, dear Nighthawks Commander." An old man who wore a cowboy hat and large aviator sunglasses walked out. He was clad in denim clothing from head to toe and was the spitting image of an American western cowboy from the movies.

This old man walked out and stretched his hand outwards before pointing towards the left side. He pointed at a group of people who were seated. All of them looked muscular and had tattoos on their arms and necks. Some of them lowered their heads and used pocket knives to clean their fingernails while others raised their legs and held the young black women beside them while getting up to mischief.

The one similarity that all of them shared was the black pocket knife tattoos on their bodies.

"The members of Black Knife." The old man in denim introduced them while smiling happily. "Those are all Vincent and Octagon Pot's people." He pointed at another group of people who were seated on the opposite side of the black people.

It seemed like this group of people came from all walks of life. There were office workers, women who sold vegetables, bakery bosses, lawyers, social-climbers and other kinds of people. There were obviously some differences between them and the people from Black Knife because they had some restrictions and were not as carefree as them.

Regardless of which side they were from, Garen still felt as if they were sizing him up carefully.

"Octagon Pot? Are you referring to the eight largest Relic Organizations in Europe?" he opened his mouth and asked.

"Of course. That's Octagon Pot." However, the old man did not explicitly say which one of the eight sides these group of people belonged to.

"I've never seen how a mediation is conducted. Am I going to see the flow of events while I'm here today?" Garen raised his hand and asked candidly.

"Since everyone has already arrived here, your presence shows your respect towards me and the Primary Colors. Therefore, why don't you just be frank and tell us your wishes openly," said the old man with a smile on his face.

The first thing Garen did after he arrived in South Africa was to use his Secret Techniques to contort his own facial structure and characteristics. Therefore, it was impossible for these people to identify his exact details. At most, they would only be able to use other channels to eliminate his possible identities but would not be able to discover the true powers that were concealed behind him.

"Openly? Didn't I just come here openly? What else do you want me to be open about?" Garen tilted his head and asked.

"We did not have a major clash with the aristocrats," said the Vincent representative loudly after he stood up. "The aristocrats decided to drive us out completely when they entered the picture, and as the weaker side, we could not even resist them properly despite working together."

"The Stone Clock of Fortune is with you?" Garen did not reply but asked him a direct question instead.

"Of course."

"Very good," Garen nodded. "If you want to reconcile, my requests are simple. Firstly, give me the Stone Clock of Fortune. Next, my Nighthawks group will be given eighty percent of the secret treasures. After that, I will just let this incident slide."

Whoosh…

When these words left his mouth, all of the people on site could not sit still suddenly.

"Eighty? Hehe. That depends on whether you're destined to take it…" The people from Black Knife sneered suddenly.

A brawny black man who seemed like their leader stood up while doing tricks with a sharp pocket knife in his hand.

"First of all, those who break the rules need to accept their punishments."

"Hehe. I heard that the Nighthawks sniping field is virtually undefeatable on the African battlefield. Do you think you could let me experience it for a moment?" He walked towards Garen and was clearly slightly taller than him.

"Sniping field?" Garen already knew that the Nighthawks' own special techniques involved forming a ring with faraway sniping techniques. The snipers who were part of this ring could protect each other while killing their surrounding enemies simultaneously. They would also be able to monitor the entire area to a certain degree at the same time to create a powerful sniping technique without any blind spots.

A few street performers who were banging on small drums walked past outside the bar. Their rhythmic drumming noises echoed throughout the area clearly, accompanying the melody of a man's strange singing voice.

Garen glanced around and noticed that everyone's eyes were focused on him as if they were either waiting for him to change his mind or were waiting to see a good show.

Black Knife and Nighthawks had always been two first-rate mercenary groups that had never dealt with each other. Black Knife had already been deeply rooted in South Africa before their first place position had been stolen by the foreign Nighthawks. They were obviously unhappy, and the Nighthawks bore the brunt of their anger by suffering injuries, as Black Knife would definitely take matters into their own hands during rare opportunities like these.

They had initially waited for Garen to show his trump card but had never expected that he would not follow the steps from the start. Since the situation turned out like this, there was nothing left for them to be concerned about.

Garen glanced at the people from Black Knife and noticed that some of them were already beginning to reach for their guns while others unconsciously held more and sharper cutting tools in their hands and glared at him strangely.

"Before we continue, I still have a question that I need all of you to answer," Garen piped up suddenly.

"What question?"

"The people who tried to ambush my Nighthawks previously, are they all here?" A sliver of a smile appeared on the corners of Garen's mouth suddenly.

Shh!!

Instantly, a bloody hole appeared on the forehead of one of the black people on site before he collapsed on the ground.

"Attack!!"

The Black Knife leader lunged at Garen and stretched his arms towards his neck immediately.

Bang bang!!

After the sound of two continuous gunshots, his arms seemed as if they had frozen in midair, and he was lucky that he was able to evade two bullets that came flying from behind Garen.

The black male leader flipped backward before two extra silver handguns appeared in his hands. He shot the gun at Garen thrice, releasing three banging noises.

There were no bullets flying towards him this time.

"Our people have discovered the Nighthawks! Capture him and take him hostage!!" yelled the Black Knife leader loudly.

The bar turned chaotic as everyone rushed to find a bunker. The sofa, bar top, tables, and chairs were all used as bunkers to shield people.

Everyone seemed like insects whose nests had been destroyed. They ran frantically and disappeared in an instant.

A crashing noise rang out when a stray bullet hit a crystal chandelier before the light was extinguished at once.

Garen walked through the bar listlessly. All of them were merely normal people and he had reached the maximum point of boredom. Moreover, he had only agreed to meet them after the others had gathered on their own.

Under the strong influence of the Primary Colors, his opponents had assumed that he would not actually make a move, but never expected that the opposite would be true instead.

The old man in denim from the Primary Colors rolled behind the bar top effortlessly without making any unnecessary noises or movements. He was a sensible person and knew that since the other party refused to respect the Primary Colors, the first thing that he had to do now was to protect himself.

Bang bang bang!!

Faint but sharp gunshot noises echoed throughout the inside of the bar constantly.

Garen walked throughout the bar confidently as if he was completely unconcerned about being hit by a stray bullet. He sat on a chair that was still perfect and poured a clear glass of spirits for himself. He did not care about the bottle and just sniffed it immediately instead before drinking a mouthful.

The gunshot noises quickly became shorter and softer and it soon became obvious that the Nighthawks were being suppressed.

One of the people from Black Knife rolled off the couch immediately and waved his hands.

Bang!!

A gunshot could be heard.

Garen turned his head slightly when the bullet hit a brown alcohol bottle inside the alcohol cabinet behind him before alcohol and glass shards flew everywhere.

When a glass shard flew past Garen, he deflected it easily. The glass shard flew at a speed that was impossible to be seen by human eyes before an airy hissing noise could be heard when it dug into the black man's forehead accurately.

Chapter 616: Tangled 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Before he could even sigh, the black man from Black Knife collapsed on the ground instantly without a single breath.

The people from Black Knife swore at him continuously.

Bang!

Another gunshot could be heard before he realized that two guns were being shot at the same time. Two bullets flew towards both sides of Garen where his hiding places were located, making it completely impossible for him to hide.

Bang bang!!

Another two alcohol bottles exploded behind Garen but no one was able to clearly see how he had evaded them.

"What the hell?!" The expression on the Black Knife leader's face changed slightly as if he had thought of a possible group and quickly nodded towards his accomplices on the right side.

It meant that it was time for their ruthless measures.

A dot of red light lit up immediately.

Crash!!

With Garen as the center of the entire bar, four blindingly red fireballs exploded around him suddenly.

The Black Knife leader flew towards him suddenly while raining down bullets in a frenzy with guns in both of his hands. Garen made complicated and mysterious dodging poses and movements at the same time.

The sound of large groups of manpower could be heard faintly from outside the bar, but no one could tell if they were from Primary Colors or other groups.

"Is there anything fun left?" Garen's voice echoed behind him unexpectedly.

The Black Knife leader was extremely shocked and rolled towards the front. He charged into the sea of flames directly without looking at the two guns that were still at the back of his hands. He leaped upwards instantly and lunged towards the bar's black cloth covered glass windows.

There was a crashing noise before he rolled on the street a few times before getting back up again.

However, he could suddenly feel a slight pain in his chest. He lowered his head and looked there before noticing that a bright red patch of blood had appeared on the white shirt he was wearing.

The blood stain became darker and bigger before spreading throughout the entire area quickly.

"When did this…?" He stretched his eyes open and racked his brains but could not remember when he had been shot. Acute pain and the suffocating feeling when his lungs were completely unable to breathe spread across him quickly. He staggered forward and leaned against the pillar of the streetlight while his vision began to darken quickly.

When he finally collapsed, he could faintly see Garen carrying a person while walking out of the bar. Meanwhile, the whole bar was engulfed in flames but no one else came out.

The moment Garen walked out, a large crowd of people rushed towards him from all directions. Some of them held knives while others held guns, making the scene somewhat chaotic.

While holding on to the person, he turned back to glance at the bar before his footsteps quickened suddenly, allowing him to appear at the side of the bar instantly. A black child stared at him with a blank look on his face while standing helplessly in the alley.

Garen shouldered the bloodied person and smiled at the child before walking towards the back of the bar.

The large crowd of people outside the alley seemed as if they had not seen him as well, but perhaps they were just turning a blind eye as this occurrence was unbelievably strange.

Once he passed through the alley, Baldy, whose arms were covered in blood, was waiting for him at the back with two other people and two cars.

"Boss," Baldy lowered his head and greeted him respectfully while the other two people lowered their heads as well.

"Take care of this person for a while. This guy is a representative of Vincent. I let the Primary Colors representative escape, so contact him later." Garen flung the person in his arms on the ground.

He was aware that they were people who were noticing and peeping at them from a faraway distance.

"Get in the car and leave this place."

"Boss, what about the people inside…?" Baldy gulped while glancing at the burning bar.

"Aren't they right in front of you?" answered Garen casually.

His intended meanings were obvious. Other than the old man from the Primary Colors, the only other person left was the captured Vincent representative in front of them.

Baldy was somewhat intimidated. The Black Knife mercenary group that was only slightly weaker than themselves could not even withstand a minute under Boss's hands and had all died completely. This meant that…

"Get in the car." He did not think about it anymore and picked up the person before turning around and getting into the sedan.

Both of the white sedans sped up and left the scene from the back of the bar.

On the other side, half of a black man's face could be seen appearing from the entrance of the alley slowly.

The black man's forehead was filled with beads of sweat and he could only hold his breath desperately as he was too afraid to open his mouth and pant.

"Three minutes… And twelve seconds…" he said in an anguished voice.

There were a few more representatives who had not entered the bar at all and had stayed in the alley instead.

A young woman who was dressed like an office lady had turned pale while her hands relaxed and tightened unconsciously.

"It's fortunate that we didn't go in," said a bespectacled man in a deep voice. "We should just inform our respective bosses for now."

The others nodded respectively, as none of them were willing to encounter the golden-haired young man who seemed normal but was not.

That guy was literally taking a brisk walk before he went inside to visit the bar. Moments later, bullets were sent flying and explosions occurred everywhere, but he walked out in perfect condition without any injuries or clothes in disarray.

"What about Levi?"

"The only way to decrypt the answer lies in Kenna's hands, and Levi is still tracking him down," said the young woman softly. "The situation has already exceeded our control. All of the Black Knife members have died. Nighthawks' powers have greatly exceeded our expectations, so I suggest that we inform Vincent's big boss."

"Did you manage to investigate that guy's details previously?" asked someone.

"I only eliminated the actions and whereabouts of the famous people from the surrounding countries. However, if this person appeared suddenly, we can't do anything," the young woman shook her head.

"I'm afraid that it's impossible. He's just a normal person. According to the rules, they cannot interfere with the order of the normal world as they please," said the bespectacled man in a low voice.

"Should the middle section just retreat then?" The black man wiped the sweat from his face. "We don't have to risk our own lives for an imaginary legend. Report the current situation and get our superiors to send more people over to sort this out."

When the other people exchanged glances, they could see the bitterness in his eyes.

They could report all of this to their superiors, but this would mean that everything they had contributed and all of their losses would be wasted and that a demotion would be merely be considered as a light punishment.

"I'm afraid we don't have to do that anymore…" said the office lady suddenly.

"The latest news stated that Kenna and Levi have run into a remote village. An ancient power is entrenched in that village, and the Stone Clock of Fortune seems to have attracted their interest."

"What happened?"

"I don't know. However, it will be a good idea to return. It looks like the secrets of the Stone Clock of Fortune may have finally attracted the attention of certain people."

"I've heard that since Kenna is an ancient scholar, he knows a lot of mysterious people. He may have run to that village because his friends are located there," he said with furrowed eyebrows.

"I think it will be better if we don't interfere. We'll discuss this later once the winners and losers have been decided," the young woman smiled bitterly. "The situation has become more and more complicated, while more powers getting involved."

The other people nodded respectively.

************************

Within a pitch black mess, an old man with a wrinkled face slowly lit a yellow oil lamp before faint yellow light illuminated the interior of the wooden house.

There was a wooden cross on the circular window while slivers of moonlight cascaded inside.

The old man turned his head and glanced at the bed inside the wooden house, where the figure of a black person laid on top.

The figure belonged to a black man who was clad in a black leather jacket that was torn and messy, while his body was covered in wounds and bloody scars especially on his face, causing him to be almost disfigured. However, one could see that he used to be an above average looking, middle-aged man if they looked past the scars.

"Oh…" The man stirred on the bed. "How long have I been asleep, Dahm Rose?"

"Not very long, maybe five hours," answered the old man with a smile when he turned around. His wrinkly face resembled a chrysanthemum flower in full bloom.

"Alright, chrysanthemum… Can I ask why I always think of this plant when I look at you?" The man rubbed his head and smiled bitterly. "Looks like you're not in such good shape either."

"Only slightly better than you." The old man shook his head and picked up the oil lamp before walking to the front of his bed. "I've told you this before, that until the final key moment arrives, don't come looking for me. Not only will there be a possibility that I won't be able to help you, but I may cause greater dangers to befall you as well."

"Of course I remember," smiled the black man bitterly. "But I really had no choice this time, and no other paths to choose." He lowered his head and ran both of his hands through his hair while his eyes were completely bloodshot.

"Looks like you're really in bad shape," the old man shook his head impatiently. "Friend, my own circumstances are not much better than yours, but if you don't mind, you can stay at my place."

"I was hoping that you could give me some inspiration." The man raised his head with a hopeful look in his eyes.

"That's useless," the old man shook his head. "When an extremely powerful force surrounds me, I have no use for inspiration." He looked at the other man and said: "Kenna, you will soon understand that whether your inspirations appear or not, the conclusion cannot be changed."

"Don't tell me that what we see is already the definite ending?" Kenna asked instead.

"It is not definite, but it is certainly the correct deduction from the gathered natural information. You must understand that accidental events don't exist in this world and that the supposed accidents are merely the final conclusions that result from the martial arts certainties that are linked up with one another," said old man Dahm Rose with a wrinkled expression.

"I'm already relying on you since I have no other places to go anyway," said Kenna with a smile even though he had quietened down.

"Is Liv dead?" The old man looked at his eyes but noticed that he was evading his gaze. "Not just Liv, but Corela and Bane as well."

There was nothing but dead silence for a moment.

"Looks like your situation can't get any worse. Just stay with me then," the old man shook his head. "Sometimes, dying peacefully is not such a bad ending."

"What are you saying?" Kenna asked.

"Nothing." Dahm Rose put the oil lamp down and took out a little bottle filled with fireflies. He poured the fireflies into an earthen jar carefully.

Strangely, the fireflies inside the earthen jar flashed but did not know how to fly away and escape.

He took a stone pestle and began to grind the fireflies slowly while some unknown powder scattered out from there occasionally.

"What are you doing?" Kenna noticed his weird actions.

Rose Dahm smiled at him mysteriously but did not reply.

Kenna got up from the bed in a slumped position and picked up a bowl at his bedside that was filled with some sticky yellow substances towards his lips before gulping all of it down in one mouthful.

He did not know how Levi had been pursuing him. Both of them had encountered countless hardships in the wilderness and had fought each other constantly, making it impossible to mediate the hostility between them anymore. One of them was destined to die before this could finally come to a close.

Chapter 617: Tangled 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Although he did not know Levi's current whereabouts, as long as he was by his old friend's side, he would be safe temporarily.

Dahm Rose was an expert in escaping and self-preservation.

Kenna walked to the side of the window and shifted his head to look outside before noticing that it was pitch black, except for a faint light that resembled stars from a faraway row of little houses.

"Where is this?" he turned his head and asked.

"My birthplace," Dahm Rose answered. He continued to grind the fireflies with his full concentration as if it was the most precious treasure. "You were unconscious for a long time and kept bouncing between a dreamlike and awakened state, so I used an ox cart that I borrowed to bring you back here."

"Are we safe right now?" Kenna was slightly worried because Levi was not someone who was easy to get along with. Although most of the Black Uniform members had been defeated by an external power, Levi still possessed unexpected moves and strengths. That person's willpower and physique were simply at a different level.

"Of course it's safe, as long as it's before dawn tomorrow," replied Dahm Rose with his smiling wrinkled face that resembled a chrysanthemum.

"This village is not a normal little village," he said in a low voice. "This place has the tranquility that you desire."

"I don't understand. You're talking about unnatural powers? Here?" Kenna asked instead.

"I was born here, grew up here until I left. You will like this place very soon," said Dahm Rose with hidden profound meaning.

*********************

The next day.

Snap.

An emerald green branch with a few leaves was snapped from a tree. A muscular, short-haired black man with a vicious aura that permeated throughout his whole body held the branch in his hand.

He placed one of the leaves from the branch below his nose and sniffed it carefully.

Shh…

His nose breathed in deeply, releasing hissing noises.

"South… Kenna, you won't be able to escape any longer…" The camouflage combat gear that once covered the black man's entire body had been reduced to a torn mess comprised of a few strips of cloth that hung on his body.

He held a black dagger in his hand and occasionally slashed at the branches and weeds that blocked his path.

This place was the extremely strange interior of a forest and was unlike the vast olive grasslands outside, as this place consisted of a continuous stretch of olive forests that rise and fell.

Crash…

Suddenly, chaotic noises could be heard from a faraway distance behind him.

Someone was shouting loudly in American English.

Levi crouched down carefully, only exposing a pair of eyes while he burrowed himself into the side of his trail under some raised tree roots before turning his head and glancing behind himself.

"Hasn't someone checked this direction already? Why are we back here?"

"Instructions from our superiors, don't be too concerned."

"We're already lacking manpower now. I really don't know what our superiors are thinking."

A few men in olive camouflage gear carried guns and walked over in this direction to search the area.

Levi lowered his head into the undergrowth and concentrated his gaze in their direction.

He noticed that there was a symbol of a black hawk on the sleeves of these men's uniforms.

"Nighthawks…" He recognized this symbol.

Previously, he had gathered the other forces to inflict serious damage on this mercenary group.

"Looks like a lot of new changes have occurred during the period of time when I did not return," he thought when his mind finally understood what had happened.

Bang!!

Suddenly, the sound of a gunshot echoed from a faraway area before a frenzied cry of a wild ox could be heard.

"Shit!! Kill it! Kill it!!" someone shouted loudly.

Bang bang!!

A few more gunshots could be heard.

A few people who were patrolling this area raised their guns frantically. But once they heard the ox shriek, they laughed happily and put their guns down.

"This group of rotten people. It would have been troublesome if they'd attracted the attention of the patrol group or the inspection cars. Couldn't they have been a little more careful?"

One of the black men spat and turned his head in the direction of the gunshot before suddenly noticing that the silence around him was somewhat terrifying.

There were traces of alertness and uncertainty on his smiling face while his hands raised his gun upwards unconsciously.

Kachak!

A large hand flew towards his neck at the speed of lightning before grabbing and twisting it.

The dead body became limp and collapsed backward before it was dragged by someone else and placed on the ground slowly.

Levi spat and took a few things that he needed from the three corpses on the grass such as their guns, water bottles, bug spray, as well as some food and snacks.

He pondered for a moment before picking someone who had a body size that was similar to his own, removing the other man's clothes quickly and donning them.

The corpses lay in the undergrowth that was half as tall as a human within the forest, making it impossible to detect any abnormalities unless one walked extremely near and took a second look.

Levi stuck his nose out and continued his chase in a predetermined direction. He was like a silent cheetah that possessed extremely fast speed and was almost completely quiet.

*****************

Garen stood on top of an olive cross-country vehicle with a pair of binoculars in his hands and looked towards the far away areas. He'd changed into a tight-fitting olive mercenary uniform while a black pistol with a large diameter hung from his waist.

Alongside him were the mercenaries that were especially in charge of driving and Baldy.

There were four similar cross-country vehicles behind the car that were seated to the brim with the Nighthawks' peripheral mercenary soldiers. Some of them were armed with machine guns while others had even brought miniature mortars.

A few of the Nighthawks' elite members had dark expressions on their faces while they checked their own equipment and sniper rifles.

"Carlo, has each group's investigation results been released?" Garen had already replaced Baldy and had taken over the command of the Nighthawks.

He wore a pair of silver-rimmed glasses and a layer of blinking light had appeared on his left eyeglass, showing a little display.

This was the latest research success that included a camera that could take pictures as well as other functions such as sound recording, short-range communication, internet searching abilities and other high-end miniature functions. This was specially made for them, and the Nighthawks referred to it as a Hawkeye.

"It's still alright. Everything is considerably smooth… No… Something has happened." A noise echoed from the earpiece that was connected to his glasses.

Garen raised his hand.

"Mark the location."

All of the twenty people who were spread out between four cars began to check their own weapons while the elite members began to test their communication glasses.

A fat man on one of the cars even raised an air cannon that was usually only used on planes…

There were bombs, anti-tank grenades, air rocket projectiles and heavy mortars among these twenty people. As long as it was a strong weapon that could be handled by a single soldier, it would definitely be there.

As the Nighthawks' were a mercenary group that would go down to the battlefield, excluding the few elite members and the decapitation team, the rest of them formed a group with tremendous firepower. Although their group merely comprised of about twenty people, all of them were senior soldiers who had experiences the flames of war and were already able to penetrate a small-scale city within a short span of time.

In Africa, an army like this would be considered as the cream of the crop.

Behind the four cars was the larger mercenary group that the Nighthawks had gathered. It was a large team of over a hundred people that was known as the Nighthawk Army.

All of them were the Nighthawks' peripheral soldiers. They had truly thrown away all of their animosities this time because the absence of the restrictions from Black Knife and other similar mercenary groups meant that the Nighthawks' could use a large number of their funds to quickly employ these mercenaries that had experienced the battlefield before.

Hoards of mercenaries enthusiastically joined the Nighthawks when they heard about their military exploits such as slaughtering Black Knife. Following a powerful army into battle meant that they would receive a considerable amount of commissions and would have a higher probability of evading death as well. Therefore, the mercenaries had always preferred to join the stronger group. They were like grass on top of a wall that would always be influenced to join the side that possessed stronger powers. On the battlefield of mercenaries, one could never allow their enemies to discover that they were weaker. Despite being less powerful, it was important to fight with the confidence of a madman so that others would be afraid.

Garen stood on top of the cross-country vehicle that was in front and turned around to glance at the three cars behind him.

The people inside these three cars were the true inner members of the Nighthawks. Excluding the elites, these people were the true members that possessed a certain relationship to the others. Meanwhile, the ones behind them were only here while the winds favored them.

"The position has been confirmed. One of the smaller patrol teams has been ambushed and three people have died," said Carlo's voice through the Hawkeye.

"Move towards that direction."

Garen nodded. When he was dressed in his military gear, a heavy air that was both ruthless and cold spread wafted from his body unconsciously.

"Yes, sir!"

The convoy began to turn around before driving towards the marked direction.

After receiving the commands from the front, the team at the back split themselves up into a few smaller groups that charged forward in a circled formation.

Garen's line of sight returned after he glanced at a cheetah that was climbing up a nearby tree trunk before he looked at a large herd of black animals in front.

The convoy had not driven for a long time before a large herd of African wildebeest charged out in front of them.

Huff huff huff…

Numerous black wildebeest groaned while charging towards the convoy as if they were a wide black river that flowed throughout the olive colored grasslands continuously.

Two twisted horns grew out of the heads of these horse-like animals that resembled cows. They were unlike buffalo as their faces were longer while their bodies were slightly slimmer.

Nonetheless, these creatures charged and ran towards them, they were not inferior to a speedy little sedan car. They were clearly very powerful.

The army groups could not help but stop temporarily.

"We should be able to reach that guy soon," said Baldy quietly as he touched the bandage that he had wrapped around one of his eyes on his own. "Levi is wearing our men's clothes, but our uniforms always have a miniature signal tracking device, making it impossible for him to escape." His expression was slightly bitter as his eye had been personally stabbed and blinded by Levi during close combat.

"There's no rush," said Garen lightly.

Suddenly, he pressed down on the Hawkeye's earpiece and turned his head around to glance behind himself.

A soldier with a face full of greasepaint walked out of the undergrowth there and stood beside the car. He held three little yellow things that resembled embroidery needles in his hands that also seemed like normal bamboo sticks.

"Commander, I've discovered three signal devices nearby from the soldiers that were ambushed," yelled the soldier loudly.

Garen glanced at Baldy while the latter struck his fist against the car door violently, releasing a loud banging noise.

"Do we have any other way of catching up?" asked Garen softly.

"The satellite. In this weather, there should be no problem," answered a woman with a ponytail who stood beside Baldy. "However, I won't be able to guarantee the precision."

"Get to it," Garen nodded.

The woman turned her notebook on before a blinding and chaotic screen reflected and flashed while clicking keyboard noises could be heard. Next, she turned the computer screen around and looked towards Garen and the others.

"It can essentially confirm the approximate area, but the rental cost of the satellite is too high. I need Boss to authorize this."

Garen looked at Baldy and nodded immediately before the latter pressed his right finger down to input his fingerprint into the computer.

Beep…

A soft noise could be heard before the woman turned the computer back towards herself again and began to focus on her investigation.

"Although we won't be able to find Levi's precise whereabouts, Kenna's specific location should not be a problem. He has a satellite phone with him, so we can use our technical means to confirm his location. He used this phone recently as well," explained the woman with the ponytail quietly. "Levi has definitely chased Kenna to his current position, so we will just need to get this."

Garen nodded.

The wildebeest herd had passed as well, leaving shrouds of flying yellow dust behind them.

The convoy continued moving forward.

Chapter 618: Tangled 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Beside a large black canyon near some grasslands, an irregular little earthy yellow village was entrenched in a low-lying area.

The village resembled a dark plaque embedded within this light yellow prairie.

There was an area that resembled historical ruins beside the village where both intact and crumbling stone pillars could be seen everywhere.

Rays of evening sunlight cascaded downwards while the area remained completely silent.

A few African elephants had been dyed red by the sun's intense heat. The elephants used their pillar-like legs to follow the baby elephants, and whenever the baby elephants accidentally ran a few steps too far, the adult elephants would wrap their trunks around them to make them slow down.

Beside clusters of tall green trees, a few giraffes stretched their long necks upwards and chewed the leaves while swaying their tails peacefully and quietly.

Most of the trees in this area grew alone but would form a cluster when more than one of them grew together.

Kenna stood at the entrance of the village and watched a group of half-naked black women gather around a bonfire. They were dancing a dance that he had never seen before. It involved them raising both of their hands and slapping their palms constantly while singing an unknown bleak-sounding song loudly.

An old woman who looked as withered as Dahm Rose sat by the bonfire. She slapped her palms together as well while singing certain parts of the song and clapping according to the music and the beat.

A few younger fellows beat hand drums while sitting on the side, following the rhythm closely.

Someone else was tapping a white thigh bone and making popping noises.

When Kenna woke up this morning, he realized immediately that Dahm Rose was gone. After being unable to find him despite searching for some time, he decided to leave the house on his own.

The natives outside the house were very friendly towards him. Although there was a communication barrier between them, the natives would smile at him anyway.

Inside this place, this tribal village that was completely foreign to him, Kenna was suddenly able to feel an unprecedented sense of tranquility.

"This place is pretty good, right?" Dahm Rose's voice echoed beside him suddenly.

"Yes," Kenna nodded. He had gotten used to the other man's mysterious appearances and disappearances much earlier on.

"There are honest and simple people in this village, as well as ancient inheritors. Unfortunately… We cannot stay here for long," he said regretfully.

"Why?" asked Kenna quietly. "Didn't you say that this place was very safe?" He touched the scar on his chin. This deep scar added to his manliness.

"I'll tell you the truth." When Dahm Rose turned around, a fearful expression flashed in his eyes. "We're actually in the same boat. I'm also being hunted down by someone."

"That can't be true…" Kenna's eyes widened. "What kind of person would be able to hunt you down?"

"Someone that is very strong exists… They're absurdly strong," Dahm Rose replied softly. "Since you're with me now, you may face the same dangers."

"Dahm Rose, do you know that you're currently giving off the same vibe as a fake medicine salesman?" Kenna simply could not believe him. This old trickster always succeeded in fooling others. Even Kenna could not remember how many times he had fallen for his lies.

"It's fine if you don't believe me," Dahm Rose merely shrugged his shoulders. Neither of them continued to speak but decided to quietly appreciate the dancing of the natives that were gathered around the bonfire.

He glanced at a certain direction in the village quietly.

Kenna's troubles were merely a Mortal's worries and were not a serious issue. Compared to this, if that guy managed to catch up to him…

After being chased for so many years and running and fleeing in all directions, perhaps it was time for him to face his final ending.

When he thought about his previous struggles that occurred because he was blinded by greed, such as all of his friends who died and were buried, perhaps no one would have been able to imagine an outcome like this in the beginning.

He was already burnt out from a life that was filled with nothing but hiding. Choosing to return to his hometown where he was born, and where he would soon die, was not a bad decision.

Dahm Rose looked over at the old woman who stood in the middle of the crowd.

"Don't give up. We have been standing behind you from the beginning to the end, Dahm," implied the old woman's gaze.

"Yes… I may have lost everything, but I still remember that I have all of you." The chrysanthemum-like smile appeared on Dahm Rose's face again. Suddenly, he lifted both of his hands up high before balling them into a tight fist, closing his eyes devoutly, and singing along with the melody of the song loudly.

*****************

At the far end of the village, on top of a cliff at the border of the large canyon.

A frail old man in nothing but dark grey bits of cloth stood under the setting sun, leaning on a cane topped with a goat's skull and glancing in the direction of the faraway village quietly.

There was a deep scar on the old man's forehead. It seemed as if a sharp blade had sliced through his skin and flesh violently and it had almost cut through his skull.

"Fate has led me here, Dahm Rose. You won't be able to escape any longer…"

The old man's body was stooped over as if a gust of wind was enough to topple him.

However, there were two golden male lions that were currently lying beside his feet. One of the lions was constantly shaking its mane while the fur on its muscular and streamlined body gleamed red in the evening sunlight.

The clothes on the old man's back seemed like numerous pieces of clothes that had been bound together. Compared to a mummy's neat and orderly bandages, the cloth on his body was an awful mess.

"Everything is guided by fate."

He raised his cane slowly and tapped it on the ground lightly.

Clap.

Suddenly, both of the male lions by his feet roared quietly. They stood up from their initial crouching positions and shook their heads as they moved towards the village.

Next, numerous lionesses began to appear in the forest and grasslands behind them. When counted, they were at least ten of them.

A large herd of hyenas soon appeared behind the lion pride. They gathered together and ran towards them quickly while releasing childlike cries. They formed a black mess, and there were as many as a thousand of them.

They swept through the grasslands like a swarm of locusts. From above, they resembled a black cloud that was drifting towards the village.

Then, a troop of red-faced baboons appeared behind them. These powerful creatures that were so ferocious that even leopards were forced to retreat had formed a crowd. They waved their arms in the air while charging over. They ran in front and behind the hyena herd and constantly howled loudly while baring their sharp teeth.

The old man stood on the cliff and looked down at the herd of ferocious beasts that were surging forward beside him.

"Oh fate…!!" he yelled loudly at the top of his voice. "Tear everyone that obstructs your path to shreds!!"

His words were spoken in the local aboriginal language. The syllables made it sound like a song or a hymn.

Clang clang clang clang!!!

The frantic sound of a gong could be heard throughout the village suddenly. The native people rushed into the village while moving their hands dexterously to prop up numerous sharp wooden railings into the ground. These wooden railings that were as thick as arms made people feel much safer.

Fearful expressions appeared on the faces of all the villagers while they looked at the herds of wild beasts that were surging towards them from afar.

Some of them spoke loudly in their native tongue, saying incomprehensible things.

Some held their young children and ran into their own houses while others gripped their long spears, arrows, and other weapons tightly. However, most of them were fixated on the bonfire in the middle.

The strongest and most mysterious Witch Doctor in the Village, Dalier, was seated there.

Dalier had a similar cane that was made of black wood. There were different colored bone necklaces draped on the cane.

"Don't worry. The ancestors have always been by our side," she howled loudly. It was obvious from her appearance that she was an eighty to ninety year old woman. However, her voice was currently as loud and clear as a young person's voice.

When her voice rang out, the hundreds of people in the village went silent as one, as if it was magic. They gathered at the square, on the flat ground in front of the village entrance. The men raised their weapons such as spears, javelins, bows and arrows, machetes, and axes. It was clear that they had all sorts of weapons.

Meanwhile, under the instructions of their leader, the women began to gather wooden railings, stones, and sacks of soil in a circle in front of the sturdy houses on the outskirts of the village. Soon, they had formed a temporary fortress.

Dalier looked towards the far end of the area. She could see that the man who was standing on the faraway cliff was the true culprit of everything.

"The messenger of disasters that resembles a plague. He has returned…"

Caegarfaber. Perhaps too many people had forgotten this name.

This was a name that once caused fear among everybody. He was a figure that made all of the tribes tremble, and he had finally returned.

The history and stories from that time that resembled an epic were memories that Dalier would never be able to forget throughout her whole life.

She had once assumed that Caegarfaber had died.

She had never expected that Dahm Rose had merely lured him away and that he had only left because of that thing.

"The Ancestral Items cannot be tarnished. They are the source of everything we have. They are the source of our bloodline!" Dalier looked towards Dahm Rose who stood among the crowd.

Both of them exchanged glances before nodding at each other determinedly.

Kenna could accurately feel that he had been dragged into an even more complicated situation…

He watched as his old friend and the old woman exchanged amorous glances at each other while an indescribably weird feeling bubbled up inside him.

"The current situation is slightly inappropriate…" he said softly.

"We want to return to our ancestors' arms," said Dahm Rose indifferently.

"What the…" Kenna's expression changed slightly. This time, he could vaguely tell that his old friend was not joking at all. "Are you sure?"

"Is it because of the crystal books that you brought up?" He seemed to have figured something out. "The Arrival Book that all of you respected as your holy ancestral things?"

"Yes. Those books have always been here with me." Dahm Rose hid within the crowd and explained everything to Kenna quietly. Currently, Dalier had begun to boost the morale of the crowd loudly in a strange, incomprehensible native language.

Looks of grief appeared on the faces of the natives unintentionally before their morale was quickly restored by the encouragement.

Strangely enough, the wild beasts that had gathered outside the village would automatically stop when there was a distance of ten meters left between them and the village. They would whine in fear as if there was something terrifying in front of them.

Dahm Rose saw that the wild beasts outside had stopped. "That's true, the goal of the person that is pursuing me is to get the ancestral book, which all of you know as the Arrival Book."

When they saw this miraculous scene, all of the natives rejoiced at once. They yelled loudly and beat their hands against their chests while raising their spears and making terrifying noises. However, most of them were prostrated on the floor and praying to an unknown force loudly.

"Arrival Book, huh… An item with a secret that is even more troublesome than the Stone Clock of Fortune. It caused a lot of chaos previously." Even though he was not from this world, Kenna could vaguely figure out this point. The Arrival Book that possessed mystical powers was the source of these tribes' strength that also possessed an unimaginable strength.

Chapter 619: Track 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Woo…

The tires of the convoy grazed against the grass while the engine made a loud noise.

Garen sat slumped against the seat casually while both of his eyes were narrowed slightly as if he was dozing off.

"Levi has been spotted!" said the woman with the ponytail suddenly while she was connected to the satellite. "There's a forty-three-kilometer distance between us."

Baldy glanced at Garen but the latter did not stir at all as if he had not heard anything.

"Pursue him," Baldy commanded on his own. He touched his own eye which had been pierced and blinded. A look of hatred flashed through Baldy's remaining eye.

"But it seems like there are signs of a large gathering of animals in front," said the woman with the ponytail softly.

"Just kill any obstructions that we encounter at once," said Baldy with furrowed eyebrows.

"Alright." The woman with the ponytail understood that if Garen remained silent, Baldy would become the head of the group.

They were a group that consisted of more than two hundred people who were all equipped in military gear with various heavy weapons on hand. Therefore, it was unnecessary for them to be afraid of any animals, as they would be able to get rid of a stampeding elephant herd immediately!

The convoy continued to travel forward.

Although Garen had wrapped his arms around himself was continuing to sleep in the car, none of the nearby elites and core members dared to let their guard down even though he was currently resting.

They were aware of the true measures and willpower that this young golden-haired man possessed. He was nothing like a regular twenty-year-old young man but was more like an extremely determined and terrifying mercenary.

Once in awhile, the gazes of the people in the crowd would wander towards Garen unconsciously.

Both of Garen's arms were wrapped around his chest while he slept in the car.

His initial plan for visiting South Africa was to get rid of his enemies and returning after retrieving the Stone Clock of Fortune. However, he never expected that the Stone Clock of Fortune would be involved in a big secret. Moreover, the person who was holding on to it has left the city long ago as well.

His initial plan that had involved a relaxing vacation had fallen through completely.

He thought that this trip would merely be a simple vacation. However, it had turned into a long and arduous track.

Furthermore, that sly Levi had used various means to lure them in the wrong direction many times. In comparison to him, their tracking expert was basically a rookie. No wonder that guy was able to live so comfortably under such dangerous circumstances.

"Another group's signal has been destroyed," reported the woman with the ponytail quietly.

"F*ck!!" Baldy reached his hand out and was about to hit his fist against the car door furiously before he looked at Garen immediately and put his hand down slowly.

How many times had they been down this road?

Not only had Levi led them to a dead end, he had also continuously hunted down the smaller tracking groups that they had sent out. So far, more than fifteen people had already died by his hands.

"Send out a command and tell them to switch to five people in a group. I don't believe that he will be able to get rid of five people so easily."

"Yes."

A row of soldiers in the convoy began to check their weapons carefully before loading their ammunition.

A heavy oppressive aura slowly dominated, as the convoy now resembled a proper army that was traveling towards the village beside the large canyon at a constant speed.

******************

Roar!!

A lioness lunged over in a frenzy and bit at one of the native people's throats but was immediately stabbed in the abdomen by numerous sharp long spears.

A pool of blood remained on the surrounding weeds, dyeing the grasslands red.

This was only one side of the story. Numerous lions, wild dogs, and baboons lunged towards the native people's village and bit them as if they had gone insane from consuming poison.

Most of them were still afraid of the unknown and chose to stop outside the circle on the outskirts of the village. However, a small herd of beasts had charged into the circle with red eyes, fighting with the natives that were defending.

The village was filled with the blood of the natives and the beasts.

On a clean circular area in the middle of the village, no one dared to enter that area even if they were fighting, regardless whether they were man or beast.

A few people stood in this area while the village Witch Doctor Dalier stood in the middle, raising a cane with a chain of bones up high and muttering incantations.

Kenna stood beside her with Dahm Rose. Both of them stood slightly behind her while neither of them moved as they watched the brutal killings that were happening outside.

Astonished, Kenna realized that the village natives were not as weak and helpless as he had expected. Instead, they seemed to possess incredible strength and speed, as well as bravery. He saw two native women work together to kill a lioness with his own eyes.

Their strength seemed to have transformed overnight while their combat moves became abnormally adept and strong.

Meanwhile, the men would only be ambushed by the beasts when they were worn out. Otherwise, each of them would be able to kill at least ten animals, showing that they were terrifyingly efficient.

Sometimes, Kenna wondered if he had truly encountered God. Did the white people know that the natives were actually so fierce during the slave wars?

His mind was frazzled and did not know what expression to put on.

"Just smile, just keep smiling," interrupted Dahm Rose while he stood beside him.

"Oh shit!" Kenna was shocked. "Could you not suddenly appear like that?"

"It's almost time," said Rose Dahm suddenly in a mysterious tone while glancing at a faraway distance. "Remember the incident at the ruins in Ceylon previously?"

"Of course."

"That old guy was once the owner of the ruins."

"... You're saying that, that old guy… Those ruins were fixed for that old guy?" Kenna reacted immediately after being hit by a great surprise.

"He was the messenger of calamities and disasters; the plague of the earth. Three hundred years ago, the tribal leaders formed once formed an alliance to use the Best Book Page to kill and seal that person. However, they never anticipated that he would resurrect now," said Dahm Rose frankly.

"Shit… Are you telling me a legend? He was killed but later resurrected himself? I'm an ancient scholar! Do you know what a scholar is? I'm a person who is well-versed in science!" Kenna really felt like punching this old man violently. "You kept bragging and saying that you've lived for a hundred years, and now you tell me that this guy has lived for three hundred years and still managed to resurrect himself after dying? Could you stop teasing me?"

"Alright… Old friend, seeing that you've regained your vigor, I am truly relieved now," Dahm Rose shrugged his shoulders helplessly.

"Don't interrupt me!" Kenna's mental state had always been strong, and a little scene like this was not enough to scare him. It was like that time when he was attacked by numerous black flesh-eating insects inside the ruins. He had only been scared to the point where his body was limp but was still in much better shape compared to the other guys who had feces and urine running down their legs.

"Be careful! It's here!"

Dalier stood in front of them and spoke suddenly. "Dahm Rose, help me for a bit."

"Alright." Dahm Rose reached his hands out and started removing Dalier's clothes.

"Shit! Both of you should take a look at your surroundings before you fool around!!" Kenna screamed in horror.

"You're fooling around!!" "F*ck!" Dahm Rose and Dalier cursed at him angrily at the same time.

"You you you…! I thought you couldn't speak English?!!" Kenna pointed at Dalier as if he had just seen a ghost.

"I've seen and experienced more things in my life than you! Boy, watch your mouth!" Dalier patted Kenna's shoulder gently before this fellow behaved immediately. His entire body had stiffened and he remained unmoving.

Only then did he realize that Dahm Rose had not removed her clothes, but has simply used his hands to grab the clothes on Dalier's back instead.

After both of them were interrupted by Kenna, the atmosphere became much lighter immediately and was no longer as heavy as before.

Both of them nodded at each other before exchanging glances.

Dalier opened her mouth and stretched her throat.

"Woo~~~~~"

A black book flew out of Dahm Rose's clothes slowly.

There was no wind but it seemed like an invisible hand was holding on to the book and allowing it to hang gently in the air in front of the two people.

The pages of the book were flipped open slowly, displaying the black words and symbols inside that were leaning towards the left. No one was able to understand the things that were recorded in the book.

"Best… Best Book Page…" A frail elderly voice echoed through the faraway winds.

The grass that grew further away seemed to be pushed aside by an unknown force while the withered grass and shrubs collapsed after being rolled over. It was as if the ground that covered the entire area had been gently combed over and pressed down, similar to someone using a tool to comb over a carpet.

Whoosh…

A strong invisible force surged towards the village and pressed down on them furiously.

The wild beasts let out frightened roars and ran helter-skelter without stopping in their original areas as if a life-threatening force was chasing them from behind. They were completely unable to fend off the natives that were slaughtering them for the time being.

Large herds of wild beasts fled the village in a frenzy, resembling a dark yellow torrent that soon disappeared in the faraway grasslands.

"Woo~~~~..." Dalier continued to howl loudly as if the energy in her lungs was limitless.

But Kenna could see that Dahm Rose was constantly taking deep breaths while his hands remained plastered against Dalier's back as if both of their lungs were linked to each other's.

Roar!!

At that moment, Kenna felt as if his own ears had gone deaf. He felt a large air current explode from the black pages while it remained floating in mid-air.

These air currents formed a strong pressure that was used to face the large pressure that came from the further direction head-on.

All of the surrounding natives were enveloped inside these strong pressures. They crawled on the ground and let go of their weapons before singing praises and praying at the top of their voices with extremely devout expressions.

Bang!!

It was obvious that there were no sounds.

But when both of the pressures collided with each other in an airspace that was less than two meters from the village, Kenna felt as if he had heard a thunderous noise at that moment. However, it was not a real noise, but simply a loud bang that only existed within his consciousness.

He made a conscious effort to cover his ears but could not find a way to block the thunderous noise.

"Be careful!!" Someone pulled him suddenly. Kenna could feel that his body had moved a step towards the left before a large invisible air current gushed past his initial position at a moment when everything was hanging by a single thread.

His shoulder had been grazed slightly and a burning pain could soon be felt there.

He was still unable to see anything in his surroundings as his eyes were blinded by numerous colors that blended with one another and twisted around, as if many different shades had been poured into a bucket and mixed, making it impossible for him to see anything clearly.

A faint noise could be heard in his eyes.

"His consciousness has been shaken. It is a weak consciousness… To have encountered an attack like this head-on… It is truly troublesome…" A stuttering noise could be heard continuously as if Dalier was speaking.

Kenna felt as if he was submerged in extremely deep water. His body movements were slowed down and he was unable to see anything and could barely able to hear a few things.

He felt as if someone was pulling him back while he was running. He passed through a colorful path before going through a cave that twisted and turned. This went on for an unknown amount of time.

Bang bang!!

Suddenly, two noises that sounded like claps of thunder rang out beside his ears.

Kenna recovered from his stupor before all of his senses returned to normal.

Suddenly, he realized that he was no longer in the previous village. His surroundings were completely dark as if he was inside a cave tunnel.

Dahm Rose was pulling him backward and following behind Dalier closely. All three of them were standing in front of a passageway that led to a cave opening.

Chapter 620: Track 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Right in front was an empty hall made entirely out of stone. It was pitch black without any light but strangely, everything could be clearly seen. There even was an old man with a crutch standing in the center of the hall, staring quietly at them.

"Where are we?"

"The escape route underneath the village."

"Where're the villagers? Are we going to ignore them?!" Cohen kept asking.

"Us leaving is the biggest protection we can provide them." Rose Dahm replied softly.

"We should be very careful with what's going to come next." Rose Dahm said in a strict tone. "I'm not joking around. We're going to die here if we're not careful."

"I have encountered these situations countless of times." Cohen smiled as if he didn't care at all.

The old man in the living hall in front of them finally reacted. His pitch black eyes started to stare at three of them.

The first one was Dalier. The old man stared at him for a full second before averting his gaze to the next person.

The next person was Rose Dahm, he was stared at for three seconds.

The last one was Cohen, who was glanced at for only a second.

"He's marking…" Dalier whispered. "The death mark… This meant that one of us will be killed by him."

"It's an ancient ritual. According to the beliefs of the ancient witch doctor, they're able to leave a part of their conscience on one's body if they stared at that person long enough. Then those two would be strung together by fate and the witch doctor would be able to track the person within a certain range."

"This also means that he's firmed in killing one of us." Rose Dahm smiled wryly. "We're definitely in his killing list."

"Why don't we hand over the book to him? That item is meaningless to us right?" Cohen whispered.

The other two stared at him in anger and it made Cohen shrugged helplessly.

"Alright fine, fine. Quit staring at me, I'm just merely saying it."

"Retreat!" Suddenly, Dalier shouted.

A faint buzzing sound came from the stone hall.

It was like those of swarming bees and Cohen, who had experienced this before, his face turned pale and retreated without hesitation.

Three of them ran crazily inside the tunnel.

Cohen turned his head and looked back and had goosebumps.

Behind them in the tunnel was countless of white worms which had a pair of transparent wings flying after them. He could even see the sharp needle-like mouth which resembled mosquitoes.

These white bugs came in like a flash flood as they went after the trio in the tunnel.

A fork suddenly appeared in front of them and each path led to different directions in the tunnel.

"Here!!" Cohen went into the inner path.

"Be careful!" A hand pulled him back.

There was a giant stone ball that was starting to get loose.

Boom!

The stone ball that was at least four meters tall started to roll towards them through the passage. The old man's face could strangely be seen on the surface of the stone. It was like of an illusion.

"Fuck me!!" Cohen was frightened by it. If he were to run into that path earlier, he would be trapped in between the stone ball and the countless of human eating bugs and would've died by now.

"You guys can't escape." The old man's voice came from afar.

"Go to hell!" Cohen shouted loudly.

Pew!!

Suddenly a sharp stone flew past him from behind and landed on the stonewall in front as it sparked.

"Bring it on!!" Cohen shouted.

The trio started to dart around left and right as they kept evading the stones shot by the swarm of worms.

The old man behind them kept waving his crutch as stones flew towards them.

"There's more in front!!" Dalier shouted.

The other two looked to the front to see a huge giant stone ball rolling with the diameter of five meters towards them. As it rolled, it seemed to be able to squash everything into mincemeat inside the tunnel. Similarly, the old man's face could be seen on the surface of the ball.

"To the left!!" It wasn't sure if it's Dalier or Rose Dahm was shouting.

Cohen couldn't make out who's who in the situation any longer. He barely made it as he moved to the left as he entered into a narrow space.

Boom boom…

The stone ball rolled past the trio.

"Cohen…"

Suddenly, Cohen heard someone calling out to him and he looked at where the voice came from.

He saw the ceiling of the tunnel broke apart. As the light shone in, a human figure jumped into it.

"Cohen, hand over the Sone Clock of Fortune." This man was a handsome white man with golden short hair. He was muscular and gave off a cold aura.

The trio ignored him as the old man was catching up to them even after the swarm of worms was crushed by the giant stone. He somehow walked out from among the countless worms and evaded the giant stone mysteriously. As he moved his crutch, it started buzzing once more.

"Move forward!! Quickly!!" Dalier shouted.

Rose Dahm followed tightly from behind and Cohen was the last one running at the back.

"Evade!!"

Another giant stone rolled towards them.

Coincidentally, another narrow path by the stonewall appeared and three of them hid in it.

The stone ball went directly towards the golden-haired man. He couldn't evade in time and there was no place for him to run but to welcome the stone ball.

"What a pity…" Cohen prayed for the fellow as he was completely innocent.

At this moment.

Boom!!

A loud explosion could be heard as if it was a volcano eruption.

The giant stone was shattered into millions of pieces in the middle and what came out of it was the golden-haired man.

"Cohen, hand over the Stone Clock of Fortune." Garen slowly walked out from the center. Countless of bugs which were surrounding him mysteriously died off and layers of them were soon accumulated on the ground.

Cohen, who was sprinting forward with all of his might, turned around to look as he heard the explosion. He literally paused as he saw the scenario.

"F*ck me… This guy is even worse…!"

The mysterious old man started shouting as he stomped his crutch.

Five to six stone balls started rolling but were demolished by Garen's fist. Each fist was like a dynamite.

Everyone started to lose their calm when they saw Garen breaking the stone like he was popping a balloon.

"What the f*cking hell!! Cohen, how did you anger this monster!!" Rose Dahm finally lost his cool. This was something out of his expectations and wasn't in his control at all.

"I don't know!! I don't even know him!!!" Cohen shouted.

As the both of them fled frantically with Dalier leading the way, the giant stone that had been chasing them was now a tool to block the person after them.

"Cohen!!!" Garen shouted and in an instant, the giant ball was split in half as Garen moved his hand.

"F*ck me! Stop chasing me!!" Cohen cried as he sprinted.

While Garen was chasing them from the back, giant stone balls would occasionally block him from them. Eventually, the mysterious old man was angered by Garen. He started shouting and would summon sharp stones and shoot them towards Garen. This made it more difficult for Garen to chase them.

Garen was angered.

The moment he was slightly less alert, the whole team encountered a swarm of crazy beasts and were almost separated.

The whole team continued moving forward after killing a portion of the beasts via some heavy weapons.

After that, they encountered trembles similar to an earthquake when the village was right before their eyes. The earth suddenly trembled and the whole village was sunk into a deep pit.

He could avoid it in time but not so far the team.

At least half of the Nighthawk team's weapons was disrupted by this deep pit.

Afterwards, Levi secretly betrayed them and he escaped into this tunnel.

Afterwards, the trembled continued and the team which managed to reassemble for a moment were separated again. Raged, Garen went down and killed everyone in sight!!!

After a series of incidents, he was angered as he was here to take revenge and not on a holiday!

It took him great effort to find any movement underground. Coincidentally, he met Cohen's team as he jumped into it.

Since the Stone Clock of Fortune appeared right in front of him, he naturally would try to obtain it.

Hence the current situation.

The trio ran at the front, Garen chasing them in the middle and the old man was at the very back.

Garen was extremely annoyed by the old man but was afraid to lose the trio if he were to deal with the old man. He was really surprised by the turn of unexpected events today.

As long as he found Cohen, Levi shouldn't be far away. He could deal with almost everything if he could obtain the secrets of the Stone Clock of Fortune.

Boom!!

Another stone ball was split in half.

"What the f*ck! Cohen, didn't you say you're being chased because of a normal antique?! How could a normal antique relate to such a monster? Are you f*cking kidding me!!??" Rose Dahm lost his cool and scolded. Since these two were able to become best friends, their characters were almost the same even in the face of danger.

"It wasn't this guy before!!" Cohen still had the energy to reply back even though his face was drenched with sweat and he looked like he could pass out any moment.

"Pass the Stone Clock of Fortune to him!!" Rose Dahm cried out.

"Faster!!" Cohen agreed as well as he quickly took out a small white porcelain item.

He immediately tossed the item behind.

As the small bottle rotated in the air, Garen obtained it without much difficulty.

He glanced at the small bottle and continue pursuing them.

"F*ck! Why is he still here?!"

Rose Dahm felt hopeless.

"How would I know!!?" Cohen was on the verge of collapsing as his stamina was fast depleting and even he himself believed that he would die from the immense exertion.

"What is that floating thing?" Garen squinted as he saw a black book-liked item which seemed important floating in front of them. "Hand over that for me and I will leave you alone."

"F*ck…"

Suddenly the trio felt helpless as they realized that he was looking at the book.

Wasn't it the same from the very beginning?

Chapter 621: Track 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"What should we do now?!" Rose Dahm's original plan had been foiled by Garen, and now he didn't know what to do.

Dalier looked back and didn't say a word. His eyes were clearly filled with complicated intent.

"Continue running and don't panic. I still have another backup plan."

"Alright." Rose Dahm nodded.

Compared to the two who had extraordinary stamina, Cohen was greatly exhausted after these ten minutes of sprinting. He was already on the verge of collapsing; both of his eyes were rolling up despite his legs maintaining a surprising pace.

As one looked closer, one could see a black aura glowing on his legs.

Even so, he was so exhausted that he couldn't even speak but panted all the way.

The tunnel was pitch black and only the Best Book Page was faintly glowing.

The tunnel became more and more narrow until the distance between the stone walls had shrunk from five meters to just a meter.

The stone ball appearing in front became thinner and thinner to the point it should be called a stone wheel instead of a stone ball.

The hefty footsteps from the trio kept reverberating in the tunnel. Seeing Cohen was at his limit, Rose Dahm turned around and patted on his shoulder.

"I can temporarily lend you your energy from the next day. However, you will need to rest for a week to fully recover. Remember that."

Cohen nodded and he suddenly felt very energetic. All the tiredness from before had completely disappeared and what replaced it was invigorating energy.

"This feels great!!" He couldn't help but comment.

"To the right!!" Dalier shouted.

The trio turned to the right and went into a corner which appeared before them. After that, they turned left and went into a pitch black nook.

Boom boom boom…

Three stone wheels rolled past them, filling up the whole passageway.

They could still faintly hear the old man shouting at the very back.

"Fate…"

The trio didn't dare to stop moving as they climbed out from the nook and continued running. After they climbed out of the small nook, it disappeared and reformed into the stone wall, as though the nook had never been there.

"This is very mysterious!" Cohen replied energetically.

"The Best Book Page's power is endless. Dalier used its power to pull us into a space that no one but us could enter to evade the stone wheel." Rose Dahm explained.

"What logic is that?"

Boom!!

A huge explosion could be heard from the back, breaking his sentence.

"Quickly!!!" Dalier shouted "In another hundred meters just jump as far as you can! Ignore whatever is about to happen! Jump! With all your might!"

The trio's speed was extremely fast, just like lightning shooting through the tunnel. In that instant, it was as if their bodies were stretched as the trio became a black line and traveled a hundred meters in an instant.

Pew!!

It was a dead end at the front and there was no path left.

As the trio turned here and there in the passage, Dalier was the first one to jump and climb against the stone wall.

Sizzle!!

A sound could be heard similar to of the noise emitted from a radio or television.

She jumped and as she was about to collide against the stonewall, she entered the stone wall and disappeared just like one would jump into a pool.

Without any hesitation, Rose Dahm too jumped into it as if the stone wall was just an illusion. However, in reality, that was just a mirror instead of a stone wall.

Cohen couldn't even react in time as his legs didn't even listen to his commands and he was propelled into the stone wall.

Ahhhhh!!

He shouted as he disappeared through the stone wall.

In an instant, the golden-haired man arrived the scene and stopped moving.

Garen looked around but he didn't see any trace of them. He moved the tip of his leg here and there and found the trio's footprints.

He then looked at the dead end in front of him.

He then instantly appeared in front of the stone wall and gave it a good punch!!

Boom!!

The tunnel trembled greatly as countless stones and clouds of dust filled the air. As the wind blew and the clouds of dust settled, a web-like crack appeared on the stone wall.

At the center of the crack was a clear hole of unknown depth.

Garen pulled out his hand which had a leather glove on out of the stonewall and exercised his shoulder. His whole right arm was inside the stone wall, right up to his shoulder.

"It's solid?" He muttered skeptically.

He looked at his surroundings.

His gaze was filled with immense power in the dark. It was so terrifying that even the few mice present were so frightened they were petrified.

Boom!!

He punched the stone wall once again.

Boom boom boom boom!!!

Fist after fist.

Explosions could be heard and the tunnel kept trembling.

Garen kept punching the stone wall with both of his fists. His hands were as hard as a drill as he created holes on the stonewall with every punch.

Suddenly, he stopped moving and looked at the back.

Thud, thud, thud.

The sound of a crutch hitting the floor appeared behind of Garen.

The mysterious old man slowly appeared at the corner of the entrance. He had the skull of a mountain goat on the top of the wooden crutch in his hand, and he was staring calmly at Garen.

"Are you… a mortal?"

The old man used a rather strange international English to ask him.

He seemed to be surprised, skeptical and astonished.

Hehe.

Garen smiled as he pulled out his limb from the stone wall. As he turned around, huge pieces of rubble fell out from the stone wall.

"Tell me, where did they go?" Garen stared at the old man like a lion staring at its prey.

"I do not know." The old man shook his head. "Although I don't know where they have gone to, I know they will be back here eventually."

Once again, he analyzed Garen from head to toe.

"Mortal, you have an unbelievable great physique and will. Do you mind telling me how you obtain such strength?"

His body was filled with a mysterious power that couldn't be seen.

"As an exchange, I will teach you my source of strength."

"Oh!" Garen patted the dust on his hand and gave a strange looking smile. This was the first time that he was in contact with a person with strong power. Compared to the Blood Breeds from the past, this old man in front of him was constantly surrounded by a mysterious force field. It looked like some sort of flowing aura yet it looked like lava. This made the person even more mysterious.

Garen wasn't able to determine what it was.

"Isn't your power only usable by women?"

"You seem to know it well. Frankly, regardless if it's the witches or us males, we are able to use the power of our ancestors. The only difference is that the success rate for a female is much higher as males have a lower tendency to attain peace due to their greed for power, affecting the fate of the ancestral power." The old man explained. "Hence if the women have a strong desire to obtain the ancestral power, they wouldn't be able to contain it."

"Are you sure they'll be back here?" Garen repeated his question once more.

"Of course. This is the leaping point so they won't be able to escape here." The old man nodded.

Garen believed him as the old man's objective was obviously the same as his. He was after the book the trio had. Since the opponent wasn't panicked at all, he must be telling the truth.

"What is that black book page item?"

The old man listened and was slightly stunned.

"Are you chasing after something that you do not know about?" He looked at Garen in disbelief as if he couldn't believe there was such a person in this world.

"Aren't you afraid that item would be harmful towards you?'

"Something is only harmful when it excites more than your body can resist." Garen shrugged. "As long as one is strong enough, then a harmful item can only be a nutrient to a stronger self."

"That would require you to deplete your life force. Even the Blood Breeds wouldn't even dare to grow in such a manner." The old man said.

"That's my issue." Garen smiled. "Now, tell me. What is that black book page?"

Both of them stopped talking as they stared at each other.

After a long while.

The old man finally opened his mouth and this time, his mood was much better.

"That is the Best Book Page. It is said that it contains records and knowledge of an unknown world."

"What effect does it have?"

The old man didn't reply immediately as he stared at Garen.

"Your greed will lead you into the abyss."

"The abyss won't be able to stop me." Garen smiled and his white teeth flashed in the darkness.

"You're too crazy." The old man held his crutch tightly.

"Between you guys and the Blood Breeds, who's stronger?" Garen suddenly asked a very sensitive question.

"Hmpf!" The old man scoffed as his eyes turned black. He held his crutch high and slammed it to the ground.

It looked slow but in that instant, the crutch seemed to touch the ground like an illusion.

Thud!!

Amidst the clear sound.

Garen's body was reacting to it.

Items like black snakes or sharp arrows were shot towards Garen.

Garen gestured his hands into a claw shape and waved around in the air as sharp whistles could be heard with every strike. Multiple white lines could be seen as a vacuum was created.

Within the darkness, his eyes were glowing red as if there was something beaming it out from the inside of his eyes. The red eyes were horrifying to watch.

Boom!

With a deep collision sound, the claw stopped short, less than a meter away from the old man.

"Entanglement!" The old man shouted. There was neither light nor movement.

Within the darkness, only the sound of the crutch hitting the ground could be heard as it reverberated in the tunnel.

It was as if everything was an illusion for there was no light, no abnormality. The old man took a few steps back as he looked calmly at Garen.

He had no additional movement as he stared calmly. Unknown to Garen, this stare had created a strong power.

Chapter 622: Track 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This invisible energy surrounded Garen instantly.

This energy was extremely strange as it would change based on Garen's strength. The more strength he used, the more powerful it became. It was similar to a glue as it stuck tightly to Garen's body.

With his amazing speed, it was strange for Garen to let the opponent shout within this wide area.

Under normal circumstances, he would have choked the opponent before he could even shout.

However, it seemed that there was something that was creating distance between him and the old man.

This made him recall those unique ones back in the totem world. Those unique ones were usually troublesome as if he didn't have enough power to disrupt or influence the field, then he could only be played within the opponent's palm.

Only when he exerted a force strong enough to disrupt the surrounding, only then could he break out from the effect.

Back in the days, he made use of the strong force exerted from the Totem Light to disrupt the stability of the surrounding so that it would be non-effective against him.

However, he currently did not have such strength.

Garen squinted his eyes as he grasped his right fist firmly. If there's a need, he would immediately go for the kill.

He had yet to truly release all his power in an instant before. However, he had been able to predict his strength based on small amounts of release and it was near towards his peak in the totem world.

Although it was just an instant, it would most likely injure his body and would require some potential points to recover.

If he were to release half of it… It shouldn't be any problem… However, he should use his normal strength to test it first.

Without any hesitation, Garen's right hand was filled with explosive energy as he sprinted towards two o'clock from his relative position.

He combined the energy with the Slaughtering Hand Secret Technique as his fist exploded.

He lunged forth like a swordfish and with a gentle roll, he landed in an empty space a few meters away from the old man.

However, that energy was still glued to him.

His every action, which started from attacking to retreating was about two seconds long. Then, the old man raised up his crutch once again and slammed it down once more.

Garen felt that his speed had reduced tremendously. His eyes flashed red as he increased his Slaughtering Hand to its maximum. Although it didn't make use of his life force, its potency was on the same level as he was at his peak in the Secret Technique world.

He immediately pressed his shoulder muscle with his right hand.

Pewe!

The muscle sunk and a gas leaked out from it as it whistled.

Garen seemed to be in pure pain. It was a natural reaction after hitting an acupuncture point.

After mastering the Slaughtering Hand, he had developed a lot of unique techniques and one of them was this acupuncture point.

He found out about this point from an ancient book. Combined with the characteristic of the Slaughtering Hand with a special activation method, he was able to produce an extraordinary amount of power. In an instant, his physique would increase greatly and be able to release a great amount of life force. Although it wasn't as powerful as the life force produced by the Slaughtering Hand, he was able to merge the life force together and form a single source of power.

As this acupuncture point was able to bring out the most life force after excitation, Garen had named it as the Life's Secret Point.

As he searched through his memory in the Secret Technique World, he was able to find nine of these secret acupuncture points and had left two of them as hidden points. No one was able to use it except him. The remaining seven points were collected together and he had formed it into a set of secret skills.

The potency of this secret technique was terrifying as he would instantly increase the status of the practitioner.

For example, if he were to open a point, he could increase his speed by one fold. By opening two points, he was able to increase it by two folds and three folds if it were three points. This wasn't just simply adding up the strength of the practitioner. What made it different from other secret skills was that it could be superimposed.

It could be superimposed with other secret skills!

This was why it was terrifying!

If one's physique was strong enough, one could activate the Shooting Shadow Secret Skill and Two-Faced Waterbird Fist before activating the Life's Secret Point to achieve a strength that stood at the edge of the body's limit.

Perhaps he had missed the life he once had back on Earth. Since the number of points was seven in total, Garen named this secret skill as the Seven Star Life's Secret Point. It was directly named from the Big Dipper from the ancient days of China.

"First star!" Garen muttered.

Hah!!

He growled as his skin started turning black. His muscle quickly expanded and his height increased from 1.8 meters to at least 2 meters.

It was different from the time when he had Mammoth Secret Technique and was called the King of the Century. He wasn't as big as before but he definitely looked more fit as his black skin shone like metal.

This was the result of activating the first star and the entangled force was immediately suppressed. It didn't disappear but rather its effect did not affect Garen any longer.

As he raised his legs and was about to rush towards the old man.

"Delay!" The crutch hit the floor once more.

The old man shouted and the invisible force surrounding him flew out and disappeared in the air between Garen and him.

Suddenly, Garen could feel an invisible force holding his limbs. He couldn't figure out where the source of the power was from as if it was air that was resisting him. This made him frowned.

As he just got off from the entanglement, he now had to experience an obstruction towards his movement.

However, due to him being two times stronger than before, he didn't feel much of an inconvenience.

The Seven Star Life's Secret Point was a secret skill came about due to the life force created from the Slaughtering Hand. To him, the life force could be accumulated via the Slaughtering Hand. He was distressed over the fact that the life force accumulated from the Slaughtering Hand had to be used all at once, even though it's powerful, instead of using it economically. After some series of thought, Garen had developed the Seven Star Life's Secret Point, which was the most effective way to use the Life Force. It was the most efficient way to convert the life force to actual strength.

However, this sort of secret skill was a life depleter for others and shouldn't be used carelessly, as it would require life force to be able to use it.

To others, life force was their lifespan.

However, as a secret skill that could be superimposed with other techniques, it definitely possessed terrifying strength.

Garen smiled as he twitched his body under this state.

"Polaris Fierce Arts!!"

He expanded once more as he pressed his chest with his finger once more and the air that was pushed away from his body could be clearly seen.

The Polaris Fierce Arts, which was a plain secret method, was completely terrifying under his modification.

One Punch!

Garen threw out a right punch and in an instant, a line of vacuum was formed in the air from the extreme speed and power. His fist was so fast that the air couldn't move in time to fill up the space he'd created, thus creating a vacuum.

"Vacuum slash!!"

Garen's right fist stirred up the air in the underground.

His golden short hair waved about like a lion's mane as the wind blew.

His fist reached the old man instantaneously as he opened up his fist and shaped it into a knife. He then slashed down like his hand was the sharpest knife on the planet.

The sound of the fist in the air changed into a sharp tone.

"Speed enhancement!!" The old man didn't panic at all as he shouted loudly before Garen attacked. At the same time, his body moved slightly to the left and by the time the hand knife reached in front of him, the invisible force had surrounded Garen's hand knife.

In that instant, a strange phenomenon occurred.

Garen's hand suddenly grew much longer as his slashing speed had tremendously increased. On the other hand, his body's speed remained at the same delayed speed.

In that instant, due to the difference of speed between his hand and his body, it had torn his body.

While his hand knife hadn't even touched the old man, Garen could feel that his right hand was about to be torn away from his body.

It was his first time experiencing such a strange phenomenon.

With a mysterious force added to his powerful slash, its strength went overboard as the momentum was too powerful, causing a difference in speed between his hand and body. For a commoner, this would cause an instant injury towards the muscle and worst, he would have torn his hand apart, decapitating it in the process.

However, Garen scoffed.

He stomped hard to put in a new source of energy, increasing his body's speed and reducing the strain on his hand. He had always casually exerted strength on his body. As he had surpassed the realm of the King of the Century, he had total control over his body and wouldn't be affected by external causes!

He instantly regained control of his hand knife.

The duration of them exchanging blows was instant. It was so fast that one wouldn't even have enough time to inhale or blink.

With this exchange at such speed and reaction, both of them had acknowledged one another.

Both knew that they were on the same level.

The hand knife ultimately missed as it cut deep into the stone wall, leaving a deep gash on it.

The old man unknowingly returned back to his original position two meters away from him.

"Mortal…" He gently caressed the mountain goat's skull on his crutch. "I have never seen such a strong mortal…"

Chapter 623: Arrangement 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen pulled out his hand from the wall.

"What are you trying to say?"

He couldn't make out the source of his energy as it seemed to appear out of thin air. This made him slightly wary as the ancestral energy seemed very mysterious. He was deliberating if he should have done his research thoroughly before fighting against them.

"Why don't we work together?" Suddenly, the old man said something which stunned Garen.

Pfft!

Suddenly a wound appeared on his pale, wrinkled right cheek and fresh black blood spewed out from it. It wasn't slow flowing but sprayed instead, as droplets splattered onto the floor.

Then, something strange happened. The blood on the ground moved about as if it was a living worm. It then formed a black line and swiftly climbed back up and into the old man's face through his leg as the wound recovered.

Although Garen wasn't injured and the energy spent using secret skills was negligible to him, this might be a good opportunity to understand the arts of the witch doctor, as the opponent's skills were completely foreign to him.

It wasn't like he'd dismissed approaching Raffaele to understand everything. It was just that Raffaele was too close to his family.

Surprisingly, this world had given him an opportunity to live a peaceful life, and he didn't want to disrupt it just yet. In addition to that, he hadn't been taking the arts of witchcraft seriously and he didn't think that it would be this effective. Hence, he decided to be more alert against it.

"Ally with you? Since we're teaming up, it means we will have a common enemy right?" Garen shrunk and returned to his original shape. His shirt, however, was messed up by this transformation and he now looked like a playboy out for a trip.

"The Blood Breed." The old man's eyes turned black. "Two hundred years ago, they surrounded me and killed me, and my grandchildren placed my torn corpse into a constructing tomb during my funeral. Consequently, I revived by absorbing the energy of the universe and I was awakened by an adventurer just a few decades ago."

"Revive…" Garen's eyes flashed. "Are you saying that you can revive? If so, what's the cost of reviving? I'm not really related to the Blood Breed, else I wouldn't have teamed up with you for such a small matter."

"Unfortunately, Resurrection can only be used by the powerful ones blessed by the ancestor. The path you walk is different from mine so you can't use it." The old man shook his head. "As for the Blood Breed, are you sure you're not related to them?" He suddenly smiled in mockery which made it strange in the tunnel.

"Why are you laughing?" Garen's face turned serious.

"Your body, it's being marked by the Blood Breed's Illusive Trace. Did you not know that?" the old man stopped laughing but he was still smiling.

"An Upper-level Blood Breed had marked you with Illusive Trace. Judging from its level, it's most likely Death Apostle level." The old man smiled. "Simply put, you should have been targeted by a very powerful Blood Breed. They are always out to hunt for the best blood vessel with the strongest physique and will. Unfortunately, you've been targeted by one of the Death Apostles."

Garen's face turned pale.

He recalled the strange dreams he had recently. They were dreams that he had never had before, where his strong will and soul were able to fully control the reaction of his body.

However, that dream was totally out of his imagination.

"They have taken you as the best blood source. The Blood Breeds are able to obtain mysterious power through ingesting blood and even we don't know how they obtain their strength. Every Upper-level Blood Breed and Death Apostle are mysterious and powerful." The old man explained in a simple manner. "However, I am different from other witches as I do know a few things about them. For example, they lure, scare and even control their prey through dreams…"

Garen's pupils shrunk.

"Dream…" He couldn't help himself as the sound of explosions started to reverberate from his muscles and joints as if they were grenades implanted in them. The horrifying explosions kept ringing in series.

"The current me is so weak that I haven't recovered half of my strength and it appears that you've hidden a huge amount of life force. That power seems to be evil in your hands and perhaps this is the reason why they have yet to make a move on you yet. Perhaps he's frightened of you too." The old man explained.

Garen closed his eyes and pondered for a while.

He then opened his eyes.

"Looks like I do have the need to understand the world of the Blood Breeds…"

The old man in front of him smiled with joy.

"You've made a wise decision."

Boom!!

Suddenly an explosion could be heard.

A shapeless void appeared behind them as if a whirlpool had occurred in mid-air and there were a few black dots floating inside it.

The black dots became larger and larger.

Thud!

A black pile of items was pushed out from the whirlpool and landed on the floor.

This pile of black stuff was actually three people clinging to one another.

Dalier, Rose Dahm, and Cohen were hugging each other as their eyes were glazed and white fluids were dripping out from their mouths.

What's strange was that a faint black light was coming off from their bodies.

"Where's the book page?" The old man walked forward as he asked. "Tell me, where is the book page?"

Three of them looked dazed as if they didn't understand what he was trying to say. The black light coming off from their bodies were preventing the old man from approaching them closer.

Garen crossed his hand as he walked to the back to observe the situation.

Since he found out that he had been marked by the Blood Breeds, what was on his mind right now was to find a way to find out which Blood Breed had marked him instead of the Book Page.

The nature of this power was completely unknown to him. The main issue was that he didn't even know how the Blood Breed had marked him.

Buzz!!

Suddenly an electrical buzzing sound could be heard.

The old man withdrew his right hand which was about two meters away from the bodies. A wisp of black smoke was curling from the tip of his bony finger.

"What's the current situation?" Garen frowned as he couldn't understand what he was trying to do.

"They have left." The old man frowned as well. "They made use of the nature of the power to leave this place."

Garen was confused as he looked at the trio who were hugging each other. "Aren't they still here?" He looked at the empty gaze in their eyes as he pondered. "Are you saying that their consciousnesses have left their bodies?"

"Precisely." The old man nodded. "They're relying on this method to escape from my search."

"What's the point? Their body is being held hostage by us and they have to return to their bodies sooner or later." Garen asked calmly.

"That's not the case." The old man shook his head. "They can instantly pull their bodies away from here from afar. Furthermore, if they wish, they are able to build a new body if they wish to do so."

"What's the rationale behind this?" Garen didn't understand the logic behind the witch doctor or witch's power at all.

The old man glanced at him. "On our path, you're not even considered as a disciple so it's understandable that you don't get it." He looked back and continued staring at the three bodies lying on the ground. "If you wish, I am willing to pass down some knowledge to you as a partner. Do you wish to know more?"

"You're willing to give me knowledge?" Garen thought that these kinds of mysterious and powerful information weren't simply passed around. It shouldn't be simply be revealed without any terrible ordeal. How could this guy simply pass down his knowledge?

"It's fine." The old man smiled. "We obtain this knowledge through dangerous means, which is searching endlessly in the universe. Even if one knows how to execute the procedure, one's body must be willing to cooperate and believe in it. Hence, it would be meaningless if one were to just know about it as the main foundation is to control your will."

"Your statement sounds very dubious to me," Garen whispered. "Fine. I hope to learn from you from now on. Perhaps this old knowledge would be useful to me."

The old man laughed at him. "My name is AG so you can call me that. We still have a lot of opportunities in the future so we should deal with these fellows who stole the book page."

Both of them stopped arguing after that. Garen took out his walkie-talkie and looked at the signal. He didn't care much about the old man's actions and started to contact his underlings.

"Angie, where's Baldy?"

"Boss is stuck in a deep drain nearby and is trying to pull the car out." A female voice came from the walkie-talkie.

"Are you with Cadytius?"

"Yeah."

"Bring your men to my place. Be careful as the ground will collapse at any given moment. Remember to bring in the heavy artillery and surveillance system."

"Understood."

The walkie-talkie was then switched off. This woman, Angie, and Cadytius were the best among the Nighthawks. They were elites who had practiced the Shooting Shadow Secret Skill. With their strength and the surveillance system, they could surveil a circular area of up to a few kilometers in detail.

The mysterious old man AG walked towards the trio, sat on his knees and placed his crutch on his knees. He then placed his hands together and started to tremble as if he went crazy.

Garen didn't know what he was preparing to pull but he could feel an invisible force emitting out from his body as it gathered on the trio.

"I'm going to leave so that I can track them. I hope you can stay here and take care of my body." The old man AG turned around and told Garen.

"No problem." Garen nodded.

As Garen finished speaking, the old man's gaze lost its colors and immediately turned dim, just like a faded gemstone.

Garen frowned as he circled these four people. Nothing strange happened near them as everything became peaceful once more.

Every second passed quietly as Garen sat waiting. The immense aura given off from his body, even though it wasn't a real aura, was strong enough to ensure the worms in the old tree didn't get near to him.

After a while.

"Ah!!"

A sharp scream was heard.

Cohen and the other two jumped out quickly and the first thing crossed their mind was to run towards the stone wall.

Garen reacted and with a stomp at his feet.

Boom! He shot out and grabbed Dalier by his neck and pushed against the wall.

Boom!

After a huge booming sound, Dalier vomited white fluid and fainted.

Rose Dahm and Cohen were scared as they shivered. They stood still as they stared at Garen and they didn't even dare to make any sudden movement.

Their faces were so pale that it seemed like they had no blood at all, as though they'd lived through their worst nightmares.

Then, the old man AG slowly woke up.

He took up his crutch, coughed loudly and stood up.

"Hand over the book page. That's mine!" He said calmly as he stared at the two with his black eyes.

Seeing Garen and the old man standing together without any intention of fighting, they were even more horrified.

"What do you want? The book page has been hidden by us at a place no one will ever find."

Rose Dahm shouted loudly.

"You people stole it away from my underground palace. Then you people claim that it is your item that you inherited from your ancestor! You people are mindless thieves!" AG said fiercely. "Fate has guided me to you. Hand it over to me and I'll consider letting you guys live."

Chapter 624: Arrangement 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen who was at the side started to become impatient. "Cohen, What's the secret of the Stone Clock of Fortune? Furthermore, where is Levi? Tell me."

Cohen shook his head.

"I don't know. Levi should be tailing me but with all the fuss, I don't know if he's still around. Everything that had happened here must have been out of his imagination. The Secret of the Stone Clock of Fortune? Frankly, there's no such treasure." He smiled wryly. "We made that out to trick you guys. The so-called treasure was the fear of unable to steer your attention with the Stone Clock of Fortune. So we made up some lies so that everyone would be in the dark."

At the other side, the old man had planted his crutch on Rose Dahm's chest as they whispered swiftly between them. It seemed like an ancient language as none of them could understand what they were talking about.

As both of them were being interrogated by Garen and the old man, Garen took out a white porcelain bottle which resembled the Stone Clock of Fortune as he listened to Cohen's explanation.

The small bottle was similar to the eastern white jaded porcelain bottle. It had a thin neck and was only the size of a palm. One could hear something ringing inside as one shook the bottle.

"Is this the Stone Clock of Fortune?" Garen frowned.

He could feel that this small bottle's surface was covered with a thin layer of cool qi. It was the qi of the potential points.

He tried to absorb it but the layer of qi was glued onto the surface of the bottle and wouldn't budge at all.

"Yes. Legend says that there's a mysterious story hidden inside the bottle. However, it looks like an antique to me." Cohen was helpless. "Believe me. We are not responsible for what happened to the Nighthawks. It was all Levi's doing. That guy is manipulative and worked with everyone to ambush the Nighthawks…"

"I know that already, which is why you're still alive." Garen butted in. "Next I would need you to lure Levi out for me. That fucker had killed quite a number of my patrols…" His eyes were filled with rage.

Cohen couldn't help but emit cold sweat. "What do you want me to do?"

"Simple. Bait him out." Garen smirked as he reached out his right hand and tapped even to eight locations on his body.

Tap tap tap tap!!

A series of clear taps could be heard and Cohen started to scream as if he was being slaughtered.

Instantly, at least ten bones in his bodies were broken as he flopped down onto the floor. His head and neck were covered in tiny droplets of sweat.

"No… Stop… I have a better idea to lure him out…" He begged.

"But I believe this is the best idea, no?" Garen smiled gently but it was a horrifying one in the eyes of Cohen.

He picked up his leg and kicked him without any mercy.

Boom!!

Cohen was hit by the waist. He flew and tumbled about and crashed into the stone wall by the side. Coincidentally, his leg was smashed into a sharp corner of the stone wall.

Ouch!!

He still had the energy to scream.

"Oh my god! Oh my god…"

Garen walked towards him and picked him up.

"I'm going to create a scenario where you're severely injured and was left alone in an empty wide field which was the most obvious to be spotted. To go against an enemy that could be dealt with from a shot from afar, I believe Levi would most likely make his move."

He picked up Cohen's head which was in immense pain.

"He will be dead the moment he makes his move."

The Nighthawks was his first trial and his first step in building a certain deterrence to let other forces know that he was unstoppable.

Buzz buzz..

The walkie-talkie suddenly rang.

Garen took it out and a girl's voice came out from it.

"Captain, boss Baldy has found and obtained five Stone Clocks of Fortune. However, we have lost a few people, do you need us to go to your location immediately?"

"Oh?" Garen's eyes flashed. "Another five Stone Clocks of Fortune?"

"That's… right. Excluding the Stone Clock of Fortune that has been broken, there.. Should be six more…" Cohen replied with agony.

"Bring him here, send him my location."

"Yes." An engine could be heard from the walkie-talkie.

Garen pulled Cohen back to where he was kicked as their tussle had resulted in them leaving the dead end.

As Garen arrived at the dead end, AG was conversing with Rose Dahm calmly in front of the big hole Garen had created with his bare hands. What's strange was that Rose Dahm seemed to be in agony as tears were flowing out from AG's eyes. AG was shivering as if he recalled something very sad.

"I didn't know… never thought of…" AG looked contradictorily sad as he looked at Rose Dahm with a strange gaze. There were love, sadness, and pain in his gaze.

"Love? What is with this development?" Garen frowned as he muttered while pulling Cohen to a corner, waiting quietly.

"I… I have some information…" Cohen whispered slowly.

"Garen looked at him, reached out his hand and tapped onto his neck to temporarily seal Cohen's sense towards pain.

"Let's hear it?"

His expression immediately changed as he stopped feeling pain instantaneously. Disbelief with what he just experienced, he tried to move his hands and leg but to no avail, as if his limbs did not belong to him. He couldn't do anything once he realized what happened.

"Rose Dahm is the descendant of AG…"

"?" Garen didn't even how to react to it. They're trying to kill each other just a moment ago and now they're families?"

"Rose Dahm and his siblings believe that the Best Book Page has corrupted AG. Hence the reason why they had stolen the book. He was trying to use the sealed knowledge inside purely as a tool. However, AG couldn't comprehend it as he views the book page as his strongest source of energy. He risked his life to obtain it and it was his most precious treasure." Cohen spewed everything out.

"I don't care if you're his cousin. I have seen the killing intent in AG's gaze." Garen butted in.

"No way…?" Cohen's eye widened.

Garen quietened down for a moment as he attempted to sense the number of potential points inside the Stone Clock of Fortune. He estimated that a bottle had about five points, which was more than he expected. Based on this calculation, if every bottle was similar to each other, then he should have twenty-five more points with the other five bottles. It was more than he had anticipated.

He pondered for a moment and shouted towards AG.

"AG, how do I contact you in the future?"

AG turned around and looked at Garen and Cohen, who was in his grasp, strangely.

"Of course through the telephone? My phone number is 8224-657930****." While he didn't say out the last four digit, the voice was directly transferred into Garen's ears.

Garen memorized it instantaneously and nodded towards AG.

Although it seemed weird that an ancient old witch was able to use a satellite phone, everything seemed possible for this guy.

Garen felt that the witches and witch doctor he encountered during this expedition were weird as their relationships were a mess.

With Cohen in his hand, he stopped pursuing the Best Book Page as the most important he should obtain right now was the foundation of energy AG possessed and the Page was not something that might not benefit him at all.

Furthermore, He had the Stone Clock of Fortune and Cohen as a bait. Garen planned to deal with the hidden Levi immediately.

That guy wasn't willing to meet him in person and had been killing his patrols from afar.

The elite members went out to try and search for him but to no avail. His hiding ability was out of this world.

As he revealed his location via the walkie-talkie, Garen brought Cohen to the left side of the tunnel.

It was pitch black. He placed down the walkie-talkie and punched upward.

Boom!!

Huge chunks of stones and rubbles were ejected outwards as a beam of light shone down.

A huge hole spanning a meter wide appeared before them.

A few huge stones fall down but Garen casually pushed them away as the stones were pushed into the stonewalls like canons.

Cohen gulped as he saw in horror. He was afraid that the stone would crash into him if Garen were to be careless. It was a force that would instantly kill him!

Without saying any word, Garen carried Cohen and jumped out of the hole swiftly. He then landed on the right side of the hole.

It was a very spacious field with wilted yellow and green leaves rustling as the wind blew. A few brown antelopes which were frightened by their appearance were running away.

The sky was incredibly blue and the sun rays were red hot.

The giant sun on the horizon far away looked like a huge orange balloon.

Garen was carrying Cohen across the greenish yellow field as he moved in a certain direction at great speed.

Soon, the sound of a car engine could be heard up front and a huge group of cars appeared before them.

Garen threw Cohen on the ground as he welcomed the team.

"Captain!" Baldy was wrapped like a mummy. He was the first one to get down from the car as he carried a black package.

"I didn't disappoint you!" Baldy said as he stood in front of Garen with his back straight. Although his some part of his white bandages were seeping with blood, he didn't mind at the very least.

Garen took the package in his hand and looked inside. There were five identical white porcelain bottles.

He patted Baldy's shoulder as he nodded with a smile.

"Not bad."

"Captain, Jay has found Levi's trace and he was pursuing him alone. Perhaps they are even fighting against each other as of this moment." A black haired ponytail woman walked towards him and said softly.

"Let's head over there together." Garen's eye turned dim as he recalled Levi. "Looks like it's time we capture this mouse…"

He turned his head and looked at Cohen.

"Bring that man along. Levi hates this person the most. Perhaps he can save me some trouble."

"Yes."

Two soldiers went over and picked up the strengthless Cohen.

"Be careful. I broke some of his bones and will die from hemorrhaging if not careful." Garen smiled as he ordered.

With the five small bottles in his hands, he felt a lot better.

The next thing he should do was to absorb six of these Stone Clock of Fortunes. He didn't expect that his subordinates would be so useful. Although he didn't know how Baldy obtained five of these Stone Clocks of Fortune, he could see that he had put in a lot of effort from his wounds.

As he cleared the issues here swiftly, he decided to enter the strength of that world for real.

Chapter 625: Arrangement 3

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On the yellow-green grass.

Tap-tap-tap…

The deep sound of gunshots continued on and on, rising and falling, once this side fell silent, the other side would ring out again.

The grass was battered up by the storm of interweaving bullets, some places had even lit up in flames, emitting black smoke.

"Split up and attack, try to keep them occupied."

A deep and powerful voice came from behind the soldiers manning the guns.

"Yes."

The gunshots stopped, and the soldiers split up into groups of five, scattering into several small teams and spanning out in all directions.

The commander had short white hair, and wore a slim-fitting black coat, his expression was cold, his eyes hidden under his slightly-black triangular sunglasses.

He had a strong body and a cold, calm aura, as though he was an icy-cold stone pillar standing on the spot, unbreakable, unmovable.

He was Garen’s most trusted helper other than Baldy, Jay Bencott.

This young man looked mature, but in truth he was not even twenty years old, and his true age was probably even younger than Garen. He was a child soldier since young, and his malnutrition made his hair turn white, the effects were irreversible no matter how well he lived as an adult.

After Garen had taught him the Shooting Shadow Secret Skill, he began to idolize Garen desperately, undergoing a series of tests, and truly becoming Garen’s trusted helper, joining the Nighthawks.

"He has no bullets, no food, and he does not dare to light a fire, or else the smoke will reveal his tracks." A bespectacled female officer beside Jay said softly.

"I exchanged a shot with him, but sadly for him I’m wearing a bulletproof vest, while he isn’t. There was the smell of blood, he can’t get too far." Jay nodded.

As he spoke, he opened the inner flap of his coat, and took out a bunch of small components from inside with a familiar hand, and then he rapidly constructed the components, quickly building a white handgun with a scope in his hand.

Activating the handgun, Jay’s hand gave a jolt.

Bam!!

A shot abruptly exploded into an empty space in the grass to their right. An earth-yellow figure leaped out of there all of a sudden, and took off in a run.

Jay did not have any time to say anything else, and chased after him.

The gun in his hand kept shooting as he ran.

Bang bang bang!

Each bullet hit the ground beneath the person’s feet accurately, but every shot missed by a hair, the second before he could steady his aim, that person could defy the laws of momentum and abruptly bounce away, without any sense of rhythm whatsoever.

"Reflexive dodging?" Jay smiled coldly. Abruptly he pulled out another white handgun from his waist.

Instantly, there was twice the number of bullets.

Bam!!

A ball of fire exploded in front of the person, it was a hand grenade!

Some of the soldiers had roughly predicted which direction they would go, and tossed a hand grenade there.

Both of them paused for a second as a result of the jolt from the explosion, then they rolled towards the left at almost exactly the same time.

There was the rattle of several more shots underneath that person, sending up a spray of yellow dirt.

And the place Jay had been standing at erupted abruptly, there was actually a landmine hidden there.

The gunshots stopped, the smog of grass and dirt temporarily blocking off visibility of this place. The soldiers in the distance stopped firing as they were afraid of hitting Jay by accident, they had tried this manner of sweeping shot many times before, it wasted a lot of bullets and was never effective.

The two of them hid in the smoke and grass, both hidden from the other.

Jay held his left arm, it was completely charred black, the blast had clipped his arm. He held a gun with one hand, a slight sheen of sweat on his forehead.

Lightly, he hooked up a small stone with his foot, and applied some strength to it.

The stone flew up instantly, landing in the grass about a meter away.

Smack.

The sound was extremely small, almost lost in the sound of the wind.

Bang!

Jay abruptly moved to the right, a cloud of yellow dirt exploded exactly where he had been, it was the splash from the impact of bullets.

"They can estimate my location just by the backtracking from the sound and direction of the stone’s landing?"

A hint of battle-thirst appeared in his eyes.

"It’s been a long time since I’ve encountered such powerful opponent…"

His handgun shook, and nodded three times.

Bang bang bang!

In the grass that had been shot at just now, neither of the other two places that he had guessed had any traces of movement, which evidently meant he had not caught his opponent’s tail.

Jay fired off a shot and decisively changed location, there was a red cross appearing lightly in his right eye, it seemed to be a bulging cross-shaped vein, but it also looked like a blurred mark.

This cross-shaped mark just happened to be in the middle of his pupil.

This was the Shooting Shadow Secret Skill, after activating the Shooting Shadow, his senses, agility, and reflexes were so much higher than normal. Even the tiniest of movements around him could not evade him.

But he had a feeling that his opponent was not that much weaker than him, even after activating the secret skill, he still could not accurately gauge his opponent’s movements.

Somersaulting and standing up abruptly, he instantly fired off a series of shots.

Bang bang bang bang bang bang!!

The gunshots did not stop, and there was a grunt hidden among them.

"Got you!" The corners of Jay’s lips curved. He retreated backward rapidly, the red cross in his eyes disappearing instantly.

The large team behind him was ready in formation.

Several mobile cannons were locked and loaded.

In that instant, the cannons spewed out clouds of white smoke, and there were the dull sounds of something hitting the ground.

At almost the same time, on a grassy hill nearby, there was an explosion of bright fire light, and waves of dirt flew high into the air.

"Target identified, exterminate on the spot." Jay lay down low, hidden, and gave orders directly into the communicative earpiece of his Hawkeye sunglasses.

"Understood."

"Pay attention, I shot him, activate the tracking chip in the bullet right now, he can’t escape." Jay told them.

"We’re already identifying the signals, please leave it to us."

"Jay, how’s the situation?" The voice in the earpiece changed suddenly, becoming Garen’s low and calm voice.

"I got Levi with my tracking bullet, he can’t escape." The corners of Jay’s lips curved, and he replied softly. "Please leave it to us, our people are already identifying the signals, coupled with the satellite surveillance, he…"

"Watch out!!" A soldier knocked him away abruptly.

There was a loud and piercing wail, then barroom!

In the scarlet firelight, that soldier and Jay were both sent flying.

"It’s a helicopter! An armed helicopter! Careful!!" Only then was there a yell in his earpiece.

Jay’s head was spinning, as he crawled up from the ground.

He could just see three black helicopters appear out of nowhere in the sky nearby, he had no idea how long they had been there, each helicopter was three times as large as regular helicopters, covered from tip to tail in cannons, just like a honeycomb. There were also two mid-air machine guns attached to each side of the helicopters. Through the glass, they could see that the people inside the helicopters were controlling the guns to aim their way.

They were all wearing white uniforms, which probably meant they came from one organization.

"Take cover! Take cover!!" A loud voice yelled.

"Where are the Firethorns!? Destroy them!" Jay yanked the Hawkeye and roared.

Whoosh whoosh!

Two missiles flew towards the two helicopters, leaving a trail of smoke behind them.

One was hit by a bullet, exploding in mid-air, and the other accurately hit one of the helicopters.

Boom!!

A cloud of red flames erupted in mid-air, the middle of the helicopter was shot into a fireball, the whole helicopter tilted down and crashed into the ground, finally bursting with a loud explosion.

"Let me!" Jay ran back into the formation quickly, grabbing an anti-materiel rifle handed to him by a soldier. He fell belly-first onto the ground and propped up the gun, the red cross appearing in his eyes once more.

The rifle’s barrel moved slightly, the wind resistance, deflection, distance, any obstacles, all of these factors and statistics flowed past Jay’s heart.

He instantly locked down his aim.

Bang!

There was a dull sound from the barrel of the gun.

In the distance, a helicopter exploded on cue. It instantly exploded into a fireball in mid-air, and spun as it crashed down.

Its oil tank had been pierced straight through.

There was one helicopter left.

But by then it was too late, the last helicopter seemed to have been shocked, pouring out all of its missiles at once, six whole missiles whistled through the wind as they shot in all directions, and the machine guns also began to shoot in madly all directions.

The barrage made the soldiers around them unable to look up for some time, some were hit by the shots, their bodies breaking into two.

Faced with this sort of war weapon, unless you had an anti-materiel and powerful weapon, most guns were totally useless against it, you had no choice but to hunker down and take the hits.

"Take cover! Take cover!!"

Just then, a missile abruptly flew at them from another patch of grass, drawing out a straight path and crashing right into the helicopter.

Boom!!

The last helicopter also exploded into a fireball, crashing to the ground.

In the distance, Garen put down the bazooka on his shoulder, he was standing on a camouflage jeep driving toward them at high speed, there was a long motorcade behind him, filled to the brim with many soldiers and mercenaries armed to the teeth.

Baldy stood to Garen’s right, and the girl with the ponytail stood at his left, looking like his guards.

The men on the two sides gathered rapidly, and by then there was already thick smoke and wildfires all over the grass. Levi’s shadow had disappeared from view a long time ago.

"Boss, I put a tracking bullet in him, he can’t get far!" Jay greeted Garen respectfully with a bow.

"Everybody, comb the area for him!" Garen waved his hand, and all the vehicles behind him stopped, the groups of men began to jump off, the gun-toting elites instructing them to search in all directions.

"Give everyone a search order every ten minutes." Garen looked at the girl with the black ponytail, and the latter nodded.

Glancing at the three helicopters that had crashed in the distance.

"Those are all Russian-made heavy duty helicopters, how many did you encounter just now, Baldy?"

"Five, and more than ten elite special forces soldiers, they were troublesome. There were all mine-planting and counter-surveillance experts among them." Garen replied in a low voice.

"Thank you for your trouble." Garen nodded, "Do you know what faction they’re with?"

"They’re with White Phoenix, the Primary Colors are very unhappy with how we stopped the operation last time, they think we broke the rules they set, so they have designated us Nighthawks as a kill target, I think they were the ones who sent these teams." Baldy introduced them simply, the Primary Colors’ White Phoenix used to be his old employers, so naturally he would still be familiar with them now.

"They’re with White Phoenix?" Garen’s eyes narrowed. "That is a huge thing…"

White Phoenix was one of the Primary Colors’ combat branches, they had a very established mercenary hiring system, and they even had some extreme and mysterious power supporting them from behind, their background was too deep to fathom.

"We can give them a little lesson, but it’d be enough to target White Phoenix alone, we shouldn’t declare war on them just yet." Garen was wary of the Blood Breed’s high-level power. After experiencing part of the witches’ high-level power, he maintained a certain sense of threat from this strange and mysterious power system.

This system was completely unlike the knowledge he had studied before. He could barely even detect and defend against them.

Chapter 626: Arrangement 4

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Before completely understanding their system, he should not brashly declare war on them. Garen’s side was not as large in scale as the Primary Colors, aside from the thousands of elite peak-level mercenaries and assassins, the Primary Colors also had immense military might and scientific power, all of which ordinary people could not defend against. Plus, it was highly likely that they had peak-level unnatural power behind them as well.

Garen did not believe that such a large group would not have a powerful background behind them, if they did not, they probably would have swallowed whole a long time ago.

"What should we do?" Jay was not at all scared of the Primary Colors’ formidable power. He always obeyed Garen’s orders unhesitatingly.

Baldy and the black-haired girl, on the other hand, looked worried.

"I’ll handle this matter…" Garen said calmly. This was the time to let that old guy contribute a little, it could also be a showcase of his power, if he wanted to join forces with him, that bit of power from before was not enough to pass.

Garen did not want to see his teammates killed off first during a real battle, leaving himself outnumbered.

If the other person could not even teach a modern mercenary group a little lesson, then he had to reconsider whether it was worth accepting this person as an ally.

"Found him, Levi!" The ponytailed girl said suddenly.

"Chase him."

Kenna was pulled out soon enough, he sat obediently beside Garen like a little chick, watching him as he called that old fellow.

Beside him, Garen told AG what he wanted, hoping that he could show some of his sincerity and qualifications as a prospective ally.

"No problem, this is a simple matter." AG agreed quite easily. He understood as well, facing an organization without unnatural power was very simple and easy, even Garen could do it without difficulty.

He could sense that Garen had a terrifying aura, evil and powerful. This aura and this power, none of it was released just now.

"We got the Best Book Page, do you want to see it?" AG continued.

"That’s yours now, if you’re willing, I do want to borrow it for a look." Naturally Garen replied, he was very interested in the thing that looked very high class.

"The next time we meet, then."

"Okay." Hanging up, Garen accepted the change of gloves that his subordinate offered him, his gloves were basically falling apart from the friction when he was underground, and the skin on his arm was almost revealed. And this was when he actually paid attention to protecting these gloves, if it was someone else who did not have his level of control over his power, these gloves would not even last one punch.

"Levi’s appeared." Baldy reminded him in a low voice.

"Oh?" Garen raised his head and looked forward, he actually saw someone raising his hands up straight, standing right in front of the motorcade. Two soldiers walked over to press his arms down, and two pointed at him with their guns, escorting him to the car.

"Pretty gutsy. Does he want to talk to me directly?" Garen smiled slightly, opened the car door and jumped out to greet him, the other elites also follow him out of the car, sticking close behind him.

Levi’s expression looked calm, he did not seem scared or panicked in the slightest. He just had his arms pressed behind his back, walking up to them wordlessly.

"Sir, he says he wants to talk directly to you." One of the mercenaries said loudly.

"Release him." Garen waved his hand, "In front of me, he cannot resist."

When the soldiers heard that, they did not hesitate, letting go of Levi’s restraints immediately, and walking to the side to form a circle surrounding him. But their gazes were still fixed intently on Levi, full of wariness.

Garen looked this person up and down.

His military uniform was falling apart, but it was still recognizable as the uniform of the Nighthawks’ outer circle mercenaries, his face was covered in stubble, his skin coarse, dry and cracked, there was a cut on his lip, and a white bandage wrapped around his left arm.

Most uniquely, the large majority of his face was covered by his hair and beard, his body filthy, so he looked just like a savage.

But the aura he was giving off was smart and decisive.

"What do you want to say?" Garen looked at this person with interest. "You killed more than ten of my men, do you think I’ll spare you?"

"Those were just normal outer circle soldiers, you can recruit any number of them whenever you want, and they have no sense of loyalty to speak off." Levi’s voice was very magnetic, just like television hosts, giving off a gentle and soft sense of comfort, while being calm and collected.

"Even so, you collected so many people and so much power to raid my Nighthawk group, causing casualties and deaths, Bady even lost an eye. Don’t tell me you don’t owe me that much?" Garen said mildly.

"That was just an accident." Levi moved his arms and shoulders, "I was gathering up all the hotshots from all the factions, and suddenly the Nighthawks just rushed in and tried to control all the masterminds, so naturally we’d end up enemies."

"Do you think that explanation would make me spare your life?" Garen smiled slightly.

"Of course not." Levi smiled bitterly, "The truth is, even if you don’t kill me, I won’t be able to live for long. Just now, I was bitten by an African black-striped, so I probably have about half an hour left to live."

Only then did the smile on Garen’s face fade slowly, the African black-striped was a snake unique to this world, its venom was untreatable, a purely destructive venom. Even the most recently invented antivenoms needed to be injected beforehand for them to work, and it would be too late to apply them after one was bitten. The time taken for the antivenom to take effect was not as fast as the time taken for the snake venom to kill him.

"In that case, why are you here?"

"I still have a daughter, she doesn’t know that I do such dangerous things, she always thought I was just a regular international tradesman."

"What does that have to do with me?" Garen said nonchalantly.

"I’ll tell you a secret, sir, and in exchange I humbly ask that you help me to protect her." Levi hesitated, "I have no choice, I have no friends I trust enough. If I die, she will be swallowed whole by my enemies. And most importantly, she’s very pretty, and very young. If she can follow by your side, I believe that at the very least, she’ll live."

"What a cruel man." Garen laughed, "I have all the information about you, that daughter of yours is only twelve, and you are willing to hand her to me, someone you don’t know anything about. Aren’t you worried that she might end up even worse off in my hands?"

"I won’t misjudge someone. You do not hide your personality at all, sir, that pride and arrogance is not something a normal person can bluff through. And the truly prideful people will not easily go back on their promises." Levi was indirectly flattering Garen.

"Her mother does not come from a regular family either, but it’s just a very normal family business, it has nothing to do with these grey or black areas. They obey the law, and have a good reputation. She doesn’t really understand all these things I’ve been doing, but she never liked them. So she can’t protect Aileen."

"Are you so sure that I’d agree?" Garen retorted.

"I’m just making a gamble." Levi shrugged, "That secret has to do with the Black Uniform Organization’s biggest secrets. This is also the main reason why I can be so far ahead of the regular elite soldiers."

"Oh? What is it?" Garen was instantly interested. He waved his hand, getting his surrounding subordinates to give them some distance.

"Regarding the Stone Clock of Fortune, the secret about the layer of mysterious power on it…" Levi’s voice was as soft as a mosquito’s hum, but with Garen’s hearing, he could still clearly hear what Levi was saying.

Finally, Garen’s heart gave a heavy jolt.

He knew, that the power Levi was talking about, should be the potential power he had always been using.

"How can you use it? That power?" Garen’s lips moved slightly, his voice transmitting straight into Levi’s ears.

Levi looked at him in surprise, seemingly taken aback by how fast he accepted it. "We have a secret method to absorb this power and keep it within our bodies, it can rapidly regenerate stamina, heal wounds, increase the rate of new cell production, and the more we absorb it, the more we use it, the stronger the human body gets, the stronger our spirit grows. We firmly believe, that this might be the brand new path for humans to reach the next stage of evolution."

He paused, "If you are willing to trade with me, I will give you this secret method, as well as the ancient relics and artifacts that the Black Uniform Organization had collected over the years."

But Garen was currently in utter shock, the way Levi said he used the power was exactly the same effect he had when adding his potential points to the Vitality attribute. But he observed the condition inside Levi’s body with his senses for a bit, and found that this power seemed to be helpless against the venom, instead it continuously swam through his body like a living thing.

In the Totem World, he had guessed that the potential value was a form of soul power, and if it really was so.

The soul could be explained as the human consciousness to a certain extent, humans had a consciousness and a subconsciousness, the consciousness dictated their everyday lives. Meanwhile, the subconsciousness was in charge of delegating the human body’s resources, gathering and providing energy where the body needed it.

If the potential value was a form of soul power, then it was perfectly capable of strengthening the consciousness and the subconsciousness, increasing the speed of reflexes and nerves, strengthening the immune system and energy regeneration, and other such overall increases to the body’s stats.

"There’s a side effect, right?" Garen asked suddenly.

Levi nodded, perfectly honest.

"Of course, but it’s nothing too serious. The side effects are, after absorbing that power from the ancient relics and artifacts, your body will have a different quality, and most of these qualities will have a detrimental effect on the body to some effect, creating some strange hobbies, habits, or minor illnesses."

Garen could guess, that this should be the biggest difference between them and himself, he had that Ability to filter off the impurities in the potential value, such that he had no side effects at all, while these people could only absorb them roughly, eating up all the good and the bad, so naturally there would be problems.

But he was indeed very interested in the filtering system his own Ability had, this was an opportunity, a chance to explore the roots of his own Ability. Perhaps he could understand how his pulse and nerve pathways worked by examining their secret method.

"The deal is done."

He looked at the man in front of him, and finally agreed.

Chapter 627: Involved 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

A month later…

"If time was a sharp scimitar, then who is the owner behind the scimitar?"

AG half-kneeled in a wide sand dune, the golden sand flowing through his fingers, like fine golden gravel.

"What are you trying to say?"

Garen stood quietly behind him, his arms crossed in front of his chest, wearing sunglasses to shield off the light.

"I’m just thinking about it." AG shook his head, staring at an oasis in the middle of the golden desert, that was the White Phoenix’s headquarters here in Africa. It looked deserted here, but they just had to walk several meters forward, and there would be an alarm from the sand dunes ahead all to the way to the White Phoenix HQ, telling them that there was an intruder in their ranks.

The hundred or so elite fighters stationed inside would also pour out, and the traps hidden everywhere would instantly shoot everywhere.

"The security here is very tight." Garen said softly. "What do you plan to do? Within less than a minute, the whole base will become a fully-armed porcupine."

AG smiled mysteriously. "Faced with an immobile target like this, we have too many ways to completely finish them off."

"Oh?" Garen frowned, "If we kill them all, the effect might be a bit severe." He did not want to make enemies of the White Phoenix just yet.

"No problem. The White Phoenix is huge in scale, they have more than a couple of enemies." AG said with a laugh.

Garen’s eyes narrowed, and he turned around instantly.

A tall woman dressed fully in white had appeared behind him without him noticing.

This woman stood quietly behind the two of them, wearing a set of long, figure-fitting white shirt and trousers, her wavy black hair falling over her shoulders, but she wore a white mask on her face, hiding the half of her face beneath her nose.

"AG, do you really plan to make a move against the Primary Colors?" The woman’s voice was exceedingly normal, like a regular salesgirl in a shop, not special in any way.

But Garen and AG did not dare to let their guard down around her.

"Nasira, how long has it been?" AG stood up, "A hundred years, or two? I remember that time when I met you at the councilman’s banquet…"

"That was already a long, long time ago." The woman interrupted him. "If it wasn’t for the fact that you taught me way back then, I really would want to tear you to pieces right now."

"You are as violent as ever…" AG smiled kindly.

"To lure an eight-year-old little girl into the abyss of physical pleasures, back then you truly were despicable." The woman said icily.

"Don’t be so heartless, we lived together for over eighty years, you know." AG said with a gentle smile.

"For eighty years I lived like I was in hell! You useless piece of shit that can only use your fingers!" The woman was getting angrier.

Beside them, Garen was starting to get a headache, AG was considered a decent collaborator, once he decided to make a move, he instantly started arranging things with him, and they came here directly, ready to go.

But his own messed-up personal relationships were the most exasperating. He had all sorts of ridiculous relationships with women, and his emotional life was more than complicated, and now it seemed that he was born sexually inept, he really could be a star in his own romantic soap opera.

Garen did not want to bother with AG’s personal life.

"Let’s begin as soon as possible, I still want to go back to America for something." He hastened them.

"Who is he?" The woman glanced at Garen, her gaze instantly fixing onto his gloved arms.

"Didn’t anyone teach you to have manners when meeting strangers?" Garen exercised his fist, his eyes narrowing.

"Manners? How dare you speak to me in such a tone!" A hint of violence flashed through the woman’s eyes, "Anyone who walks with AG, is probably also a piece of trash!"

"You uneducated bastard!"

Boom!

Before the words even finished ringing, a powerful energy erupted from Garen’s body, and pressed down hard on the woman’s body, almost as though it was a solid thing.

It seemed to be a wave of air, but the sands around them showed no signs of being blown away.

Bam!

Only the woman herself took three loud steps back, her face reddening with blood, before she could steady her footing.

"AG! I want to kill him!!" The woman instantly screamed, as though she was humiliated beyond belief. Her hair began to dance madly like a nest of snakes.

Garen chucked coldly, and stomped his right foot.

With a bang, many grains of sand shot towards the woman like bullets, as though instantly forming a storm of bullets, falling down from everywhere, unstoppable.

It was as though Garen had stomped up a yellow mist that rushed at the woman.

The woman screamed, and actually dashed forward, her waist twisting like an agile snake. She actually pierced through the veil of sand, rushing straight for Garen.

"That’s enough!"

AG’s voice instantly jolted towards them, like an unbreakable glass window, blocking between the two of them decisively. It seemed to a trick of the senses, making both of them stop instinctively.

"Nasira, don’t be rash. He’s just an ally of mine." AG told the woman gently.

"Your body type seems to be somewhat different?" Garen narrowed his eyes and looked at the woman, a hint of contempt on his lips, "No wonder you’re so fearless. An absorbent body type, huh? I just need one hand to kill you."

As soon as he spoke, the woman’s expression changed slightly.

Her body type was indeed her greatest advantage, it was her greatest guarantee when facing all sorts of unnatural power, but now this man had identified it so easily.

An absorbent body type plus immensely powerful close combat techniques, as well as gunslinging skills, all of these made her fearless even when facing enemies with unnatural power. Add that to her powerful background, and Nasira always thought that the so-called strong witches that she had meant so far were all just exaggerated paper tigers, she just had to poke them with a finger to make them collapse.

But this time, this man…

For the first time ever, she swallowed the words on the tip of her tongue, and said no more.

The three of them fell quiet again.

Despite the ruckus on this side, the White Phoenix did not seem to notice anything at all. Those on patrol kept patrolling, those on duty kept on with their duty, some cars entered and left the base, following the only way in.

There was always at least satellite watching over this place at all times, but somehow no one seemed to have noticed these three people here, even after so long.

AG turned around, looking at the White Phoenix base that took up this whole oasis.

"Their real headquarters are actually underground, it’s a lot bigger than this bit on the surface.

"What do you plan to do?" Garen asked quietly, ignoring the crazy woman.

"Underground, we just need to make a few adjustments…" AG chuckled mysteriously.

He opened his hand, there was a cloud of fine golden sand on his palm.

The wind seemed to be getting stronger, blowing in gusts, sending their clothes billowing up and down.

Garen shook the windbreaker he wore, putting his hands into his pockets, quietly sensing the tiniest changes in his surroundings.

He had not used any of the potential value he absorbed from the Stone Clock of Fortune, because he was waiting for AG over here to obtain the new power system, perhaps it might be of use to him.

Right now he was still musing over the secret method he had obtained from Levi, the secret method to absorb potential points.

When he came back to the present, AG in front of him seemed to be silently waiting for something.

After a long time, he suddenly moved.

The palm holding the grains of sand turned slightly, and the sand on his palm began to spill, slipping off, and forming a straight golden line of sand as it fell to the ground.

Strangely, it seemed as though this line of sand would never finish flowing, it kept on tilting and spilling, already forming a tall hill of sand on the ground, but there was still a pinch of sand in AG’s palm.

"See, this is the power of the earth…" AG smiled.

All of a sudden.

The line of sand in his hand bulged out, and fell to the ground as though it was wrapped around a lead ball, crashing into the ground.

Bam!

The earth gave a hard jolt.

Wooo~! Wooo~! Wooo~!

There was a piercing siren from the White Phoenix base in the distance, wave after wave.

The people inside were confused, as the alarm kept echoing, the guards everywhere who were already wary began to receive reports, and instantly their expressions changed, as they all ran into the base.

AG was still smiling, and a clear spherical object flowed out of the line of sand in his hand once more, crashing hard onto the pile of sand underneath.

Bamm!!

The ground jolted yet again, and it was as though something had shattered and collapsed, there was a deep rumbling under their feet.

"Just a tiny bit of power, can trigger an unbelievably vast strength." AG said softly, looking at Garen and the woman.

Clap clap clap clap…

Garen smiled, and began to applaud.

"What a fascinating use of chain reactions, so you were counting the nodes this whole time, and you used them to trigger the chain reactions."

"Of course. This is also a method to use our power." AG nodded with a smile.

"Hmph." The woman in white harrumphed coldly, not surprised in the slightest.

"Let’s go." The sand in the middle of AG’s palm finally ran out.

The three of them did not even look at the White Phoenix base, Garen did not know how the other two interpreted the situation, but he could already smell the faint odor of blood coming from the ground underneath his feet…

His exceptional five senses allowed him to clearly feel that whenever the sand in AG’s hand crashed down in a clump, a large chunk of the White Phoenix’s underground base would collapse. This was an extremely intricate mysterious power, it was as though he was playing with dominos, one after the other, each force exponentially magnified, and applied directly to the essential points of the massive underground base.

Garen knew that this was AG showing off how powerful he was.

This user of ancient power that seemed like an ancient undead monster in the eyes of others, he had a strength that could be used almost anywhere. He was that living legend.

The three of them turned back, walking to a jeep parked nearby behind them, then they all got onto the jeep and took their seats.

Strangely, the jeep did not seem bothered about sand getting into it, it took a turn, and rapidly left into the distance, the tire tracks rapidly covered by the sandstorm.

The White Phoenix behind them rumbled loudly.

Everything on the ground that had been part of the base, crashed down hard, sinking deep into the sand.

A huge black hole appeared where the base had been, and the vast amounts of yellow sand around it flowed into it endlessly, slowly burying the houses and buildings, the vehicles and the people.

Chapter 628: Involved 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After returning from the White Phoenix base, and separating from AG and Nasira, Garen returned straight to where the Nighthawks were based, a privately-owned estate in the wilderness.

It was several tens of kilometers away from the city, there was the Nighthawks’ surveillance equipment installed everywhere, and there were guards on duty twenty-four hours a day, so it was definitely safe.

In a wide room, Garen swept everything out, leaving a completely empty room, with nothing save the floorboards and the walls.

It was about a dozen meters long and wide, and felt especially vast.

That night, there were the faint sounds of the mercenaries telling tall tales or playing cards, while others snored loudly as they slept.

There also seemed to be the sounds of engines blaring, other than the large-scale missions, the Nighthawks also accepted small missions here and there, like a bodyguard escort service, going along for negotiations and so on. These missions were safe and easy, when normal people saw their troop appear, and laid eyes on that logo, they would all choose not to make enemies of the Nighthawks. Even if the situation in South Africa was complicated right now, some small countries and governments toppling overnight, power struggles all over the place and all the time, military revolts a dime a dozen.

But when anyone saw the logo of the Nighthawks, they still would not choose to declare war on them. The reputation of the number one mercenary army in South Africa was still very influential, this name was built on thousands or even tens of thousands of corpses, it did not come from nowhere.

As soon as Garen made a move, he wiped out the Black Knife’s main leaders, and then chased Levi over thousands of miles, capturing Kenna, destroying the White Phoenix’s support and maintenance teams.

This series of victories had instantly shaken the mercenary scene in the whole of Africa, some people were already calling him the Nighthawk King behind his back, because not long after the White Phoenix fell prey to his hand, before the teams there could even gather and react, the White Phoenix’s base somehow met with an earthquake, the whole underground collapsing, with a large number of casualties and deaths.

Some people guessed that this was no coincidence, and could very well be man-made. But no one believed them.

The final result was that the White Phoenix had no time to bother with Garen’s matter anymore, now that the branch had encountered such a problem, incurring heavy losses, the main question was how would they report it to the Primary Colors HQ.

One week after returning, Garen’s life had returned the same old routine, waking up in the morning for his morning exercises, reading books in the noon, listening to some music, contacting his parents and friends, and going out in the afternoon, buying souvenirs everywhere like a normal tourist, eating good food. At night, he would study that secret method he had just gotten his hands on.

As for the Stone Clock of Fortune, after Garen absorbed all of the mysterious power on it, he just tossed it to the Nighthawks, giving it to their long-time auction partner for auctioning off some day.

Not just that, Garen even sent Jay to receive the Black Uniform Organization’s property that Levi had left to him.

Although the whole Black Uniform Organization had been utterly destroyed by the Nighthawks, their most important property, fortunes, and connections were all stored under cipher in international banks, and they required him to send someone there to retrieve them. All of this needed time.

Garen was still waiting for the relics and antiques that the Black Uniform Organization had collected over the years, with the information collected by such an organization over the years, he might be able to find the true process and principles behind these relics producing potential value.

"By the time the White Phoenix realize that AG was the root of the problem, they’d probably grow wary as well. However… AG’s so-called small lesson was a bit too big, is he trying to force me into his camp?" Garen’s hands were tapping in rhythm, his fingers laced lightly and placed in front of him, as though he was holding a heart in his hand, pulsing in time.

His breathing was fast at times, slow at others, sometimes long, and sometimes strangely short.

And as his breathing changed, the beating of the heart in his chest seemed to be the opposite of the beating in his hands, when this side rested the other side beat, and when this side beat, the other side rested. Both together formed a continuous thumping.

As the beating continued endlessly, the cool air in Garen’s body began to travel slowly, like a thin ice-cold snake, constantly swimming around his organs, as though swimming through his thoracic cavity.

This was how he absorbed potential value through the secret method, and not by using his own Ability to filter it, this was the most primal potential energy.

He wanted to use this method to experience the difference before and after filtering.

This breath was only a small part of the Stone Clock of Fortune, just a tiny part, and he used it as an experiment, absorbing it using the secret method. As for the rest, he absorbed them directly using his Ability, storing them away as potential points.

Just that was also the result of Garen’s own suppression, in that instant when he absorbed it, the Ability immediately took effect, trying to instinctively absorb the potential power, but Garen tried his best to control it.

"It has to be more impure… This power…" Once more feeling the potential value absorbed by the secret method slowly strengthening his organs, Garen closed his eyes slightly, feeling for the tiniest changes.

In one of the attribute panes in his field of vision, the Vitality attribute began to slowly blur and blink, it was evidently changing, but this change was extremely tiny, even the blurring was unusually minute.

"Using this secret method to strengthen myself involves too many impurities, too much is wasted in the process, and the efficiency of using my body’s own abilities to purify the power is too low, a lot of energy is lost with the impurities, compared to filtering it with my Ability, it is almost wholly ineffective."

Garen calculated, if the Ability could create ten potential points from twelve units of primal potential power, then to achieve the same result with the secret method would require at least a hundred units.

The difference was massive.

And the Ability produced pure potential points, they could even be added to his skills, just by precisely strengthening the comprehension and understanding components in his brain, this was not something the coarse secret method’s strengthening could hope to emulate.

The secret method’s strengthening could only strengthen his Vitality, and could not do anything more than that...

"A failed product… This level of guesswork is too low quality." Opening his eyes with some disappointment, Garen heaved a long breath, his breath mixed with an unpleasant odor, the smell of the impurities in his body being expelled.

"My power, when temporarily boosted, might be able to reach level six, but that power will only last for a split second, and when it’s over I will be heavily injured as well, requiring potential points to recover, this is far from my peak condition in the totem world. I still need many potential points to recover my body’s strength."

He glanced at the thin book on the floor next to him.

Those were the secret notes that AG had given him before leaving, it had some basic knowledge about unnatural power. It had detailed information about the high level Blood Breeds, the Death Apostles especially, describing their powers, levels, methods and the like in great detail.

Flipping through the pages, Garen scanned them with his eyes, and the lines of new words entered his line of vision clearly.

When AG wrote in his book, far away from here, this book in Garen’s hands could constantly update its own contents.

It could also be a method of secret communication between the two of them.

‘Among the levels of Blood Breeds, the upper level Blood Breeds are already enough to threaten you and me, we need to be wary of them. Death Apostles are far beyond our power, you must not interact with them simply, they are extremely hard to kill, and ever Death Apostle has a different yet powerful ability, they can be reborn in the body of any creature that has their blood. According to my conjecture, the one targeting you is very likely a Death Apostle.’

AG’s words appeared slowly, line by line.

Garen frowned slightly.

"Just how destructive is a Death Apostle’s power?" He took a ballpoint pen out of his pocket, and wrote quickly on the page. Strangely, as soon as he finished writing these words, AG’s notes and words continued to appear underneath.

‘They’re not purely material, they don’t have souls, we can’t understand this manner of living. But it’s exceedingly strange. There are different powers at the Death Apostle level, but what they have in common is that they all have immensely powerful strength, speed, and physicality. The strength physicality you demonstrated before has already achieved the pinnacle of humanity, but compared to them, you are still far beneath them.’ AG replied.

"Can you be more specific?" Garen frowned.

Multiply the foundations that you showed back then by several dozens, or even hundreds of times.’ AG responded, ‘There were Death Apostles who were hit head-on by an experimental laser cannon, and they still managed to walk out completely unscratched. Nobody knows where their limits are, no one has defeated them in the Material World. And no one has been able to kill them in the Material World.’

"The Material World?" Garen pursued the question, "Does that mean we can kill them in some other worlds?" He remembered the inner world in the Totem World.

‘They are the manipulators of consciousness, the kings of dreams, their true bodies are hidden in the Dream World, if you want to kill a Death Apostle, you need to find their true bodies on their dreams.’

"Dreams?" Garen instantly remembered that strange dream from that day.

‘In dreams, they can easily control the other person’s emotions, thoughts, triggering all sorts of negative feelings. All in order to achieve their goal. Sometimes they will also weave perfect dreams, fulfilling all of the dreamer’s desires, trapping them within in, if you yourself cannot sense that you are in a dream, then it is highly likely that your innermost secrets will be revealed. You must be careful…’ AG ended with an ellipsis, this usually meant he was ending the conversation.

Garen closed the book.

He was beginning to understand the terror of the Blood Breeds in this world. They were basically monsters living within dreams, if they really could not be killed the real world, then this would be his biggest disadvantage.

He was completely unfamiliar with dreams, he had no experience with them whatsoever, and as for whether or not resistance to this power had anything to do with the strength of one’s soul, Garen guessed that it would not be very relevant. He could tell just from that strange dream last time. The other party had easily triggered the fear in his heart, that completely inexplicable terror was something he had never experienced before.

All of his power was based in reality, he had completely no resistance against dreams.

"Witches can resist upper level Blood Breeds, that must mean, that the witches must have a similar resistance method." Garen hypothesized, "Looks like I have to learn the witches’ power system as soon as possible."

He did not want to become a Blood Breed, much less a cannon fodder vampire, as for an upper level Blood Breeds, all upper level Blood Breeds created their descendants, and could completely overpower their descendants’ spirits, so Garen had no intention of giving himself a superior out of nowhere.

He had better get along with the witches and become one of them first.

The unkillable Death Apostles, such a description had raised all of his alarms, if he could not find the opponent’s body in their dreams, that meant he could do absolutely nothing to them. This was already nothing to do with destructive power, they simply were not in the same territory.

"Tell me, about your training." Garen wrote on the book pages heavily.

‘You are in danger, whenever you enter the dream state of your own volition, you could be discovered and used by the enemy. Now is not yet the time.’ AG replied. The words that both of them written began to fade rapidly.

"Then when do I have to wait until?"

‘When the Blood Breed descends into chaos.’

Chapter 629: Prologue 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the largest city of England, Pruyn.

Between the streams of countless traffic, a group of masked men dressed in black carried their bulging backpacks and rushed into the headquarters of a bank by the street.

"On the ground! On the ground! All of you, on the ground!!" Bang bang!

The gunshots instantly triggered everyone’s nerves, the screams rang out immediately, but they were forced down again quickly, a few guards surrounded from the sides, and were just about to raise their guns, when they were instantly taken down with two more gunshots.

This scene triggered some more soft screams.

In the bank, there were still people withdrawing money for their work matters, as well as the staff at the counters, behind the thick bulletproof glass, the staff quickly and calmly rang the police alarm.

Wooo~~

A piercing siren wailed abruptly, and the whole bank’s shutters fell down quickly and automatically.

"Get rid of ‘em." The leader in the black mask did not panic in the slightest, saying to his partners in a low voice.

One of his partners sniggered, pulled something from his waist, and tossed it at the door.

That black thing instantly began to spin rapidly, emitting a faint red light, this red light somehow stopped the shutters from descending, and they began to go upwards instead.

The black-masked leader walked up to the counter, and faced down the staff inside.

Bam!

His hand instantly shattered the glass, the bulletproof was more than ten centimeters thick, but he still reached straight through it and grabbed the head of the staff member inside.

With a smack, the head exploded into a bloody mist in his hands.

"Aaaahhh!!" A female staff member beside them began screaming loudly, and in that instant, the terror spread.

Even bulletproof glass could not stop that person.

The smile could clearly be seen on the leader’s masked face.

"Come on… Come on… Hehehe, Cadytius… What should you do?"

The dozen or so black-masked people behind him began to install something in the bank, in a very disciplined manner.

After about a dozen minutes, the group rushed out of the bank, dashing into a dead-end alley off the street, and then seemed to vanish into thin air, never showing up again.

Barroom!!

With a deafening explosion, the headquarters of Pruyn’s largest British Billion Bank became a sea of flames just like that, and the whole bank building began to snap, starting from the first floor, tilting and falling down with a crash.

The bank building, several tens of meters tall, was like a dying giant, its enormous shadow falling down, and crashing heavily onto the streets beneath it.

Boom!

The shattered glass and walls sprayed everywhere, concrete meeting concrete, cars squashed flat, some people could not make it out in time, and were buried underneath the buildings, while others were just grazed, crawling and escaping while covered in blood, there were people around them yelling, others taking out their phones to call the emergency hotline, there were some who hid behind strong walls, and even more who scuttled around everywhere, madly.

***************

"On the 21st July, 2411, at noon, there was an earthshaking terror bomb attack at the crossroads of Lotus Street, in England’s largest city, Pruyn. The British Billion Bank’s headquarters collapsed due to an explosion, resulting in several dozen dead, and nearly a hundred injured. The incident is still under investigation, according to witness testimony, the terrorists all wore black masks and seemed to be very experienced, they seem to be extremely similar to the masterminds behind the Gatling gun incident last time…"

The news reporter on the television was reporting the latest developments in the case.

In a dim yellow luxurious suite of a hotel somewhere.

A shirtless blonde man with a black dragon tattoo on his arm was watching the news quietly, his golden hair fell over his shoulders, and he wore a white towel, his legs propped up on the coffee table in front of the sofa, his whole person handsome and lazy.

"Looks like they did well." A woman’s voice came from the bathroom nearby, gentle and magnetic.

"Looks like it." The blonde man nodded. "It’s about time the other side makes a move as well."

"How did you plan it?"

"Wasn’t it settled a long time ago?" The blonde man’s expression stiffened somewhat. "Even if he is my uncle, once he’s chosen a stand, he needs to pay for it."

There was instantly some laughter from the bathroom, the woman seemed to be very satisfied with it.

"This is just a little prologue." The man said softly.

The battle between the light party and the secret party was just beginning.

***********************

In the Calm Forest

A secret area that the light party had yet to discover.

This was the most high-tech underground base, black walls, black floors, black ceiling, it was all hard and smooth rock and stone, bright red lines carved onto the surfaces, monotonous and repetitive.

In a conference room in the very heart of the base, there were many men and women dressed in suits, sitting in their high-backed black chairs, they whispered among each other, discussing something in low voices, some had their brows knitted tensely, others were staring at the host, and yet others were listening to their phones, nodding their heads slightly.

The one sitting in the very center and the very front of the long table was a white-haired man in a black-striped suit, he was like an artist, his long white hair tied into a ponytail, his fingers laced and placed on the table in front of him, his expression stern and calm.

The low voices in discussion continued unbidden, but he seemed to be wholly unaware of them.

"A lot of things have happened recently, some of the secret party members have been acting strangely over there in America, and the witches are appearing more often now, I’ve already taken certain preventive measures." A bespectacled lady on the right spoke.

"The missing persons cases over here in Asia have not been settled yet, in fact, they seem to be escalating over the years, we don’t have enough upper-level people, so we hope that the headquarters can send us some special agents to help." A yellow-skinned middle-aged man said deeply.

"Hand in a proposal letter later." The white-haired man nodded, "Don’t be too extreme with the American preventive measures, try to be gentler, your priority is to ensure that the regular citizens are not disturbed or frightened."

"Understood."

"The Space Agency needs extra funds, we’ve had the newest, biggest breakthrough!" A fat white man hammered his fist onto the table and yelled loudly.

"Over the years, when have you not made a breakthrough?" Someone jeered.

"This year is different!" The fatty argued. "Funds! We need funds! As long as we have enough funds, we can immediately carry out our plan to modify the planets! It’s a matter of time before we get a second Earth!"

"How many years have you said that? Ten? Twenty? Or a hundred?" The icy lady sitting directly opposite him said contemptuously.

"You!!" The fatty raged.

"When it comes to space exploration, it does take a lot of funds, we can’t interfere too much with that, you can try to make deals with the representatives from different governments." The white-haired man shook his head and smiled.

"On England’s side… Did they cause that explosion?" The white-haired man looked at the last black-haired man of few words at the table.

"Yes, they were the subordinates of one of the secret party’s Three Moros, this was my oversight." The black-haired man lowered his head and apologized.

"The Three Moros…" The white-haired man tapped the table with his fingers, and in that moment, that tapping seemed to have some kind of magic, instantly silencing the whole conference room.

"Leave this matter to me." The black-haired man said in a low voice, "As for Lord Scarlet Moon’s side, may I request backup from him if necessary?"

"You may, if he’s willing." The white-haired man nodded. "We need to suppress this matter as soon as possible, to prevent creating even more panic."

"Understood."

"The standards of this year’s National Educational Selection are a little too high, it might be somewhat harder for us here to…" A new person spoke up, following the order of their seats.

"Regarding the selection test, this year’s standards were carefully calculated, we don’t need people who can’t meet the standards, and it just so happens that we need to be very selective with the evolutionaries for our neo-humans." The white-haired man raised his hand and gestured for the next one.

"Some of the island countries in the Atlantic Ocean discovered some supernatural phenomena that require investigation, it might trigger a volcano eruption or even a tsunami."

"Didn’t we send a special agent over for this last time?"

"Unfortunately, that secret agent is currently missing in action."

"Send Bartons, he’s bored with nothing to do right now. Tell him I told him to."

The proposals, suggestions, questions and cases were all raised one by one.

The secret party’s bomb incident was actually only a very small part of this.

But no one noticed that the glint of red light flashing through the lidded eyes of the black-haired man who was previously in charge of the secret party’s bomb case.

"The secret party has indeed not made any ‘drastic’ moves… They were just lightly sweeping away some of the bugs in England."

As for Lord Scarlet Moon, as the strongest fighter under the leader of the light party, Scarlet Moon was the number two Dearg Apostle, and should be treated properly…

What if the other two Lord Death Apostles joined forces?

The black-haired man’s lips curved slightly.

************************

‘There are four Death Apostles in total, it had always been that unchanging number. The light party has two, the secret party has one, and the last one is very mysterious, making it very hard to track this person down, so they’re considered neutral.’

Sitting in the plane on the way back, Garen quietly read that yellowed ancient scroll that AG had given him.

He sat in the Economy class, there was a bald geezer sitting next to him, who was in the middle of taking off his glasses to wipe them carefully. The young couple in front of him was laughing softly, and the two young girl behind him seemed to be flying international for the first time, they were chatting about it excitedly.

In such a normal and peaceful environment, Garen felt as though the ancient scroll in his hand was like a script from a fantasy movie, it did not feel real at all.

He seemed to be just a normal American university student, holding an imaginative movie script novel, and reading it carefully, as though the world inside it had absolutely nothing to do with him.

Garen tilted his head to glance at the geezer beside him, that guy gave him a friendly smile. Then he lowered his head, put on his glasses, picked up the airplane’s newspapers and began to read in his own time.

Garen returned to his senses, and continued to read the newly updated contents on the scroll.

Every so often, AG would update part of the contents of the scroll.

‘My ally told me, that the most mysterious Death Apostle might be making an appearance soon, this will destroy the balance between the light party and the secret party.’

‘But the light party has the number one Death Apostle, known as the strongest Death Apostle, Ashen Castine, and the number two Death Apostle, Scarlet Moon, is also there, their advantage won’t broken just like that.’

Garen flipped to the next page. Taking a ballpoint pen out of his pocket, he wrote on the pages slowly.

‘What is your ally?’

There was no reply from the other side, perhaps AG had not opened the book yet.

Garen was not particularly bothered, he continued reading the new information below.

‘Your first step is to remember or be aware that you’re dreaming, when you’re dreaming.’ AG seemed to be teaching him the first point of their power system.

‘For most people, the biggest problem is that they can’t tell that they’re dreaming while in their dreams, they will be completely defenseless and prone to spilling their greatest secrets under the influence of their environment. It’s like a place that seems completely quiet and empty, or a room that seems safe and secure, there are too many scams just like that.’

‘And the key for you right now, is with that Death Apostle who marked you, he is watching you at all times, so you must first be aware that you are being watched. He will exist in your dreams, once you enter your dreams, he will notice you. So you must take advantage of the moment when he is dragged into the Blood Breeds’ internal conflict, find the primer he left behind, and destroy it, only then can you escape his surveillance.’

Garen put down the book, deep in thought.

The Blood Breeds in this world were completely different from those in the previous world, these were evidently masters at manipulating wills, they swam the currents between reality and dreams, their lifespans almost endlessly long, they were an extremely strange yet powerful existence.

This power might yet bring him an unexpected reward.

Chapter 630: Prologue 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

On a village path in the English countryside.

On the grassy slope by the road, a pale-faced man was stumbling, his hand gripping his chest, continuously moving forward on the grass.

With every step he took, he would squeeze out yellow and black bullets out from between the fingers gripping his chest, these bullets rained onto the ground, tumbling in the grass, but there was no trace of blood whatsoever.

The wound between the man’s fingers was only a red slit, that slit was like a mouth, spitting out bullets every so often.

The hot sun shone down on him, but the man’s skin was obviously growing paler, a mark like a red moon could be clearly seen on his brow.

He turned around occasionally to look behind him, as though worried that someone was chasing him.

His lips were dry and cracked, like those of someone who had gone without water for a long time.

Psst-psst-psst!

In an instant, three black shadows appeared around him, forming a triangle and surrounding him.

The three shadows’ faces could not be seen, they seemed to three men in black hoods, the light around was them was somewhat blurred.

Without saying anything or making any sound at all, the three shadows appeared and rapidly pounced at the man in the middle, like three bolts of black lightning, but completely silent.

With a similar hiss, the man in the middle seemed to blur, and he instantly disappeared from the spot, with a blink, he appeared several dozens of meters away.

And those three shadows remained where they stood, their bodies tilting, before falling to the ground with several thumps, turning into three mounds of black ash, even their clothes completely turned to ash.

He watched the three men disintegrate on the ground. Then the man coughed a few times.

"You dare to harm Lord Scarlet Moon… All of you… should die! If the Blood Alliance hadn’t sealed it off… There must someone from the secret party beside Lord Ashen as well! I must think of a plan…"

The man’s figure quickly vanished into the woods.

*********************

On the airplane

Garen fell into deep thought.

His Slaughtering Hand secret technique originated from an Ancient Endor Demon King’s peak-level secret technique, it had the powerful ability to absorb life force, this ability was very effective even against normal Blood Breeds, he just did not know if it had any effect against Blood Breeds of the Death Apostle level.

Right now, he looked carefully at the current state of his secret techniques.

‘Garen Thomas.

‘Strength 2.8. Agility 2.7. Vitality 2.9. Intelligence 2.4. Potential 1558%. Soul Limit 30.

‘Soul Seed: Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique.’

‘Violin Mastery: Second level, proficient. (Total three level)'

‘Slaughtering Hand: Third level: Bloodshed. (Can be upgraded to higher level)

One of the Ancient Ender's 42 Demon Kings, Black Sethe had an unspeakable talent for killing. With a glance, souls would be extinguished and legend spoke of his hands that could send anything to the abyss whether dead or alive…’

"Fifteen potential points, if I forcefully level up the Slaughtering Hand…" Garen wanted to calculate how effective the Slaughtering Hand would be after the upgrade, but unfortunately, this demonic technique was different from all the Living Secret Techniques that he had practiced before, so even he could not estimate how strong it would be after the upgrade.

Garen’s gaze fell on the Slaughtering Hand technique.

Suddenly, a short and abrupt message flashed through his heart.

‘To upgrade the Slaughtering Hand, you will require ten potential points.’

If he could not use the other power system to train for the time being, then it might be a good idea to develop the currently unknown future of the Slaughtering Hand.

Garen finally set his mind on it, his gaze gathering on the Slaughter Hand.

In that instant, the icon began to blur, and then it began to shake violently.

The potential points cascaded madly, like a waterfall, dropping from fifteen points to a measly five points. The five points he had just obtained disappeared just like that. Now he probably had to wait until he had completely received the relics and antiques from the Black Uniform Organization before he could get another refill.

The icon for the Slaughtering Hand began to stabilize.

Soon enough, a brand new triangular icon, glowing with a black light, gathered and formed again.

‘Slaughtering Hand: Fourth level: Massacre (now creating more formation levels…)

Mad massacres brought Black Sethe immeasurable pleasure, his hands could now steal away enemy souls through specific pressure points. After the fourth level, the Slaughtering Hand will be able to gather even more life force, and, by collecting information on the practitioners themselves, it will be able to create brand new derivative levels afterward.’

‘Soul Seed Strengthening Effect —— Frost Essence (adds frost power to attacks, can inflict frost damage on enemies. Has a very high resistance towards cold surroundings)’

Garen observed it closely for a long time, but he could not find any drastic changes in the fourth level of the Slaughtering Hand, he could just store more life force at once, and then some new details on how to deal with this secret technique naturally appeared in his brain, it was some information about some pressure points that were not elaborated on in the Slaughtering Hand Secret Technique’s own records. He knew these pressure points, there were only a very few that he had not noticed himself, all of them could be fatal, but these things were utterly useless to him. He had countless secret techniques and skills that could kill others, but to beings as strange as the Blood Breeds, there was seriously nothing he could do, if what AG said was true, and he really could kill them without first finding their true bodies, then it really would be troublesome for him.

He felt slightly disappointed, but in any case not everything will develop exactly as he hoped.

He did not dwell on it long either, when the Battle of the Blood Breeds truly started, he could easily find an opportunity to hunt a middle or higher level Blood Breed as a guinea pig for his Slaughtering Hand.

Just then, the ancient scroll in his hand moved slightly.

Garen hurriedly opened the scroll lightly, putting it somewhere outsiders could not see.

New, clear lines of words had finally appeared on the pages, AG had evidently just written them.

‘The light party’s number two Death Apostle, Scarlet Moon, is grievously injured and missing in action. Perhaps you can start now, the first step of your training.’

‘If you want to become a true witch, the first step is dreams.’

And then AG began to teach Garen about the levels among witches.

They corresponded with the level systems of the Blood Breeds as well, Death Apostles, upper level, middle level, lower level, disciples (vampires), they had actually drawn out their levels according to the level of Blood Breeds that they could face.

And until now, there was only one Death Apostle level female witch -- Lion Mother, the leaders of the other territories were only upper level witches at the most, and as for male witches, he was the very last upper level male witch…

Male witches were actually about to disappear from the pages of history, they were being utterly eliminated by the female witches.

‘That’s why the Blood Breeds are so strong, because they have four Death Apostles.’ AG wrote as such.

‘So my power is only at the upper level as well?" Garen asked.

‘Your situation is very dangerous, and also very strange, but perhaps the Blood Breeds are wary of the mysterious power in your hands, so even if you have no awareness or resistance whatsoever to their dream powers, they still have not made a move against you. You are special. However, the power in your hands cannot protect your consciousness, so you were still affected in that dream. This means your position is still very dangerous, your power is nowhere near enough to deal with attacks from Death Apostles.’

‘Unless you are willing to release your hands, but even that is merely a temporary measure, the Death Apostles are undying, you can’t kill them. Of course, I don’t really know what will happen when you face a Death Apostle either.’

Garen frowned.

"Right now, putting aside my own power, how long will it take for me to learn the basics of your power system?"

‘I don’t know, maybe a month, maybe more.’

"You just said, that the number two Death Apostle named Scarlet Moon was grievously hurt and is now on the run? Didn’t you say they’re really hard to kill? Without finding their true bodies."

"Two Death Apostles who were extremely familiar with him surrounded him, my news also comes from the proper channel, you don’t need to doubt me. Not even the number one Death Apostle, Ashen, knows this. But it can’t be hidden for long.’

"Then which side is the Death Apostle who marked me from?" Garen persisted.

‘Unfortunately, I don’t know, but I have a guess, a very bold guess, that maybe that Death Apostle does not belong to any side at all, the scent of its mark is something I’ve never seen before.’

"Are you saying it’s a new Death Apostle, who had been wandering outside the two main factions?"

‘Or worse…’

"Then what did you mean by that ally you mentioned in the very beginning? Is it a companion of yours?" Garen pressed again.

The other side stayed silent for a while, before replying again in words.

‘The minimum requirement to become a witch is to have your own ally. That is a companion you can trust unconditionally, with no barriers between you, we usually believe that it is a part of the body’s consciousness that had split away independently, but nobody has done any real research into it before. You can ask him, and he will answer all your answers, these questions are all things that you already instinctively know, you just can’t dig them out from the depths of your memory.’

Garen frowned deeply.

He did not like having to trust someone without knowing anything about them. What does that ally sound like the first signs of split personality disorder…

Maybe he can just research the witches’ power system, and absorb the part used to fight Blood Breeds…

He began to think about that, once he got his hands on the many relics from the Black Uniform Organization’s side, he might have a large intake of potential points at once, then he would have more choices.

He had a feeling that the Slaughtering Hand’s derivative levels from now on might bring him an unexpected surprise. Although he could not really tell the principles behind it…

As for AG’s rating of him, he naturally would not take offense, after all, he still had many things he had yet to reveal. Such as his aura, for example…

**********************

America -- Grano.

Night, twelve minutes past ten.

Isaros brought her sister Arisa out of the convenience store, the car had already been refueled, and she swiped her petrol card.

Isaros gestured for her sister to get into the car first, taking out her phone to check her messages, the white light shining on her face and making it seem somewhat blindingly white.

In an instant, the sisters had stayed here for several years. She counted, and for a moment she could not remember clearly, this peaceful life was way too comfortable, so much so that they were beginning to forget how their days were before.

"Hey, Big Sis, there’s someone lying here!" Suddenly her sister Arisa’s voice came from the car.

"Hm?"

Isaros smoothened out her long hair, and strode over.

Beside her white car, there was an unconscious man, dressed in rags.

The man had no signs of any injuries or bleeding, so he looked like a homeless person.

"Big Sis, why don’t we take him home?" Arisa seemed to feel pity for him. She was always like that, she had plenty of love for all thing pitiful, be it people or animals.

"No way, that’s a man. What if he has bad intentions?" Isaros decided to use this opportunity to educate her sister.

"Big Sis, are you scared of such a thin man?" Arisa asked in confusion, "Weren’t you able to easily beat up five or six in the past?"

Seeing her little sister’s imploring expression, Isaros also sighed helplessly.

"Fine, fine, we’ll bring him back, it’s not like we never encountered this before…"

Neither of them noticed that the unconscious man had a mark like a scarlet moon in the middle of his brow, that was the mark of a Blood Breed under Scarlet Moon’s command.

Chapter 631: Troublesome 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

They took care of a stranger, a man that had never met before but was found passed out on the road, and they were two young girls to boot.

This was undeniably an unbelievable thing under any circumstances, but it did indeed happen.

Perhaps Arisa sensed something wrong as soon as she laid eyes on that man, her sympathy was triggered like never before. Or perhaps Isaros was absolutely confident in her own abilities, and did not care at all what intentions that thin homeless man might have, she just planned to bring him home, toss him something to eat, and let him rest for one night in a windless corner under her roof, that would already be the biggest good she could do for him.

But regardless, the two of them did indeed bring this person back.

It was exceedingly strange.

By the time Isaros came back to her senses, she was sitting in her kitchen, with her little sister, watching that man gulp down his food while sprawled on the table.

"Looks like the poor guy was starving…" Arisa said to her older sister quietly, the two sisters were sitting side by side, both rather speechless.

"What is going on here?" Isaros glanced at her little sister, she had no idea why she allowed this filthy tramp into her house, and then let him eat at the table like he belonged here.

"Thank you very much for your kindness." The tramp lowered his head to show his gratitude, smiling slightly, the air about him feeling nothing like a man of the streets, but more like a well-bred English gentleman.

"My name is Perseus, I sincerely apologize for disturbing your lives, I’ll leave straight away." The tramp politely stated that he would leave immediately.

"Mr Perseus, you’re not a tramp, are you?" But Arisa was beginning to feel interested in this well-mannered man. At sixteen years old, her curiosity was at its peak, she felt that this man must have some unknown story behind him, and was instantly even more curious about him.

"Can you tell us about your past? Your mannerisms mean that you were once a very well-bred person, right?"

Isaros wanted to speak but held back, she got the feeling that this person was not very normal.

"I’m very sorry, some natural-born characteristic of mine attracted you two, it was my mistake, and it’s also our… our race’s self-defense ability…" Perseus smiled bitterly, "I am currently in a very troublesome situation, the best method is for me to leave right now, otherwise I might cause you a lot of trouble."

"My Big Sis is really strong!" Arisa had seen how strong her sister could be, catching a blade with her bare hands was nothing, she had even faced down guns many times before, Isaros was in fact an elite fighter who had undergone White Phoenix’s training regimes. She was herself a prodigy to start with, so those with average abilities could not hope to match her, even with guns.

"Don’t say that. There are many others stronger than me. Even Uncle Thomas’ son, Garen, is stronger than me." She heard that Garen was training in combat every day as well, the last time she went to him for sparring, she was indeed no match for him, just in terms of fighting, Garen was strong enough to be a professional.

"But you are strong, Big Sis." Arisa widened her eyes.

"I think I should go now." Perseus stood up suddenly, and only then did the two of them notice his heavy British accent.

Perseus wore a torn-up grey shirt, his jeans and shoes were both covered in a layer of grey-black, and the original white beneath it could just barely be seen.

He quickly walked up to the kitchen window, holding up a tiny corner of the curtain to peep outside. There was the faint sound of a car engine approaching.

"They’re coming."

"Is someone after you? Mr Perseus." Isaros could tell that his anxiety was real, "Do you want us to call the cops? The head officer in town is also a good friend of ours."

"It doesn’t matter if the police come…" Perseus smiled bitterly, "There’s no more time, I’ll be off now, thank you for your dinner."

He quickly walked to the window on the other side of the kitchen, raising the curtains with a whoosh, then he jumped lightly, and instantly flew out of the window, vanishing from sight.

Behind him, the sisters thought that their eyes were playing tricks on them, Arisa rubbed her eyes, and still could not see any trace of Perseus.

"Don’t dwell on it." Isaros had experienced a lot in life, and now she quickly calmed down, remembering those rumored supernatural phenomena. Alarms rang in her heart.

She walked over and quickly closed the window, drawing the curtains.

"Go wash up and sleep, just pretend we’ve never seen this Mr Perseus."

Arisa had been on the run with her sister for many years, so she knew when things were serious, and presently she nodded obediently without asking any more questions.

The two sisters washed up with their respective thoughts, then they went back to their rooms and went to sleep wordlessly. But that Mr Perseus’ figure was always wandering in their thoughts.

******************

"Raffaele, there are Blood Breeds in town again."

In an underground room in town, two young women were standing behind Raffaele, watching her as she went through some documents at her desk. The candlelight flickered, constantly emitting a pale golden halo of light, this light was just enough to cover the three of them, no more and no less. It formed a strange spherical space.

"Which side are they from?" Raffaele picked up a document and asked casually.

"There are some from the light party and the secret party." A black woman with many braids lowered her head and replied.

"Are they the ones after Scarlet Moon?" Raffaele frowned, and immediately found it troublesome. "Grandma told me that the battle between the two sides is at its peak now, we can’t interfere carelessly.

"Then do we allow those Blood Breeds to just wreak havoc in our town?" That goes against our rules." The other white woman said grudgingly. Her older brother had been sucked dry by the Blood Breed’s secret party, so after she became a witch, she harbored an unprecedented hatred towards the Blood Breed’s secret party. She had always been one of those who supported taking a hard stance against the Blood Breed’s secret party.

"This is not a small matter." Raffaele tilted her face, her long golden hair shining in the candlelight. "As long as there is one Blood Breed with Scarlet Moon’s blood, the Death Apostle Scarlet Moon will not die, so they will need to exterminate all the Blood Breeds with the Death Apostle’s blood before they can truly eliminate Scarlet Moon. On that front, there is no way the secret party will back down, especially now that they have been greatly strengthened with two Death Apostles."

"They won’t compromise, so if we reject them, it might incite a war. This is something I can decide, as a leader of one territory."

Raffaele stopped.

"Inform them of our rules, as long as they don’t cause widespread destruction, we will tolerate them. Otherwise, in order to survive, we will begin this war, that is our bottom line."

"Understood."

The two women left the circle of light and the underground room, wearing different expressions.

Raffaele turned her head around, looking into the darkness ahead.

"Grandma."

It was pitch black there, but a pale old woman in a metal wheelchair slowly appeared from the shadows.

She sat in a wheelchair, her face full of wrinkles like tree bark, but those eyes alone were extremely young, like the eyes of a teenage girl, pure and clean, as blue as the ocean.

"Your decision was correct." The old woman nodded, "We must not be swept into the Blood Breeds’ internal conflict, this is an unnatural storm, an unprecedented maelstrom, and it might very well decide the way of the world from now on. Before the Lion Mother makes her intention clear, we must make sure not to cross any boundaries."

"What does the Lion Mother intend?" Raffaele asked.

"All the leaders have yet to reach the old dame. The prophecy tells her that we have to wait a little longer." The old woman replied softly. "Before you become an upper level witch, don’t be hasty. Your talent is the strongest of any I’ve ever seen, you also have the most hope of reaching the upper level."

Raffaele nodded quietly.

These territory leaders, especially those in charge of border territories, were mostly middle level witches, this meant they were as powerful as middle level Blood Breeds. That sounded weak, but in truth that was extremely common, and they were actually stronger than average.

The Blood Breeds that tended to fight with them were mostly vampires, it did not matter to the Blood Breeds how many of these cannon fodders were created, they used very, very little in the way of resources. But true Blood Breeds were a lot rarer. They were strong, noble, and due to their meager numbers, they lived easy and luxurious lives, so they would not easily reveal themselves. Most of them had assimilated with the humans, living the high life.

They had long lives, great power, and most of them were officials in high positions, with high statuses. None of them would want to give up such comfortable lives, which was also why there were many more Blood Breeds in the light party than the secret party. Who would give up their peaceful lives, and run into one of violence and killing?

So ninety percent of the ones who were active outside were all vampires, and occasionally there would be a lower level Blood Breed to control their promises and the conflicts with the witches.

Under these circumstances, a middle level witch was already a very powerful presence.

Most witches could only reach the level of disciple, and the better ones could reach the lower level, this meant they were capable of fighting lower level Blood Breeds. This already meant that they had unnatural power.

Such witches were one in a hundred, they were already part of the core fighting force. And the powerful magical tool that had controlled the Grano witches were idolized and worshipped by the witches in other territories. The title of Sun’s Will was not just for show, she had won it through tried and true battles and tests.

"I understand." Raffaele nodded.

The old woman nodded, satisfied, and once more disappeared into the darkness.

Only Raffaele was left, deep in thought.

************************

America, the state of Faya,

The next morning, 11:22 am

In a large white state bus headed to Grano.

Everyone in the bus was groggy and sleepy, most of them were napping under the warm sunlight.

Garen sat in his seat, watching the plains, roads, cars, and the occasional traveler on a bike all whisk past his window.

After he got off the plane, he immediately got onto the bus, and after a few transits, he finally boarded this large tourist bus, full of people all going to Grano, although it was slower than usual, he did not have to transit anymore, so it was a lot less stressful.

He was still holding that ancient scroll in his hand, but his thoughts were elsewhere.

Chapter 632: Troublesome 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

It would be at least another month before the Black Uniforms’ relics were transferred to him, and the situation was extremely troublesome.

After the news of Levi’s murder got out, his enemies and allies all made their moves, stealing the power and people who used to belong to the Black Uniforms, and many of their men had carried their secret to other organizations, most of the relics had been lost to outsiders.

The Nighthawks were low on manpower and could not prevent all this from happening. All they could do was try to pick up the pieces little by little, Jay ran about here and there with his own little team, Garen had promised that he was solely in charge of the Black Uniform Organization’s power and members, in other words, all the Black Uniforms would become a subsidiary of the Nighthawks under his watch. That way, he had no choice but to go all out, after all, the power getting away was all to be his in the future.

Baldy, on the other hand, had gone back to recuperate, his wife had been in Europe on a mission, but when she heard that he was seriously injured, she rushed to Africa overnight to care for him, and now Garen had let them off on a vacation around the world.

And now that woman with the black ponytail, Sandora, was in charge of the Nighthawks.

While everything was still getting in order on this side, Garen also took the chance to hurry back to America, and visit his parents at home. After this he might have to delve into his training to deal with the mark of the Death Apostle.

Suddenly there was a beeping from his phone, it was his message notification.

‘Where are you now?’

It was a message from his father, Emmer.

"Still on the road, I don’t where either, but it will take at least four hours." Garen replied.

‘We prepared beef chicken finger foie gras caviar soup to celebrate your first time coming home from university, it’s a dish your mom’s trying out. It tastes great with durian salad. You’ll love it!’

Garen did not know what expression he should have.

Just by the name itself, he could tell that the soup would definitely taste terrible, it was a soup will all meat and no vegetables at all. And there was that durian salad or something, just hearing about made his tongue feel heavy.

‘Your mom has been studying nutrition recently, she thinks that by distilling most of the nutrients from meats and adding it to soup, we can get the nutrients needed without having to stuff ourselves, you’ll love it once you get back.’

"What about Jason, what’s he doing now?"

‘He went to a Nohn state university, if you hadn’t gone for the exam first, he should have gone before you. Oh yeah, after you left, Raffaele has been coming to visit a lot less frequently, but Arisa and her sister have been coming quite often, asking about you, do you want to consider choosing one of them?’ This was followed by a pervy expression. ‘I think Jason’s got no chance.’

"I’m still early, what’s the rush?" Garen could not help but think of those two strange-looking sisters.

They had many connections to the Primary Colors, and they had that strange air about them as well, as though they were the center of the world.

"They’re still okay, right?" He sent a message to ask.

‘Not bad, Arisa’s going to be in high school soon, together with little Vivien. Her older sister Isaros has many suitors, and she declared that the minimum requirement for anyone who wants to pursue her is they have to beat her head-on, didn’t you beat her back then? Go for it! Don’t be afraid! Your mom and I will be supporting you from behind!’

Garen could not be bothered to respond to this nonsense.

"Have they acted strangely in any way?"

‘Strangely? Nah, they’re totally normal.’

"Let’s discuss it when I get back." Garen replied finally.

‘Sure.’

Breaking off his idle conversation with his dad Emmer, Garen quickly gave Raffaele a call.

After a short moment of ringing, the other side picked up.

‘Garen? You’re coming back?’ Raffaele’s voice was as confident as ever.

"How did you know? I’m on the way back now. How have you been?"

‘Not bad, you?"

"Okay."

Then there was a short silence, neither of them knew what to say.

‘The town is a little chaotic recently, you shouldn’t have come back now.’ After the silence, Raffaele continued, ‘Want me to accompany you around for a bit?’

"Chaotic? Hasn’t Grano always been fine?" Garen heard something amiss, he actually already knew that Raffaele was probably a witch, so if even she said it was chaotic, then something serious must have happened.

‘Some criminals on the run have infiltrated the town, the situation’s not too great.’

"I’ll leave once I see my parents, I won’t be staying long anyway, so it’ll be fine." Garen chuckled.

‘How’s school life?’ Raffaele changed the subject.

"Not bad, it’s the same as always." The two of them fell quiet again.

"Then I’ll hang up now." Garen said first.

‘Mm.’

The line broke off.

Garen suddenly felt as though he did not have much to say with Raffaele anymore, before this they used to swim together, mess around together, they lived so near each other, and went to school together, but now they had nothing left in common.

Putting down the phone, he suddenly felt a bit tired, so he closed his eyes and rested.

"Sonny boy, you don’t look so good."

An old man sitting in front of him turned around to look at Garen, he seemed to have noticed Garen when trying to pick up something that he had dropped.

Sitting in this bus, an exceptional-looking young man like Garen was definitely very eye-catching. For example, on the seats to his left, two young girls sitting next to each other kept peeking at him now and then.

"I’m fine, I just haven’t gotten enough sun lately." Garen smiled politely.

"Is that so?" The old man wore a round straw hat to block off the sun. He wore a thin floral print shirt and black shorts, looking every inch the fashionable geezer.

"The last time I saw you, you were a lot better than you are now. I remember you could play the violin as well, right?" The old man said smilingly.

"Violin?" Garen frowned. "Excuse me, do I know you?"

"Didn’t we meet last time?" The old man replied with a smile.

His voice suddenly began to shake, twisting, blurring, becoming low and muffled.

His face actually started to melt, dripping down like candle wax, dripping onto the floor of the bus, creating holes of different sizes at the bottom of the bus.

Garen realized with some surprise that after the bottom of the bus was melted away, it did not reveal the high-speed freeway, but instead it showed a blurry mass of black.

He did not know why he found the old man’s face melting so natural, and was instead surprised by something else.

His gaze could not help but gather on the black holes below, lowering his head, he could only see the old man’s trousered bottom half from the corner of his eye.

Strangely, when he wanted to focus and observe the details on the floor inside the bus, he could not focus at all, as though everything was a blur. There were no details, no patterns, no dust.

Smack.

He seemed to hear something.

From the corner of his eye, he saw the old man stand up, turn around, face him, and stand motionlessly in front of him, then he suddenly lifted his leg and walked straight towards Garen.

Garen suddenly felt an unprecedented wave of fear wash over him.

He wanted to raise his head and look at the old man’s face, but he could not move at all to complete such a simple task, he could only keep his head lowered.

The old man’s body grew closer and closer, closer and closer, and the yellow wax dripping from his upper half also grew closer.

"What’s happening here?" It was as though there was a veil over Garen’s heart, his thoughts were very slow, like a baby moving on instinct, he had completely lost his ability to think, and could only watch as the old man approached him.

Bam!

There was an intense jolt, and Garen abruptly opened his eyes.

Phew…!

He leaned back in his seat, and stared wide-eyed at the empty seat in front of him, there was no one there at all. There was only a young woman sitting in the seats even further front, and her head was tilted as she slept.

There was the mumble of complaints in the bus for the jerking around just now.

"Sorry, I didn’t notice a rock in the middle of the road just now, so I just went over it." The driver apologized loudly.

Only then did Garen realize that he had fallen asleep, and all that was just a dream.

He touched his forehead, it was completely dripping wet.

He looked at the back of the seat in front of him again, closely, there was an ad with a beautiful woman messing with her head and posing, one hand raised up, the other hand on her waist, and she wore nothing but a blue dress with a low neckline. There was a line of small words next to it: Ancient Eastern methods, to give you back your purity.

Underneath that, they introduced the various effects, the main services being painless flow and repairing the virgin’s *...

There was a black stain on the unknown noun, he didn’t know what it was that dyed the ad. Beside it, someone had written in black ink: F*ck you!

A strange sense of happiness instantly washed away Garen’s previous indescribable emotion, he settled his heart, and touched the material on the back of the seat, it felt rough, like raincoat material.

He looked to the left, and saw a middle-aged couple leaning on each other as they slept, there was no young girl at all.

"What was that just now? If I wasn’t awoken by the jolt of the bus, what could have happened?" As soon as Garen thought that, there was an indescribable panic in his heart, as though his very soul was facing some huge threat.

‘You must realize you’re dreaming while in a dream.’ AG’s words resurfaced in his heart.

"How do I tell that I’m dreaming when I’m in a dream?" Garen thought back to all that had happened, that unprecedented sense of danger and panic did not feel false at all, if that thing that did not seem human really did touch him, then what happened to him next might really have hurt his soul.

That was the natural warning from his Soul Seed, it was not false.

After this contact, he knew that the person he suspected to be a Death Apostle had made his move, that dream he just had was an attack! A very dangerous attack!

Garen concluded in his heart, taking out a tissue to wipe the sweat off his forehead.

If he wanted to know that he was dreaming while in a dream, then following one of AG’s methods, he could determine the difference using details, that was where the biggest difference between reality and dreams lay. Dreams were illusory, because they were constructed based on a human’s own memories, these constructions could not be too intricate, so there would definitely be some blurred or unpresented details. That was why right now, he should be able to tell that he was not in a dream.

Garen wiped his face with his hands, for the first time, he felt as though he could not fight back at all, and was completely ambushed by another entity.

He looked at his attribute pane, and the number in his Spirit pane had actually dropped…

From 2.4 to 2.3, it had dropped a whole 0.1.

"As I thought… That attack just now was really…" Garen also saw a new icon, like pitch black mist, behind his Condition pane.

The instant his gaze moved onto it, an inexplicable piece of information flowed into his heart.

‘Nightmare Weakening: The terror of the dream will constantly reduce the main body’s qualities over five days, until all the attributes have dropped by an average of 0.1. The curse will last forever and has no time limitations, and the deactivation method is unknown. Warning! This curse can be stacked on!’

"Nightmare Weakening! …" For the first time, for the first time ever, Garen personally felt how powerful and troublesome his opponent was.

Chapter 633: Void 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

An attack method outside of what he knew, outside the areas he was familiar with, to Garen, this truly was a very troublesome matter.

Although he was not afraid of anything, and the Slaughtering Hand on both his hands had some effect, he still was not primed to deal with this.

"Just a split second’s time is enough to pull me into this dream, this ability really is very troublesome." Garen sat up straight.

Nothing else happened on the way back, and although Garen was constantly on high alert, nothing else out of ordinary occurred all the way until he reached home.

Several hours later, the large bus slowly arrived in Grano, the surroundings turning to lush green forests. Some places were already yellowing, it was autumn now, and there was the faint fragrance of fruit in the air.

When he got off the bus, his older brother Jason was already waiting for him at the bus station, he stood in the crowd, tall and muscular, like a rugby player in a group of dwarves.

"Hey!!" As soon as he saw Garen, he started yelling loudly, waving his hand hard, attracting the gazes of everyone around him.

"Mom’s waiting for us over there, in the car." Jason rushed over in a few steps, and took Garen’s luggage.

"You’ve gotten so muscular." Garen hammered his chest, it felt a lot more solid.

"Twelve sets of mixed training every day!" Jason chortled.

Trish, who was sitting in the driver’s seat, was wearing a white lady’s shirt, and waved at them.

The two of them ducked into the car, Garen sitting in front, while Jason was pushed to the back.

"Let’s go home!" Trish said with a laugh, and she hit the gas, sending the car rushing forward, then she turned around the bend and drove on home.

The town was barely different than before, but most of the wooden houses had a new layer of paint, all white and bright.

The car drove extremely slowly, some of the uncles and older sisters from houses by the roads nearby kept greeting Trish, and Trish replied happily each time.

Going past the suburbs, they entered many streets, there were a lot of accessory and crafts shops by the streets, and a great many more passersby. Most of them were unfamiliar, and quite a few carried cameras around their necks, they were evidently tourists.

"Hey."

A few pretty young girls on bicycles slowed down when passing by Trish’s car.

One of them was actually Raffaele.

"You’re back?" She tied up her long golden hair, and was wearing a white T-shirt and long black trousers, a smile in her eyes.

"Mm." Garen reached out his hand, outside the car window, the two of them gave each other a light high-five.

"Aunty, we’ll be going on ahead." Raffaele smiled at Trish as she said that.

"Have fun." Trish was not very happy with Raffaele, that girl had actually turned down the opportunity to go to university, to Trish’s family, that was something they could not quite understand.

Compared to Raffaele, she was more inclined to Isaros, that girl had a good education, and was more suited to their family’s pace and ideals.

The row of girls in bikes formed a procession, going past the slow-moving saloon cars, and soon they disappeared down the road ahead in the midst of tinkling laughter.

Garen watched their backs and said nothing. He knew that Raffaele had come over to protect him, and that was no coincidental meeting.

"Let’s go, we’re going home straight away." Trish glanced at Garen, and sped up, driving home.

　*****************

After they got back, Garen gathered with his family for a bit, discussing some of the things that had happened in school, and ate the so-called feast, even though the taste was barely bearable.

His little Vivien kept sending messages on her phone, and she did not dress as innocently as she used to, now she had a cooler and more fierce look, plus she was no longer as warm and uninhibited with her older brother, and instead treated him with an inexplicable shyness that he did not understand.

"Serin went to a school in the north, didn’t she call you when she left?"

"No. It’s been a long time since I had any contact with her." Garen dealt with his mother’s questions.

"I hear she found a boyfriend, a real beefed-up fellow." Jason paid more attention to the other person’s muscles. He never ever forgot for a second to show off his powerful muscles, "Not as beefed-up as me, though." He flexed his biceps.

"You must be tired after the journey, why don’t you clean up and go to bed early." Trish noticed that Garen was distracted.

"Alright." Garen nodded.

He chatted a bit with his father Emmer, then he put down his cutlery and went straight to his bed, it was exactly the same, nothing in the room at all had changed since he left.

His blankets were new, pure white silk covers.

Garen collapsed onto the bed.

For some reason, he felt very sleepy, and very tired. This was extremely abnormal.

With his Vitality, forget a few hours on the road, he could go a few days and nights without getting tired.

But right now he did indeed feel extremely exhausted, he could barely keep his eyes open, and wanted so badly to just fall into bed and sleep it off.

He checked his body’s condition, but could not find anything out of the ordinary.

Closing his eyes and lying on his bed, he allowed his breathing to slowly even out.

Suddenly, his bedroom door was flung open. Someone walked in.

"What’s the matter? Are you that tired? Big Bro, you don’t look so good."

It was Vivien, her golden hair was falling over her shoulders, and she wore a feisty black T-shirt and white hot pants, revealing her long, rounded, and fair legs. She was sixteen, the purest and prettiest age.

She pounced down on Garen’s left, sprawling onto the bed.

"Bro, did something go wrong between you and Raffaele?"

"Kids shouldn’t be so nosy." Garen was too lazy to even open his eyes, closing his eyes and lying on his back as he replied. "Do you have a boyfriend now?"

"No! That sort of thing is too boring, I don’t care either way." Vivien curled a lock of hair around her finger, "Elder Brother found one, though, from out of town."

"Out of town?"

"Yeah. A real decent-looking girl." Vivien described frankly.

"Hey, be polite."

"Yeah, yeah. Forget it, you go ahead and sleep, I’ll go back to my room now." There was the sound of Vivien getting up, and then he heard the door closing, her footsteps moving further away slowly.

Garen lay on the bed, unwilling to move.

"Oh yeah, Bro!" Suddenly Vivien’s voice rang out again, and his room door was opened then closed, the footsteps rapidly approaching.

"What now?" Garen’s head hurt slightly, all he wanted now was a little time to himself so he could consider his condition.

"Do you think I look good today?"

"Yes, yes.." Garen replied half-heartedly, "Little Vivien is always the prettiest and cutest."

"You said that without even opening your eyes."

Exasperated, Garen was about to open his eyes when he suddenly sensed something amiss, he could not open his eyes at all, as though he could not exert any force with his eyelids, his body was stiff and immobile, all he could do was lie frozen on the bed.

His thoughts had grown slower, as though he evidently knew how to get out of this situation, but he just could not remember what to do.

"Here it is again…"

His heart gave a jolt.

He could not defend at all against this attack on his consciousness, there was no rhyme or reason to it, just a split second was enough to put him under.

"Bro, you don’t look so good." Vivien’s voice reached his ears, "You sick?"

"Maybe, I don’t know either." Garen replied.

"Forget it, I’m going to go bathe." Vivien seemed to have gotten angry, and then he heard her footsteps going away.

The room suddenly fell silent.

Garen lay in bed alone, his entire body as though cramped, he could not move at all, neither could he open his eyes.

In the silence, he suddenly heard faint footsteps, calmly approaching his bedside.

That person seemed to be walking towards him, closer, closer and closer, closer and closer.

The footsteps only stopped beside his bed, the other person seemed to be staring at him.

Phew…

There was the sound of a faint exhalation.

Garen felt that person seem to reach out their hands, lightly grabbing for his face.

Boom!!!

In an instant, a power like a cloud of flames erupted from Garen’s arms, this power burned like an intense invisible fire, slowly spreading all over Garen’s body.

In that moment, Garen felt as though all the skin on the surface of his body erupted with a burning hot flame, and that flame reached that person’s hands directly.

Scree!!

He seemed to hear a sharp scream, like the cry of a mouse. And then he opened his eyes.

With a whoosh, everything from before vanished in an instant, as though it was all just an illusion.

Garen felt his whole body was soaking wet, as though he had sweated profusely. He sniffled a little, and vaguely smelled a faint fragrance coming from his left. Turning his head over, he saw little Vivien lying on the bed to his left, she had fallen asleep just sprawled there, and goodness knows when she had come in.

Lifting his upper body slightly, Garen felt the sweat flowing down his hairline and forehead, tickling him.

He did not like this feeling, rather than face-to-face brawls to the death, this feeling that he could be ambushed at any time was much worse.

He sensed the life force left in his arms, he had already used up a third of it.

It was that explosion just now that managed to critically injure his opponent.

But Garen sensed that it would not be that simple.

Leaving his bedroom, he saw that the light in the study was still on, but he did not know who was inside.

He walked to the washroom, taking the towel and wiping the sweat from his body.

All of a sudden, he saw that in the crevice of his right collarbone, there was a tiny line of black words.

He instantly froze his wiping movement, those were words he recognized.

"Ancient Endor words?" Garen touched the line of letters on his right shoulder.

It was as though they had somehow been tattooed on, he could not erase them no matter what.

"The one that defeated us, was the unknown Void…" In a soft voice, he translated the meaning behind this sentence. "What does that mean?"

The Ancient Endor civilization was closely related to the Warlocks’ legacy, they were powerful and mysterious, pursuing the path of Death into the Underworld, for a moment they were incomparably powerful, but as though overnight, they disappeared without a trace.

If he recalled correctly, these words were not there when he bathed last night, in other words, they just appeared today.

Garen watched the ink and material in these words carefully, the black words had a hint of black-red, like dried blood.

Chapter 634: Void 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

For some reason, looking at these words, he vaguely found them slightly familiar, as though he had seen them somewhere before, but for now he could not remember where from.

"Ancient Endor… Black blood writing… They just appeared today, the Slaughtering Hand activated automatically…" He could be certain that he did not control that sudden activation of the Slaughtering Hand, at first he had thought that it was the secret technique’s instinctive self-defense mechanism, but now he felt it was not that simple.

He bent down and used his hands to splash some water from the tap into his face, instantly feeling a lot more awake.

"Could it be Black Sethe?" He felt that these words seemed to be speaking from an Ancient Endor point of view.

The thing that destroyed Ancient Endor, was an unknown Void…

"Looking at it that way, it makes a little sense. I’m practicing the Slaughtering Hand, so strictly speaking, I’m also one of the inheritors to the Ancient Endor legacy, perhaps there is a hint of Black Sethe’s soul left in this secret technique."

Garen remembered all that black mist that had gathered into the secret technique after Black Sethe was defeated. Remnants of Black Sethe’s soul could easily have mingled in with it.

If these were the words Black Sethe left behind, that would be very likely.

The more Garen thought about it, the more he thought it was possible.

Suddenly he remembered that when he found the original version of the Slaughtering Hand secret technique back then, the words on it were exactly the same as the ones just now!

"Black Sethe…" He murmured Black Sethe’s name in the Ancient Endor language, he could be certain that these words were left behind by Black Sethe, and that power just now was probably also Black Sethe lending him a hand.

He reached out his hand to touch the words on his right shoulder.

All of a sudden, without any foreshadowing, the words blurred slightly, and actually rapidly turned to brand new words.

‘You guessed right, I am Black Sethe.’

Garen’s heart gave a jolt.

Black Sethe, one of Ancient Endor’s 42 Demon Kings, he used to have that unprecedented position, he was one of the 42 people at the very peak of the civilization, so powerful that he was considered non-human, and honored as one of the 42 Demon Kings.

"You’re still alive?" Garen asked him quietly in the Ancient Endor language, suppressing the confusion and surprise in his heart.

‘This is just a portion of the memories I left behind. My real soul had rotted a long time ago, the real me died several millennia ago.’ The black blood writing blurred and changed again. ‘I need your strength to maintain normal conversation, with my own power alone, I can’t last long…’

"No problem."

Garen did not hesitate at all, this was his first contact with an important figure from the Ancient Endor civilization, he had too many questions and mysteries he needed answered.

Without any hesitation, he moved wisps of life force from his arms, allowing them to move down his arms and biceps, rapidly gathering at his right shoulder.

‘Alright, that’s enough.’ Black Sethe’s words appeared again, ‘If you have any questions, ask away.’

"What do you mean by what you said just now?" Garen asked in the Ancient Endor language. "Ancient Endor was destroyed by an unknown Void? What does that mean?"

‘Haven’t you already been targeted?’

"What? You mean by the Blood Breed Death Apostle?" Garen replied with a question.

‘Death Apostle? What’s that? No no no… the thing targeting you is a Void Creature, not the so-called Death Apostle." Black Sethe replied quickly, the words changing again. ‘Back then, the Void Creatures warred against the Warlocks, fighting over domination over the world, but it ended badly for both sides, both sustained damage as never before, they are our arch enemies.’

"Void Creatures?" That was the first time Garen heard that noun, "Are they creatures from the Underworld?"

‘No, the Underworld is the Underworld, that is the theoretical world we’ve been chasing all our lives, there might not really an Underworld at all, our culture believes that there is a source to the Mother Stream, eternal and everlasting, forever flowing with power, that is the place we call the Underworld. That is the end of death, the source of the purest life, we want to go there, but only those who do not wish to live would want to enter the Underworld while alive.’

It was the first time Garen heard such an explanation, he had always thought that this Underworld referred to the Underworld in legends.

"That what do you mean by Void Creatures? And what was that war you mentioned? Could you elaborate?"

‘Those were two unprecedentedly powerful wars.’ Black Sethe paused, ‘Warlocks controlled everything, treating creatures from all other races as slaves, regardless of whether they were sentient or not. The Warlocks were at the very top, their power was limitless, their lives long and vast. In their exploration of the very fabric of life, they went further and further, eventually breaking past the world barrier, descending and infiltrating new worlds one after the other, that time in history, was also one of our most glorious eras. However…’

"However what?"

‘While exploring a new world once, the Warlocks encountered pioneers just like them, those were the Void Creatures.’ Black Sethe’s tone was lonely as he described, ‘The Void Creatures are powerful and greedy, they have an endless desire for domination, as soon as the two sides made contact, they began to attack each other in unison, and this lasted almost ten million years. It lasted until both sides sustained heavy losses, even losing all their legacies. That was the first war.’

‘And then several millennia later, our Ancient Endor slowly recovered some of our glory as Warlocks, this time we respected and worshipped the Mother Stream, and the Underworld, so we trod carefully and thoughtfully. And this time, the Void Creatures were the ones who came after us.’

"Did you win or lose?"

‘In order to exterminate the Void Creatures’ world, we incited the wrath of the Mother Stream, and nobody could have predicted what happened next, the wrath of the Mother Stream was far too terrifying, the Void Creatures were completely wiped out, and we were also swallowed by a huge force, the whole civilization became history overnight. Melding into part of the Mother Stream.’

Black Sethe seemed to be getting tired.

‘The Void Creatures consider us enemies, they swore to hunt us down generation after generation until eternity. They swore on the name of the Mother Stream, that any creatures who inherited the civilization of the Warlocks would become their beacon in the darkness. They will follow you in your dreams, continuously attacking you, until you die.’

"What kind of an existence are they?" Garen frowned. "In this world, the powerful Blood Breeds, the Death Apostles, have an attack that is very much like theirs."

‘The Blood Breed’s Death Apostles? I never met them, if you can find me an example, I might be able to give you some suggestions. But I don’t think they’re Void Creatures.’ Black Sethe replied.

"Why?" Garen retorted.

‘Because they are greedy and powerful, but they do not exist in a normal world, they are creatures who exist in the crevice between illusion and reality, the weak ones are about the same as a secret technique user at best, the strong ones can even destroy whole worlds. Can you tell me what kind of life form is this Death Apostle of the Blood Breeds you speak of?’

Garen explained everything he knew about the Blood Breed’s Death Apostles in the Ancient Endor language.

Black Sethe mused for a while.

‘They’re somewhat similar, but they’re not the same, the Death Apostles’ ability has a fundamental difference, the two of them have different systems.’

"How so? They both attack creatures through dreams, right?" Garen frowned.

‘No, it’s not the same.’ Black Sethe explained, ‘Death Apostles control the dreams formed by creatures themselves and sneak in, controlling their target’s thoughts. The Void Creatures, however, create illusions, not just dreams, and they can forcefully drag other creatures into the illusions they create, or it might even a product of a mixture of illusion and reality.’

‘The power of the Void Creatures’ lies mainly in confusing you as to whether they’re real or not, whether you’re living in an illusion or reality. Both are fundamentally different.’

With that explanation, Garen understood.

"In that case, how can I be sure that my conversation with you now is actually taking place in reality, and is not actually an illusion?" He asked suddenly.

‘The Void Creatures’ illusions have an important characteristic, which is that they fear life force. You can try channeling the life force in your arms all over your body, that way you can fight their attacks to a certain extent.’

Black Sethe did not stop, continuing on.

‘Their moves are somewhat similar to the Death Apostles of this world, but they are not the same, only the effect seems similar. I suspect they noticed you when you entered the Mother Stream, and that was when they targeted you, following you here.’

"Why do you say so?"

‘Because they have yet to fully enter this world yet, they just sensed your scent, they’re still slowly corroding and settling in this world. That’s why their power is so weak.’

"This is weak…" Garen was speechless, "If what you say is true, that I was the one who brought this thing to this world, is that so?"

‘Indeed, they are using you as their location marker, and with every dream illusory attack, they are constantly settling their place in this world. This connection is established through the link of the ancient oath. You can also sense their position similarly.’

"Then you all would have methods to deal with the Void Creatures, right? And the complete legacy of the Warlocks."

‘You want that?’

"Of course."

‘Then you must agree on one condition for me, or rather, give me a promise. An Eternal Oath to the Mother Stream. You must dedicate everything to completing an Eternal Oath, or else you will forever be cursed by the Mother Stream. Reply to me when you’ve thought it over.’ Black Sethe’s words instantly faded and vanished.

"An Eternal Oath…"

Wiping the water off his face, Garen walked out of the washroom.

He slowly released some of the life force in his arms, allowing it to flow all over his body, and he instantly felt a lot more awake, as though his senses had suddenly gotten a lot clearer.

He just had a lot of information dumped onto him, so he needed some time to digest it properly, the fact that Black Sethe’s remaining soul or rather his memory had awoken, the existence of the Void Creatures, the fact that they were not the Death Apostles, but rather an enemy he had brought into this world himself. He needed time to think over all of these things.

It was highly unlikely that this was false, after all even if Death Apostles could control dreams, these were all things he would not be able to know, and it was impossible for them to instantly learn the Ancient Endor language, before this, Garen had never before used this language in front of outsiders.

Chapter 635: Mission 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Back in his room, Black Sethe never came out again.

Garen sat on his bed alone, looking over his Attribute pane. Without him realizing, his spirit, also known as Intelligence, had decreased once again from 2.4 to 2.2, by 0.2 points.

"No, the decrease should only be 0.1 isn't it?" Garen remembered the hint he had seen before.

Then, he noticed the change in the Nightmare Weakening icon.

‘Nighmare Weakening 2: A superimposition in the Weakening. Permanent decrease by an average of 0.2 points every five days. Effects cannot be undone.'

He quickly stood up while switching on the light and walked to a full-length mirror.

"Trouble has come…" Garen's eyebrows were furrowed.

Previously he'd thought it was temporary but now it seemed to be permanent!

His attributes were accumulated little by little through training since he was small. Even 0.1 point needed one of his potential points. All of a sudden he lost two 0.1 points which were equivalent to two potential points!

"Is there a way to get rid of it? Black Sethe."

He muttered to the mirror using Ancient Ender language.

‘Make the vow and I will tell you how to lift the curse' Black Sethe's handwriting appeared on his reflection's right shoulder.

‘Let me remind you, once the third Nightmare Weakening superimposition arrives, your body will weaken once again, and more seriously. However, your vigilance is something worth commending. Only a little change and you realize it this soon. I expected that you would need two more days to notice it.'

He paused.

‘You need to be careful. This kind of change is irreversible. Once it's too late, even I cannot restore what you lost. That's why you must make your decision soon.'

"What kind of vow do you want me to make?" Garen asked.

‘A very simple vow yet a very difficult one.' Black Sethe did not keep him in suspense. ‘Pursue and kill Void Creatures until they are completely erased, no matter which world! Swear in the name of the Mother Stream!' His hatred for the Void Creatures could be felt in his handwriting.

"Is there a time limit?" Garen unexpectedly did not care about the content of this vow.

‘Of course not. However, a vow in the name of Mother Stream requires you to complete it wholeheartedly. The hatred from the whole civilization will be passed on to you and you will inherit it involuntarily to kill and to pursue the existence of Void Creatures.' Black Sethe seemed quite candid about this. ‘I don't want you to regret it.'

"Do I have a choice?" Garen asked.

Black Sethe was silent.

‘Indeed not.'

Void Creature had come for Garen and had taken a shot at him. Since this was the case, there was no need for Garen to hesitate.

"I promise you, in the name of Mother Stream, to kill Void Creatures for life until they are annihilated completely!"

Garen answered in a low voice.

‘In the name of Ancient Ender. The soul of the warlocks will look out for you! They are supervisors yet also supporters. Their gazes are upon you and when it's necessary, you may summon their main body in the Mother Stream to help you in your fight.' Black Sethe replied.

"They are still alive?"

‘No, those are just traces of their past imprinted in the records of the Mother Stream. However, their strong thoughts will allow them to respond to your summon. Countless heroes, former gods and us, the forty-two Demon Kings together with all those who swear to destroy the Void Creatures will respond to your summon.' Black Sethe answered solemnly. His voice was as though it gave off the feeling of a mission that spanned from the distant past.

Garen also felt an incomparably heavy pressure.

"How do I make this vow?" No matter what, he needed to solve this Nightmare Weakening curse.

‘Swear with your Soul Seed. Let it vibrate.' Black Sethe's handwriting reappeared.

Garen went silent for a while.

Only then, his voice slowly sounded out.

"I swear with my Soul Seed…" Just as his voice came out, the Soul Seed in his mind vibrated, as though this sentence contained a particular meaning. Weirdly, when he said it in the language of Ancient Ender, his tone sounded as though he was singing a song.

‘For eternity, pursue and kill Void Creatures, until they are exterminated.'

"For eternity, pursue and kill Void Creatures, until they are exterminated!" Garen said it out loud according to Black Sethe's handwriting.

At that instant, he could feel that something in between his eyebrows split and fly out into the air and disappeared. He did not know what that was but the sense of separation made him feel uncomfortable.

‘That is True Soul.' A man's low voice sounded beside his ear.

Garen squinted his eyes, hesitation reflected on his face.

"Are you Black Sethe?" he whispered.

‘Of course, you swore with your Soul Seed and in the name of Mother Stream. Ancient Ender language has the ability to resonate with the universe and is one of the most mysterious languages. So, your oath succeeded. A bit of your True Soul separated and returned to the Mother Stream. It became a trace that is imprinted in the Mother Stream.' Black Sethe said, ‘This way, my imprint is able to communicate with your imprint directly through the Mother Stream, achieving a phenomenon as though I am talking to you directly.'

He paused.

'This way, when you returned to the Mother River in the future, the future generation can also summon your main body through your imprint.'

"Will this affect me?" Garen frowned.

‘Not much of an influence. This is only a sign that you are part of our inheritance. The Ancient Ender and the Ancient Warlocks are different. We believe in the Eternal Mother Stream, the mysterious and unchanging Underworld. Therefore, you are now a true successor.' Black Sethe's deep hoarse voice contained a certain charm.

"Is there any meaning to all this?" Garen was puzzled.

‘Of course, there is a meaning.'

Black Sethe suddenly fell silent.

Hiss…

Suddenly, Garen found that all over his body, there were strands of black smoke gathering and condensing behind him.

Very quickly, the black smoke formed an obscure dark figure.

The figure was over two meters tall, taller than him, His body was made of smoke with only two red eyes in its head.

‘In the name of Mother Stream, you are now granted a new destiny, Void Pursuer.'

Black Sethe used his alluring voice to say out this sentence.

In that instant, Garen felt that his body had become heavy. He felt as though he was wearing armor yet he could not felt anything at the same time.

He felt his skin burning, as though something with a rough surface was chafing his skin.

‘Within five days, find and kill the Void Creature that cursed you and your weakening will be eliminated. This also serves as your trial.' Black Sethe said.

"What's the use? I mean this Void Pursuer identity." Garen moved his body, feeling no changes.

‘Without this identity, you will not be able to get rid of your weakening even if you kill the Void Creature. This is a kind of soul illness, a soul disease.'

After Black Sethe finished talking, his body dissipated and turned into a clump of black gas floating in the air.

‘You have awakened me and practiced my Secret Techniques. To a certain extent, you can summon my imprint in the Mother Stream easily. That is if you want to.

His voice was coming from the ball of black gas.

"We'll talk about it later." Garen did not give a direct response. "This means you will work with me in the future?"

‘If you're willing.'

The ball of black gas condensed into a black ring. The surface was inlaid with two red lines made with red jewels.

The ring floated in front of Garen. He caught the ring and wore it on his left hand's middle finger.

‘I can help you guard against the Void Creature's attacks to a certain extent and when you summon my imprint, the cost will be lower.'

"What is the cost of summoning?"

‘It can be anything, Mother Stream is not picky as long as there is the energy of life. But you have to be careful not to overdo it because it may consume your lifespan, not the lifespan belonging to your flesh body but your soul's lifespan.' Black Sethe reminded him. ‘After this, I will impart you the key to deal with Void Creatures. There is no need to hurry, the creature will come for you soon, I will help at that time…'

The voice faded away.

Garen stood in front of the full-length mirror while rubbing the black ring on his finger.

He suspected that Black Sethe was still concealing something. In the beginning, Black Sethe was planning to take over his body but was ultimately defeated. Now, he came out to help him on his own volition without seeking anything in return. This made him even more wary.

However, the attack of the Void Creatures was imminent and he had to resort to using his power.

"No hurry, I'll deal with it when it comes. Any attempt will reveal itself." Garen looked forward to even more Potential points. As long as there were sufficient Potential points, he would be able to get stronger and reached an extreme point where it might be possible to find the key to deal with Void Creatures.

He glanced at his Attribute Pane.

At the bottom, a new title called Void Pursuer was there.

‘Void Pursuer: Successor of Ancient Ender, the mortal enemy of Void Creatures. Has the ability to heal and become stronger through plundering the core of Void Creatures. It is an ability granted by the mysterious Ancient Ender.'

*****************

"Arisa, please hand me my towel."

Isaros shouted from the bathroom.

"Alright." Arisa put down the fashion magazine in her hand, got up from her bed and ran over to the bathroom on the other end of the living room.

Grabbing her sister's white towel, she went exited the bathroom and instinctively glanced at the front door. There was a faint fishy odor.

"What's that smell?" She whispered. Slowing down her pace, she crept over to the front door.

Suddenly, she saw some sort of red liquid flowing in through the gap in the door.

"This is…" She squatted down to touch the liquid with her hand and sniffed.

"It's blood!" She exclaimed.

"Sis!!"

Chapter 636: Mission 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

In the bathroom, Isaros was startled. She'd heard her little sister's shrill voice. Not waiting for her hair to dry, she rushed out of the bathroom wrapped in a bath towel. She ran to her sister in the living room while barefooted.

She saw Arisa squatting by the front door looking nervously at her.

"Sis, it's blood!" Arisa lowered her voice volume. She'd experienced several years of being hunted down with her sister, and naturally, she had more experience than the people her age.

"It came in through the door," Arisa added.

Isaros nodded. She went over and crouched down. Stretching out her hand, she touched the blood and sniffed.

"Open the door." She adjusted her body to the best position and said to Arisa.

The latter nodded and carefully opened the door.

Creak…after a very slight sound.

A bloody figure was lying down outside the front door.

Isaros who had prepared herself went over and slightly kicked the bloody figure.

"This man seems a little familiar..."

The bloody man laid motionless on the ground, seemingly unconscious.

"Sis, this man seems to be that Mister Vagabond…?" Arisa said cautiously.

"That Pu-something…" Isaros was reminded of him, the mysterious homeless guy she saw before.

"He must have met some trouble…he lost a lot of blood, we have to help him!" Arisa said. Her compassionate heart was triggered again, especially towards someone she had met before.

"Arisa, we must not cause trouble." Isaros said seriously, "The skill this person displayed last time, not even I can deal with it. If there is someone who can injure him to this extent, then that person is not someone we can cope with. This is beyond my ability, we must send him out."

"But sis, he's hurt this badly…" Arisa also knew this situation was too much for them, but she could not bear to leave this man lying here unconscious with his injuries. "He's going to die!"

She pleaded, "After we wake him up, we can let him go, please?"

"This is already more than I can handle," Isaros said seriously.

"But Sis…he's hurt so badly, he's going to die…" Arisa crouched beside the man and pleaded softly.

Looking at her little sister's teary eyes, Isaros finally relented and nodded.

"Fine, drag him inside quickly, I'll handle the traces of blood!"

"Yay! Sis is the best!" Arisa knew that the situation was very serious. She immediately started dragging the man to the living room slowly.

Isaros got a mop to clean up the blood and sprayed some air freshener. Her action was as though she was used to it. She looked around carefully and only then she closed the door.

"The plan was to meet up with the Thomas family's bro Garen." Isaros frowned while looking at her little sister wiping the blood from the man's face.

"We must send him to the hospital!" Arisa also frowned, but she was looking at the wounds on the man's body. She used to deal with her sister's wounds and was very experienced in this field.

Carefully inspecting the wounds, Arisa gave out her judgment.

"Seem to be wounds from the claws of a beast. The wounds are deep but they'll heal well."

She quickly found disinfectant, gauze, and bandages.

"We can only do some first aid and send him to the hospital immediately."

"No!"

The man suddenly woke up with his eyes wide open and grasped at Arisa's wrist.

"Don't…go…hospital…"

His cleaned up face was handsome yet pale. There was no trace of blood, on the contrary, his face was pale green and traces of black could be seen.

Both his eyes were bloodshot. His gaze contained desire and was locked on Arisa's white wrist, specifically on the blood vessels standing out against her pale skin.

However, rationality stopped him from doing so.

Trying very hard to turn away his line of sight, he loosened his hold on Arisa's hand with an apologetic look. The sisters seemed to be a little frightened.

"Sorry, seems like I scared you just now. My condition right now is very weak, very weak. So sorry, I'll leave immediately. I won't bring trouble to you girls."

He struggled to stand up but it was useless. As soon as he stood up, with a snap, his body fell to a side.

"Ah!" Arisa exclaimed while covering her mouth.

The man's left knee bone broke with a crack sound and bent into an unnatural angle towards the back.

"Never mind, it's going to heal soon." The man did not seem to mind his broken bones at all and sat down on the floor. "It's going to heal very soon… no problem."

"Your leg…!!" Arisa did not know what to say. Her wide opened eyes kept staring at the indifferent man, her heart in a mess.

Isaros, who stood at the side, had a face of admiration. This kind of injuries was actually disregarded by him. This man, regardless of his past and identity, he was a tough guy worthy of admiration.

"I must leave here immediately, or you girls will be dragged into trouble!" The man revealed a bitter smile while he spoke.

Isaros quietly looked into his eyes and could feel his sincerity. The latter truly did not want to drag them into trouble.

"No need to hurry, is someone pursuing you?" she opened her mouth and asked.

The man nodded. "Yes, they are very strong and I'm not their opponent. The police forces are helpless. They can forcibly shut down any public forces," his face showed helplessness as he talked.

Suddenly his expression changed as if he had detected something.

"Coming! They're coming! Careful!!"

He struggled to his feet.

"You girls hide somewhere quickly, I'll deal with them!! They're…" he shouted while standing up.

He had not finished speaking before he was stunned at the sight of Isaros taking out a rifle from a vase. She took a shot at the left wall without looking at where she aimed at.

Peng!!

Peng peng peng peng!!

Without any change in expression, she pulled the trigger continuously.

Countless bullets flew past. None of the bullets hit the wall but struck a dark young man. Wherever his figure passed, he was shot at by the rifle.

This man had originally been aiming for Arisa's neck, but he'd been mowed down by the rifle. His chest was shot to pieces with his blood splattering and scattering everywhere.

After Isaros' bullets were spent, she casually tossed the rifle aside and withdrew a black dagger from the handle of a door at the side. This time, she lunged towards the right side with her face impassively.

Chi!

The black dagger drew a dark line and stabbed into the forehead of a woman behind her.

The latter had just appeared behind her and had no opportunity to do anything before her eyes went wide and her body stood motionless.

Hua!

Two killers collapsed instantly and turned into two piles of black ashes.

"They're…very strong…" Only now did that man finished the rest of his sentence…

He looked at the two piles of black ashes on the floor and turned to look at the expressionless Isaros and Arisa.

He suddenly felt that humans were terrifying…

Two vampires were done in instantly by a weak-looking girl. This totally crushed the outlook on his world, his life and his thoughts so far!

"Sorry to have scared you," Isaros said while stowing her dagger and looking strangely at the black ashes on the floor. She frowned and said, "Can you explain why their bodies turned to ashes when they died?"

"Sis has an ability to sense impending danger. Though these two are fast, they have no skill at all. Compared to the opponents Sis had to deal with in the past…they are too weak." Arisa shrugged while looking indifferent.

They had survived in the past with only their ordinary human bodies and grew up until today, naturally, they were not so simple. Not only her Sis, she also had an ability.

"Compared to this, we're more interested in why they had turned into ashes when they died?" Isaros repeated her previous question.

The man gave a wry smile.

"Looks like I have encountered some amazing people…let me introduce myself again, my true name is Pritto, Pritto Scarlet Moon. I am a member of the ancient Scarlet Moon Blood Breeds."

"Blood Breeds?" Isaros frowned and said.

"This wasn't your name last time right?" Arisa pointed out. "Although it's also Pu-something?"

"Sorry…last time was a fake name. I was afraid that you girls would be dragged into this, so I didn't give out my real name."

Pritto's face grew paler.

In this short span of time, the injuries all over his body had healed a lot.

He walked over and looked at the unlucky vampire duo's ashes and was speechless for a while.

"Even if I didn't want it to happen, you girls still got involved. They are on to you now."

"Are they hard to deal with?" Isaros said calmly, "Blood Breed… Just like the vampire in the legend? I've heard of it before but I thought it was just some fairy tale, it was real?"

"But shouldn't the Blood Breeds be handsome and beautiful?" Arisa was puzzled at the side and asked.

"You girls…you girls are not worried?" Pritto did not know whether to laugh or cry, staring at the sisters who did not feel a shred of pressure.

"Worry? These small fries are not hard to deal with. Why should we worry?" Isaros casually explained and began to reload the bullets in the rifle. "Just what is going on? You explain properly."

Over the years, she had grown from the hunted into the hunter. Deadly threats to other people were just an everyday occurrence for both of the sisters. She was just upset to be involved in a dispute that had nothing to do with them.

"This matter can only be explained slowly…" Pritto smiled bitterly and explained.

"From the ancient times, Blood Breeds have been divided into two factions, the light party and the secret party and I am one of the Blood Breed subordinates serving the leader, Scarlet Moon in the light party…"

"Then the ones after you came from the secret party?" Isaros had seen various formidable killer techniques. Some techniques looked like magic and so she did not show much reaction to the Blood Breeds because she treated them as some sort of mutant.

"Yes, those two were just the lowest level vampires…"Pritto said, "This place is no longer safe, I'm afraid we'll have to move."

Chapter 637: Vigilance 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Garen, where did you put the shampoo? Why can't I find it?" Trish's loud voice called.

Garen was sitting in the living room watching an entertainment program that also served as an education program on the TV. The fat host laughed loudly and started pulling some idols up to the stage to answer some weird questions, while laughter could be heard offstage.

‘Your Mom is calling you, you're not going?'

Garen changed the channel expressionlessly. "Ask Vivien, she washed her hair yesterday."

"Come and help me search for it! I can't find it!" Trish's voice was heard again.

‘Your Mom is calling you, isn't it bad not to go?'

Garen stood up and went to the bathroom to get the shampoo hidden in the drawer under the sink.

‘This is not the shampoo your Mom wants right? I remember she prefers that little red bottle of the Griffin brand' Black Sethe continued without getting tired.

"I say, why do you remember what kind of shampoo my Mom use?!" Garen finally could not take it anymore.

‘Because the scent they give out is different. It's true and you should believe me, I am not wrong on this.'

"Garen! This is not the shampoo I want!! Where's my red Griffin shampoo? Help me find it!" Trish's voice came at the same time.

Garen rolled his eyes and went back to the drawer to search again. Then, he handed it over to Trish who had her head covered in foam.

‘Know the thirteen ways to open a drawer? And the 256 methods to manufacture a drawer.'

"I don't care about your drawer manufacturing methods. Can't you say something useful?" Garen helplessly said.

‘Well, you have to understand that it's been thousands of years since the last time I have spoken. My True Soul in the Mother Stream can communicate with you. This is simply a miracle among miracles. Even the probability of a meteor the size of a sesame seed dropping down on your head can't compare to this. You have to be understanding.' Black Sethe explained. ‘Did you know? I was called the messenger of wisdom in Ancient Ender. Everyone was interested in listening to my enlightening teachings. They all praised me and revered me. Hence, you should feel honored to have me pointing out directions at every moment. This is something that countless people dreamed of.'

Garen continued to roll his eyes. He went back to the living room to watch his TV. Of course, that was what he displayed on the surface. He was actually practicing the Deep Control Technique that Black Sethe mentioned before. It was a training technique used to hunt Void Creatures.

Before getting this set of skills, Black Sethe had requested him to not close the communication channel between them and to maintain it without any hindrance. Now, he regretted…

He could never imagine how touching and exciting it was for a talkative person, who had been unable to talk for thousands of years, to finally be able to unleash and vent all he wanted.

When Black Sethe finally showed his true colors, he could talk non-stop for half an hour on the topic of a vase. Starting from the manufacturing methods and the various magical vases he had seen, to the love story he had with someone because of a vase. He could even link it to an ancient spirit with a strong will that had possessed a vase and yet ended up smashed by a little maid due to her carelessness and had a tragic end… The unit of measurement for all these nonsense could only be truckloads and he was certain that there were no repetitions.

Was this the so-called 'one flower for one world'? (TLnote: Literal translation, this is a verse from a poem. )

From one flower, he could talk about the whole world, just how high was his talking skill to reach this level?

Garen finally chose to ignore him.

If you chose to respond to him, he would get even more excited. He could talk about the feeling when you ate an apple, which race would get poisoned by apples and which Secret Technique would be severely affected by apples. There was once a Five Apples Religion that preached about eating five apples a day as a concept of immortality…

"I say, Black Sethe." Garen switched to another channel while observing his Attribute pane. The Intelligence attribute did not weaken anymore but now Vitality was affected. His Vitality had decreased by 0.1 and became 2.8.

‘…Do you know the history of tea tables? I have seen tea tables worshipped as a holy artifact in a different world. They felt that that tea table contained powerful wisdom and strength. There, I saw a tea table with a height of two, three hundred meters, and the space even with kettles and cups on top could allow hundreds of people to live there! That kingdom was called Tea Table and their king called himself the King of Tea Table. Their nobles were craftsmen that could create the highest grade of tea tables. Countless people would even sell their children to acquire the manufacturing method of the tea tables, all of it was to become a noble and gain riches…'

"Black Sethe…I'm not interested in the story of Tea Table Kingdom…" Garen felt like he finally understood the reason this guy was one of the forty-two Demon Kings… Even a master that had trained Secret Technique to its peak like him felt his head swelling, and his mind was foggy and disordered.

‘Know the one hundred and eight origins of how stories came to be? Let me tell you, the first came from ancient myths, I personally did research on it…'

"I…" Garen could feel his ears buzzing and his limit approaching. He held endless regret towards his promise with Black Sethe to maintain the communication channel between them.

He had never imagined how talkative one person could be.

"I wanted to ask, when will the Void Creature come and when can I begin?" Garen heard his words being engulfed by a torrent of sound, just like throwing a pebble into the sea, not even the slightest ripple could be seen.

"Fine…" Garen gave up on his intention to communicate with him normally.

He was completely unable to associate the current Black Sethe with the previous insane man that had tried to take over his body.

While pretending to watch TV, he continued to wait for the possible sneak attack from the void creature.

The opponent would try to weaken him through sneak attacks and let him die naturally. This was the normal practice for void creatures, as it would not cause any rebound from the laws of any world. There was no trace to be found.

How to catch the void creature and dig out its core? This problem would be handed over to Black Sethe to solve. Garen could not do anything to it just yet. After settling this void creature, he would take some time to train until a certain level to become a true Void Pursuer.

Now Garen lacked time, sufficient time.

Void creatures were masters of illusion and dream. Without sufficient ability to differentiate between illusion and reality, he could only be a sitting duck.

For now, Garen could only be a bait, a bait to lure out the void creature.

He was sitting on the sofa watching TV unenthusiastically.

Jason had gone hunting with his friends, Little Vivien was shaking her legs in her room while reading a book and listening to music and Trish had to go out and pick up her friend in a while. Her best friend had come over to their little town for vacation. His Dad, Emmer was sitting in front of computer typing something.

There was only him alone sitting on the sofa watching TV in broad daylight and it was also a dull variety show that Little Vivien despised.

He sat on the sofa and made himself as comfortable as possible. Without him realizing, he was getting sleepy and his eyelids were getting heavier.

Black Sethe's voice beside his ears gradually became unclear and then turned into something similar to the buzzing sound of bees and slowly drifted farther away.

Time passed by.

‘It's here!' A voice suddenly jerked him awake.

He felt hazy. He did not know why but he could not lift his spirits, as though he was still in a half-asleep state.

Black Sethe's voice sounded beside his ears.

‘For any creature with intelligence, their mind is divided into two parts. Their self-consciousness and subconsciousness. If a person's self-consciousness has a strong sense of reasoning and self-control, then their subconsciousness will be more casual and indulgent. The more it is oppressed by the self-consciousness, the more it bounces back. And obviously, that's the kind of person you are.'

"Me?"

‘Your control over your self-consciousness is strong. This also means that when you are in a state similar to sleeping, your subconsciousness that takes over the body control will be in an extremely casual and indulging state. This is the accumulation of your desires that were suppressed by your self-consciousness and what your subconsciousness was always trying to find ways to vent. A person needs balance. You have to understand that suppressing yourself and putting yourself in an unbalanced state in order to reach the state you want is to change yourself. Changes require a new kind of balance. It is an instinct to survive and also a law of the universe. Life has always been a cycle of balance.' Black Sethe lectured.

"What do I have to do now?" Garen said. He looked around in a daze. Amidst the trance, he was still lying on the sofa in the middle of the living room but he did not know since when the white sofa had become a tattered sofa. A little mouse was lying on his left side sleeping soundly.

In the TV in front of him, a singer's face had been stretched to look like a horse. He only had an impression of the shiny thick necklace that was hung around his neck. That necklace made him feel familiar.

‘Don't care about anything else. Just leave it to me. Observe your dream, this is your dream, look at it closely.'

Black Sethe's voice slowly began to sound distant and became smaller.

Garen sat alone on the sofa in a daze. He did not want to do anything. An inexplicable sense of laziness filled his whole body. He felt very very tired. He just wanted to plop down on the sofa and continue to sleep.

Wa!!

Suddenly, a frog-like bellow woke him up from his daze.

Garen opened his eyes and found that he was lying on the sofa. Trish was gently covering him with a blanket. Realizing that he was awake, Trish smiled.

"Sleep more if you're tired. I'll call you for dinner."

Garen nodded and watched Trish walked away while wiping his hair with a dry towel.

‘Awake now?' Black Sethe's voice sounded.

Chapter 638: Vigilance 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Have you succeeded?" Garen asked.

'Just an ordinary Void Worm. Your luck is not bad, this guy's intelligence is pretty low. It only knows how to steal your dream's image of your life to make you lower your vigilance so it can paralyze your nerves. No wonder its corruption is so low.' Black Sethe said with a tone that suggested Garen was extremely lucky.

"This is still low?" Garen was surprised. He used his hands to feel the texture of the sofa in details. It was firm and the texture felt delicate with a slightly cool temperature. All of this clearly conveyed to him that he was not dreaming right now.

'Of course, Void Worms are known as the weakest among the Void Creatures. Meaning that they are as weak as roadside bugs. When we go in and out of the void, sometimes we may unintentionally trample a bunch of them.'

Black Sethe answered like it was natural.

Garen was speechless. He was unable to imagine the strength of these Demon Kings when they were at their peak.

'Look at your ring.'

When Garen heard this, he looked down at his black ring. On top of that black ring inlaid with red jewels, there was now a small purple-black crystal sticking to it. The crystal was the size of a fingernail. The surface had a texture similar to that of wood but it was translucent.

Using his right hand to take off the piece of crystal, he felt that this crystal was just like it had grown out of the ring, similar to plucking mushrooms.

Pinching that crystal, Garen took a sniff at it. There was a faint aroma of milk.

'This is Void Crystal also known as Void Core. It's a crystal produced inside Void Creatures. Some research states that it's the crystallization of Void Creature's energy of life but my personal opinion is that this is just a dense bone left over from the Void Creatures. Whatever it is, this can relieve your body's weakening condition.' Black Sethe explained.

"How do I use it?"

'You can eat it or use demonic technique to absorb its vitality, it's up to you.'

"May I take a look at the corpse of the Void Worm?" Garen was quite curious about the Void Creature.

'Unfortunately, you can't see it. Void Creatures are mostly vague shadows or mist. Rarely are there any corpses after their death.' Black Sethe said casually. 'Maybe you'll meet them in the future, but not now.'

Garen considered for a moment then put the crystal into his right hand's glove and let it be absorbed by the demonic technique, Slaughtering Hand.

"And then?" He asked.

'Then, your weakening will not go on. It will temporarily stop and on the fifth day, it will be lifted completely, that's all.' Black Sethe answered. 'After this, you can choose your path.'

"What path?"

'The path of Warlocks, Secret Technique or summon and control. It's all up to you. Of course, these two are just a rough classification. If you want to walk the path of practicing Secret Techniques then you can choose one Secret Technique and focus on it while continuously hunt the Void Creatures to hone your martial arts. Your Secret Technique has reached a very high level. Even in our time, you can be considered as a class of your own. If you choose choose summon and control, then you can collect Void Core to use as your summon army. In the future, you can even manage multiple summons of the ancient True Soul's imprint to form a legion.'

'Simply put, this are two general paths, either go with strengthening your body or increasing numbers.'

"Didn't I make my choice long ago?" Garen answered.

'True.'

　

******************

Grano, Faya state, State Underground Blood Union Hall.

The wide, golden, dome-shaped hall was brightly lit. The hall that was large enough for ten thousand people was currently occupied by hundreds of people.

Standing on top of the white stage was a gentle-looking young man wearing white-framed glasses. He wore a white suit and his hair was combed back. With a charming and gentle smile on his face, he stood on the white stage as a confident speaker with a style of his own.

Facing the buzzing crowd with hundreds of different gazes, the young man maintained his composure.

"In lieu of the recent rampant activities of the secret party, an order of suppression came from above. After repeated ineffective warnings, they have openly taken the most extreme action of disregarding all measures of prevention and caused the deaths of fifteen of our compatriots. As the governor of the Blood Union of Faya State, I express my deepest regrets and condolences. I received the news today that Scarlet Moon himself had received severe injuries and his subordinates everywhere have been hunted down. Pale Leaders have issued a general notice to all. Two months later, all light party members will move to hunt down the members of secret party. Any action to conceal or assist the secret party will be sentenced to two hundred years of non-blood imprisonment. I hope that everyone has reflected. Please quickly deal with anything out-of-the-line so as not to cause any unnecessary misunderstandings."

The buzzing sounds gradually quieted down. One of the three only Faya State upper-level Blood Breeds, a bejeweled white-haired old lady, stood up.

"Against the rampant action of the secret party, I think that the first action we should take is to protect Scarlet Moon's direct lineage. They are now being hunted down. Why is our tracking imprint unable to find their location? I feel that there are people inside the Blood Union interfering and causing damage. We should do a thorough inspection on the Blood Union Intelligence Department!"

After speaking, she sat down with the help of a little girl beside her.

"I agree with Madam Vanessa's view." Another upper-level Blood Breed stood up to speak. This was a radiant middle-aged man with a fit body, wearing a black suit and dark red tie.

""Faya State is ranked at the bottom among the country's 32 states, from the status of our economy or our geography and population. Yet, even in such a region, we could not find any blood relatives of Scarlet Moon and also couldn't contact them. This is definitely a problem with the Blood Union Intelligence Department. I suspect someone is using the Intelligence Department to prevent our tracking. If there is no proper explanation for this, we'll have to pull out our forces in the Intelligence Department to form our own investigation team."

This remark immediately received approvals from a large number of middle-level Blood Breeds.

The Blood Union was originally composed of the clan members of the various clans of Blood Breeds. Every clan played a part in in it. If there really were withdrawals due to this, the so-called Blood Union would become an empty shell.

The state governor and state leader of the Blood Union, which was the bespectacled man, frowned.

"Isn't it too early to make such radical remarks? Mr. Henderick, although the Blood Union has not done a good job in this matter, handling other matters has always been our most solid backing. We cannot dissolve the Blood Union due to such a little problem, this is too extreme. Regarding the tracking information, I will take measures as soon as possible. A thorough inspection will be conducted on the Intelligence Department. I can't do anything about other states but the Faya State will give you a satisfactory answer within three months!"

The state governor said decisively.

"Good! Then we'll wait three months!" said the middle-aged man, Henderick and sat down exchanging a few glances with Madam Vanessa not far from his seat.

Half an hour later…..

After the meeting was concluded, the crowd exited the hall into the corridor towards the elevator.

Behind Henderick were more than ten middle-level and low-level Blood Breeds. He deliberately slowed down and lagged behind to walk with Madam Vanessa.

The groups around them gradually merged and made a safe environment for them.

Henderick, with a cigarette in his hand, took a puff and blew out two lines of green smoke through his nostrils.

"Looks like the hands of the secret party are stretched far… I've decided to let Aier investigate the situation. Five hundred years ago, I owed a debt to Scarlet Moon. I can't just watch him walk into danger."

Vanessa was holding a slender white cane and walked with a trembling gait.

"The Tomb's Crow Aier? He is your best subordinate… Isn't he going to be promoted to upper-level soon? I remember that one hundred and twenty years ago, he'd reached the peak of middle-level."

"Soon, but promoting one to upper-level isn't so easy. Perhaps there will be hope in two hundred years' time." Henderick shook his head, "I will investigate this matter properly and I hope you will support me, madam. The governor's attitude is somewhat suspicious…"

"That's natural. The governor's two descendants have turned towards the secret party. One of them died by his own hands. It was still alright when the conflict between both parties had not intensified. Now, the situation has become complicated. He has become old and has no way to divide his Blood Core to make a new descendant. In the case that he loses another descendant, if anything happens to him, his position will be unstable." Vanessa sighed.

Henderick nodded to indicate his understanding.

"From the information that I gathered, there are fifteen hideouts of the secret party in this state. There are three places that are serious in the Biwinter city. The allied Witches there have already filed a request to control the Blood Breeds to my clan in advance. They've expressed dissatisfaction in the increase of the number in the secret party. I've sent my clan members there but at a great risk. I need your support, Madam."

"No problem, I will let all the person in charge to cooperate with you. Elvin, Biwinter, Kama, Sili, Grano and Marseille have the largest number of secret party members. This is the classified information that my clan members got from inside the Blood Union. I hope you'll have good results." Vanessa replied.

"I hope so, thank you very much for the information." Henderick bowed his head. Biting his cigarette, he walked slowly towards another elevator on the other side with his people.

Vanessa looked at Henderick's shrinking figure and shook her head.

"The light party has been accustomed to a gentle and peaceful life. I didn't think that even Henderick could disregard any interests and clearly state his position. But the result is not optimistic. The light party has been too accustomed to peaceful life. The more they have, the more timid they are."

The little girl beside her frowned.

"I think the biggest problem is that we can't differentiate the members of the light party from the secret party. A poisonous snake in hiding is the most terrifying."

"That's right. Remember to stay alert." Vanessa sighed.

Chapter 639: Training 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Grano

In a forest behind a small building, Garen was standing there paying attention to the surroundings and every swaying leaf and blade of grass. Wind gusted through the forest, sending the leaves dancing.

His whole body was surrounded by greens and shadows. His eyes would wander occasionally, glancing at some inconspicuous place.

‘Void Worm is just a scout. They already have their eyes on you. Now, you need to learn to deal with this sort of creature yourself.’ Black Sethe’s voice sounded beside his ear.

"What do I need to pay attention to? How do I exterminate them?" Garen asked.

‘They are just worms, very very weak, only that normal physical attacks have no effect on them. You have to cover yourself with aura. Aura is the origin of Mother Stream. It’s their nemesis. You just have to condense your aura and attack them with it. That’s how you settle them.’

‘However, the trouble now is that you cannot control yourself when you’re dreaming. Your subconsciousness is bouncing back too much and causing you to completely follow your instinct. Hence, there is one thing you have to do first, which is to raise your focus in your dreams. Otherwise, you remain too susceptible to your instinct and cannot even control your actions, nevermind your aura.’ Black Sethe said.

Garen repeated: "The first step is to train my attention in my dreams, right?"

‘Go on and try.’

"What about those ordinary people who don’t have aura? What can they do if they encounter Void Creatures?" Garen suddenly asked.

‘Search and distinguish them, or try to communicate with the risk of being contaminated to get a certain amount of knowledge about Void. Else, take the initiative to avoid them by getting out of their dreams. The flow of time they live on is different from ours. Generally, the Void Creatures live on a slower timeflow than us. Their one breath may be years for us, so don’t try to compete in patience with them. That’s what they’re good at. Some of them can even live on for more than ten thousands of years.’ Black Sethe droned on. ‘The Void Creatures usually do not take an interest in average people. If it happens, then there are only two possibilities. One is that they’re trying to pollute the human race. Because they mainly consume a constant stream of energy from biological consciousness, polluting a consciousness will make it one of their kind and a producer of their energy source. The other reason is curiosity, pure curiosity. Just like when the researchers found some ants who don’t grow antenna.’

Garen nodded to indicate his understanding of the meaning behind Black Sethe’s words. Although his explanation was redundant and long-winded, he understood the main points behind his teachings.

The trees and grass swayed and not far from him were the sounds of cars and advertisements.

Garen slowly sank his consciousness while controlling it and began to fall into a deep sleep.

His consciousness began to grow blurry. He unconsciously leaned against a large tree. His back touched the rough surface of the bark and he sat down on the soft, moist grass. The ground was slightly warm and he could smell the faint aroma of grass.

Without noticing, Garen closed his eyes and slowly fell asleep.

Chirp chirp…chirp chirp…

It seemed that there were birds chirping in the distance.

Garen opened his eyes drowsily and found himself lying on the bed at his home. There was an electric fan blowing at him. The shape of the fan was unclear. It seemed to be white and it also seemed to be made of noodles. The wind was hot and humid.

The surrounding walls seemed to be constantly flowing and its color was ever changing. It seemed to be brown in color. Garen felt dull and he did not know what he was doing. He tried to lower his head to see the pose he was in but he was unable to.

‘Put the knife back into the box.’ He suddenly had this thought and then his body floated from his bed. He found out that at the back of his room, there was an additional black knife. The knife was long and wide and its edge silvery white.

He felt himself drawing towards it and took the knife down from a shelf that came out of nowhere. After that, out of nowhere in his hand was a box and he inserted the knife into it.

Garen suddenly remembered that he had something he had to do but standing there and thinking for a long time, he just could not remembered what it was.

So, he kept on standing there and kept trying to recall. Suddenly, he felt his right leg getting itchy as though a worm was crawling on it. He tried to bend over to scratch it but he could not find his right leg.

Pa.

A drop of dew dripped on Garen’s head and slid down his nose bridge, and from his chin it rolled past his shirt collar.

Garen opened his eyes and there was a comfortable feeling all over his body.

‘Did you wake up?’ Black Sethe’s voice sounded right on time.

"Seems like I did not succeed?" Garen frowned.

‘It’s obvious that you failed.’ Black Sethe sounded happy, ‘You weren’t even aware that you were in a dream, got led around by the nose and finally you came out achieving nothing.’

"This looks troublesome." Garen frowned and said.

‘That’s for sure. Anyone who does this training has to do it for a long time. You’ll get better through practice.’

Garen stood up. He really did feel something crawling on his right foot.

He shook the leg of his pants and out came a small white ant. The ant flipped over from the ground and soon disappeared into the grass.

"This is a whole new thing." Garen said in a low voice, "But I will have a lot of time to train and deal with it."

‘Someone’s coming.’ Black Sethe’s voice quickly died down.

Garen glanced towards his left. From his point of view, he could see that on the lawn between two houses was a tall slim girl walking over. She wore white casual wear while carrying a small red bag. She had long red hair, an oval face, white skin and exuded a cold aura.

"Isaros, long time no see." Garen smiled and gave a greeting.

"Garen, you came to morning practice?" Isaros also noticed Garen, slightly startled. "Something cropped up yesterday so I didn’t go to see you."

"It’s okay. You came for some afternoon exercise?" Garen asked.

"Mm. I am used to doing so at this time." Isaros nodded.

"Now that I think of it, it’s been a year since the time we first practiced together here?" Garen walked forward a few steps and stood a few paces away from Isaros. Suddenly, his nose slightly twitched and he flashed her a strange look.

"How about a spar or two?"

Isaros’ eyes lit up.

Hu!

She did not wait for a response and went for a side kick, blowing away the air.

Pa!

Garen warded off her kick but another kick came over from the right. He continued to parry and the spar went on with the third, fourth and fifth strike!

The both of them continued with their spar with peng, peng, peng sounds.

Isaros’ speed became faster and faster. Both her legs did a series of kicks as though she’d become a spinning top. Her toes were like spinning blades that constantly brushed against Garen’s right hand.

"Watch out!"

Isaros retreated for a bit with her right knee bending up. She suddenly throw a straight kick like a cannonball forward.

Peng!

Both of them suddenly separated. Garen’s right hand went down slowly and his face showed a charming smile.

"You’ve improved again."

"Still can’t force out your second hand." Isaros slightly sweated and shook her head.

"Remember that trick I showed you?" Garen suddenly lowered his voice.

He stretched open his right hand’s fingers as though holding something. At this moment, a strange scene happened.

It was as though there was wind slowing in the middle of his palm.

Air currents as thin as strands of hair were flowing around his fingers.

These life-like invisible currents were constantly circling in the palm of his hand.

In that instant, Isaros felt her vision blur. She did not hear any sound but only saw a blur until Garen’s right hand had already reached her forehead. His thumb stretched right in front of her left eye with just a little bit of distance.

Only then did Isaros felt a slight chill.

The crisis premonition that she had always been proud of had no reaction at all this time.

"Silent Killing Technique." Garen took back his arm. His right arm lightly gripped as though holding invisible wind.

"You have an extraordinary sense for wind and air currents. You may be able to really grasp the essence of this skill."

There was nothing wrong with his words. This was definitely a technique, not a secret technique or some secret skill or secret method. This was just a simple trick, a trick to control the flow of air currents that through movements.

In theory, only those who grasped vibration skills in secret techniques could achieve it. However, Garen had discovered something special about Isaros. She was very sensitive towards the impending change in the subtle flow of air. Perhaps she might possibly be able to master this skill that applied the technique that induced airflow changes.

"Silent Killing Technique?" Isaros repeated this name. Her eyes glittered and her hands started to imitate Garen’s previous actions. Although the actions were exactly the same, not even the slightest change had occurred.

"Don’t be fooled by its name. I am a law-abiding good citizen." Garen laughed. "Then I shall go back first. You should slowly practice it."

"Okay." Isaros nodded and said but her hands were as though controlled by demons and kept repeating the previous actions.

She felt that she could learn it.

Garen laughed again while looking at her who’d been charmed and walked towards the back door of his home.

Aside from any selfish motives, he admired a gifted student like Isaros. She was someone who knew how precious these techniques were. She had almost died countless times before these seemingly simple techniques. Only those who had first-hand experience would know the value. For such a person, imparting a little bit of knowledge was reasonable.

Chapter 640: Training 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

'You seemed very optimistic about her?' Black Sethe said.

"Optimistic? No, compare to those two seeds, I just admire her." Garen shook his head.

'Those two seeds?' Black Sethe did not understand. He did not know what Garen had done in school.

Garen smiled and did not answer him.

"Isaros' skills had already gone beyond that of normal people. This is merely something that was self-taught. What if I give her some directions?"

'You are really bored.' Black Sethe said, 'The world has too many geniuses, I think you're ust bored.'

"Perhaps." Garen did not told Black Sethe that he had discover something different about Arisa and Isaros sisters. He did not explain anything and only hinted at it. Maybe, it could be put up for some good use in the future.

"We should go back."

******************

"Hochman!!!!"

A mad roar sounded.

A strong black guy waved his dagger at the bespectacled Hochman. He was like the wind, his speed very fast and even left afterimages.

An empty field near a dumpsite, Hochman quietly leaned against the side of a black car, dressed in a black windbreaker while looking coldly at the black guy who rushed over.

Peng!

A side kick mercilessly came from Hochman's right side and accurately hit the black guy's waist and made him fall to the ground.

There was a bald muscled guy with shiny muscles like it was made of metallic substance. He bumped his fists and grinned while walking out and picked the black guy off the ground.

"What a fool! He dare to go against the mighty Mr. Hochman." The bald white man laughed. His right hand that was grabbing the neck of the black guy tightened. Just like grabbing a small chick, with a kacha sound, the black guy's neck bone snapped and the light in his eyes dimmed.

Hochman lit up a cigarette and lightly took a puff.

"Is there any more that had not been settled?"

"No more, this is the last one." The bald white man bowed respectfully. He was a murderer that was casted out by his family. He who had never obeyed any of his family's commands were now like a sheep in front of this man.

"Mister's plan should be able to be carry out successfully."

"There will always be something that doesn't obey, jumping out…" Hochman lightly said, "Recently, the district has received a lot of attacks. Take some people and patrol. If there is any trouble, you settled it directly. Recently, the situation seemed a bit messy."

"Yes."

Hochman turned back to open the car door and sat on it sideways.

Gazing at the moving scenery outside the window, Garen slowly closed his eyes.

"Search for the details about the freaks who attacked us last night."

The driver sitting in front nodded slightly and did not utter any word.

Hochman slightly pondered. He could feel his secret techniques gradually reaching a breakthrough. The feeling of evolving and getting stronger was very intoxicating. Just last night, when he was doing inspection in one of his subordinate division, he unexpectedly encountered some attacks, the kind that was very strong and also proficient at using guns. His best subordinates could not even hold them back.

Hochman shot and killed several of them on the spot. Only then, the situation was stabilized but the origin of these people were still unknown.

Looking at the scenery outside the car passing by even faster, he gradually fell into deep thoughts.

******************

"If these kind of trash still come in, just kill it." Dahm stepped on the face of the people lying on the ground, his face showing disgusts. He wore a large red gender-neutrall clothes with each of the shoulders embroidered with two large black characters. Putting together, they formed the word 'Dahm'…

Around him were more than ten tall strong men bowing their heads with their complexion showing a trace of fear.

"Drag him out." Dahm stepped on the head of the man below. That step produced a kacha sound. Whether he still lived on, it was unknown.

A strong man quickly dragged away the man on the ground.

The rest urged Dahm to sit at the main seat of the conference room.

Dahm's face had become more and more feminine. He was now exuding feminine temperament all the time but there was no tenderness that could be seen in females in him. It was only sharp and blunt.

Although his temperament became more and more neutral but the angular face of a man was still the same. Yet, he still put on a red lipstick, faint purple eye shadow and a thin foundation. He pierced his ears and wore two shining diamond earrings.

"Recently, there were a lot people trying to break into our headquarters. They're really seeking death. The government has send people to help us but I refused them. Coincidentally, I am lacking some experimental materials. My Non-faced Waterbird Fist has not been perfected yet. I need some living people to try it."

He deliberately let out a false voice that did not sound like a male. It was very shrill. People who heard it would feel their skin crawling.

"Marshal Dahm, those people who tried to break through has very fast speed. We heard the news from a few sources of information that they are most likely people from Macquarie Organization and they have a huge backing."

"Huge?" Dahm chuckled. He already knew the identities of those intruders. He got the message from his family not long ago. Macquarie Organization was now very ambitious and planned to expand aggressively. Their company belonged to the grey side, a mix of black and white.

"There really are someone who seek death by trying to go against us?" Dahm stuck out his tongue and licked his fingers. "Macquarie Organization hired some mercenaries and thought that by breaking the rules, they would be able to win? Ridiculous."

"But these are just minor problems. The main problem is with Hochman." Dahm's line of sight went to the woman sitting at the end of the table.

"Hochman had also been attacked but we don't know who the opponent is." The woman promptly answered.

Dahm felt around his chin seeming to be searching for stubbles that had not been shaven clean.

The surrounding subordinates were now on their toes. They were scared of him. Dahm's mood was well-known. Disobey him a little, he would take it out on you. Most of the time he would just pat you lightly on the back, then you would discover that you were urinating blood. The second day you would have kidney failure and lie in the hospital forever.

Rumors had it that he and Hochman came from the same organization called combat club. Both had become their respective families' leading figures and owned more than half of their families' inheritance. Some people who disobeyed them would be change to their people.

"Where's that cute little apple?" Dahm suddenly asked.

"She had safely left America. Now she had been sent by our people to Asia. We're not sure about the specific location." A subordinate promptly answered.

"I really want to see what Hochman would look like when he knew about this…" The corner of Dahm's lips curled.

He did not notice that his skin was becoming whiter and transparent.

Illusory Spinning White Jade, the fourth level of the illusion and adding the seed that had sprouted inside his body had allowed his body to integrate his spirit, consciousness and aura into one and made him reached an unprecedented strength.

"Marshal! There's another challenger!" A shout from a subordinate came from outside the door. "It's the Golden Belt Underground Fighter King, Leidman from Eastern Europe."

Dahm stood up.

"Looks like another material for experiment had come for the bounty…" He licked his lips. Under the gaze of everyone standing up, he walked out of the conference room.

**************

Time flies.

Garen had come back to school for more than half a year.

He did not go to the combat club. Most of the time, his whereabouts was unknown. He was no longer living in the dormitory but he went out to rent a house.

Apart from the normal daily classes, he gradually lowered his presence. His main focus was now training in his dreams. The first step was training himself to understand that he was in a dream. This step had stopped him for a few months.

Maybe his talent in this area was not that good. Such a slow progress disappointed him.

From the information that he got about the mercenary industry from the Nighthawk Mercenary intelligence network, the mercenary industry now had some rumors about a mysterious group called the Combat Club.

It was rumored that every fighters that came out of Combat Club were elites. Among the rumors was about Combat Club's Xander who accidentally killed too much and disappear. After his total disappearance, the rumors about Combat Club were becoming widespread.

Under the threat of being shot by guns, Xander killed six people and disappeared without a single injuries. With the threat from guns, yet he was still able to kill six people. This had no doubt made a stir in the world of fighters and mercenaries.

In addition, there were also Dahm and Hochman who came from the Combat Club. Both were ferocious, powerful and terrifying. Guns could not do anything to them with their skills. They had totally reached an inhuman realm.

As both of them became stronger and more well-known rumors about the mysterious and powerful Combat Club were also growing. When they ceased to go to the school's Combat Club, it had become an empty shell. Even so, there were still quite some people coming over.

Garen also did not expect this situation. Dahm and Hochman becoming so powerful and progressing so fast were partly due to him. The power they used was largely centered on the seed of his soul.

The disputes among Blood Breeds did not spread to this state. To be more accurate, the states that were in this direction were not involve in any movement as if they were in a totally separate world.

Garen did not pay attention to these slow-paced changes. He focused everything on training in his dreams. The probability of success were not high. Out of ten times, only three times were successful. There was a need to keep stressing to himself that he was about to fall asleep before he really slept, but it seemed to not be effective.

Black Sethe suggested to use some medicine to assist him but Garen rejected it.

Black Sethe suggested another way which was to focus on looking at his hands. Before falling asleep, carefully remembered the details of his own hands and then in his dreams, he only need to think of looking at his hands.

This method seemed more effective. After trying several times, the success rate slowly increased.

However, sometimes he would get distracted by stray thoughts and the strange vision inside his dreams, then he would get drifted to some unknown place.

Unfortunately, he could not enter his dreams at will. Only when he wanted to rest his body would he be able to do so. Otherwise, the biological clock in his body would go into disorder.

Chapter 641: Ambushed 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Due to the fact that the time could not be adjusted freely, most of the time was spent on waiting for the exhaustion of his physical energy. Due to his suspiciousness, Garen did not continue to practice Slaughtering Hand. He had been vigilant towards Black Sethe although Black Sethe was quite harmless on the surface. However, he could not forget the situation where the original Black Sethe tried to seize his body. If it was not for his Seed of Soul, together with Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique suppressing the fragment of soul, the result might be different now.

‘It’s useless, Slaughtering Hand is a very strong Demon Technique against the Void Creatures. You have trained it until this point and yet you’re trying to convert, don’t you think it’s a pity?’ Black Sethe said after he saw through his plan.

"Towards something that might bring me harm, I’ve never felt pity because giving up on it is not my loss but my luck." Garen answered.

He was sitting cross-legged in a spacious wooden hall. The hall was actually a large dance hall renovated into a hall for him to meditate.

He spent six hundreds Gallon per month which was equivalent to Earth’s U.S. dollars. However, compared to the quiet environment and the large space now, the price was nothing.

‘Worrying about this and that, hehe, Void Creatures will not give you the time to worry. Their intelligence are stronger than the other and their numbers are getting larger. When your progress can’t keep up with the opening of the void cracks, you can only die.’ Black Sethe laughed.

Garen was too lazy to bother with him. He closed his eyes and continue to observe the situation inside his body.

He had spent a great deal of time to observe the state of his Slaughtering Hand Demonic Technique. Although he did not find any harmful parts, but some subtle uncontrollable parts had become quite obvious. This made him stop the training of the Slaughtering Hand.

Now, he began to think of his future path.

He came from White Cloud Gate and trained in Mammoth Secret Technique. After that, he trained in Golden Statue Technique and achieved an unprecedented realm and reached the legendary Divine Statue Technique. He mastered the secret technique and no longer had an opponent. Even if it was Sylphalan, he had the self-confidence that at most they would just take down each other.

On secret technique, although he had an ability to shorten the time needed for growth but there were a lot of things that needed to be understood. In the face of death, whether what he had could help in his survival, all depended on himself.

These things were not imaginary but real growth.

Garen recalled his experience of growth step-by-step.

At the Totem World, the more he saw the vastness and mysteriousness of the universe, the more he was awed by it. In this world, even the civilizations as strong as Warlock’s vanished. Only the universe was everlasting and unchanged.

His original arrogance and pride slowly subsided and became a thirst for knowledge and exploration.

Finally, in the totem world, he lost everything that he was familiar with due to the power of time. Once again, he understood the power of time, the vast power of the universe could change anything.

Arriving at this world, he felt real peace and quiet. There was not much deceptions and not much of the survival of the fittest rule. It was mostly a peaceful growth from childhood until now. Even if there were Blood Breeds and Witches, they were all hiding without interfering with the humans. Although the place they interfered with looked wide, in fact, if it was carefully counted, it would only be small area. Ninety percent of the area were places to live and work. Most people did not have much twists and turns. They only lived honestly, day by day, year by year.

Putting aside the little bit of extraordinary power, this world was actually just an enlarged version of the original Earth. If no one took the initiative to touch that extraordinary force, for the rest of the region, they could pick any single place and still lived out the rest of their life peacefully as a common person.

However, this was not what he wanted.

"What do I want?" Garen asked himself.

"I just want to witness this world, this universe, from the bottom to the top, from the humble to the great. Just to take a look at what they are." He answered himself. "I don’t want to come to this world without knowing anything and then die without knowing anything…"

His heart was unwilling. He savored this unwillingness. It seemed that was source of power that moved him up till this day.

Black Sethe was still nagging beside his ear but he did not know what he was talking about.

Garen was just silently in a trance as though he had heard nothing. As though he was isolated from all sound leaving only the sound of his beating heart.

That kind of deep unwillingness was as if a volcano that was about to erupt, full of thick and hot lava, exerting pressure in his chest.

Following this flow of power that originate from inside him, he recalled all the hundreds and thousands of secret techniques and various knowledge.

Excluding Slaughtering Hand, his secret techniques that was created and perfected by him and Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique that came from Black Water True Technique that went through numerous evolutions and fusion of two Living Secret Technique seeds to become a peak Living Secret Technique and Divine Statue Technique that went through various trials to become a peak skill were the two secret techniques that were most familiar to him.

"Since Slaughtering Hand belonged to yin element, then I should practice a secret technique of yang element to slightly bring back the balance." Garen pondered and began to search for a yang element secret technique in his mind. Secret Techniques that could enter his eyes were at least those with extraordinary origin or having very high potential and covered wide range of uses.

However, those which could reach the level of the Divine Statue Technique were rare. Higher level secret technique like Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique numbered even less. Perhaps, only Slaughtering Hand could reach this level.

As a result, his choice was very little.

"Extreme Heat Palm, the type that had no special effects. It should not be restricted in this world but it was only at the level of the Divine Statue Technique."

Garen slightly hesitated but then treated it as though passing his free time. Extreme Heat Palm did not have much of a special effects and only belonged to middle grade secret techniques. Due to the fact that its cultivation period was very long and yet the results were not that good, it should be categorized under cultivation techniques for health. Its advantage was that it could provide warmth to the body. It could counter the yin nature of the Slaughtering Hand and the Seed of Soul.

However, the level of Extreme Heat Palm was not high. This was because its creator did not have a high cultivation level. The greatest characteristics were prolonging lifespan to more than a hundred years and its attacks were continuous and full of vitality. The overall improvement to the body’s quality was about the same as the previous version of Divine Statue Technique, the Golden Statue Technique. Garen did not felt any interests towards its supporting footwork technique and palm technique.

All he needed was the warmth that was provided by technique.

Coincidentally, the cultural relics had almost arrived. He was going to get a large number of Potential points.

Garen took out his phone to check whether Bald head’s message.

The relics had arrived. Someone had sent it to his rented house in the suburbs but it was robbed in the middle of the journey and there was not a lot left.

"Please rest assured. Those that dare to provoke the Nighthawk will be personally handle by me." Bald head Kaedun said. Ever since he came back from Africa, he had become more confident.

After sending a reply to Bald head, Garen dialed another subordinate, Jay’s number.

"Jay, where are you now?"

"Reaching the Faya state, Boss." Jay who was in charge of the Black Uniform’s affairs said, "Someone intercepted us this time, we’re very sorry…"

"The problem this time was not due to you. Both of you can decide on these matters yourselves. What about the matter I want you to investigate?" Garen interrupted him. They could just robbed the relics back. Perhaps only those Black Uniform’s men knew about this secret.

"We investigated it clearly. The previous person-in-charge, Levi’s daughter, Aileen is now twelve years old. She’s studying in Medanslain Private School in Yorkshire, England. She’s a very pretty little mixed-blood girl. Now, she’s under the care of her mother Besna. The father, Levi Kennyton was an international businessman have some fame."

"What about the people? Since I promised Levi, I should take good care of her." Garen asked.

"Originally, Black Uniform Organization had ordered some people to protect Aileen. With the collapse of the organization, I continued to maintain the previous order. The people are still maintaining the protection. No changes there." Jay reported.

"Bring her over. With her father’s identity and enmity, she is doomed to be unable to live a peaceful life. We can’t always protect her. Right, generally who are his enemies? The kind that would tried to attack his wife and daughter."

"England’s Earth Dragon and his small group had received huge damage from him, and the Germany’s Heavy Infantry Army is an organization specialize in killing and India’s Nagas also had some grudges against Levi…" Once Jay began talking, it was non-stop.

Garen finally understood why Levi was willing to exchange his biggest secret for his daughter’s safety. Just look at these organizations and killers that hated him to the core, with a casual mention, there were at least seven or eight famous names in the list not to mention those who were hidden in the dark.

"Pay attention to how you deal with this matter. Do not let me down. When you encounter any problem that you could not handle, report it directly to me."

"Understood."

The phone disconnected.

Garen kept his phone.

‘You collect relics?’ Black Sethe began.

Garen was lazy to care about him. This guy belonged to the type which the more you talk with him, the more he got into it. If you kept ignoring him, he would quiet down. Besides, matters concerning relics was his biggest secret, naturally he would not talk about it.

‘You really think that you are safe and can ignore the threats from the Void Creatures now?’ Black Sethe continued. ‘The truth is there is one more bad news which I haven’t tell you.’

Garen stood up.

"What news?"

‘Hehe. It’s something I found out after killing the previous Void Worm. I was afraid that you would get scared and so I did not tell you in advance.’ Black Sethe said.

Garen did not speak and just waited for him. Under normal circumstances, he would be tempted to let out the news himself.

Sure enough, he could not hold himself back a minute later.

‘I found out that Void Worm was not a solitary organism. It belonged to a colony, a race.’

"Your point is that, killing the worm would invite more trouble?" Garen asked. He walked out of the room without hurrying and closed the door behind him. He slowly walked along the corridor and could occasionally see some other people.

‘That was a predator race. They have a strict hierarchy just like the colonies of bees and ants forming a synergistic group. Messing with one of them means messing with the whole lot of them.’ Black Sethe gloated, ‘I think you’ll meet some trouble soon.’

Chapter 642: Ambushed 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen fell silent.

‘Did you think your Soul Seed and Secret Techniques could triumph against them? Don't be naive.' Black Sethe laughed sarcastically. 'Only techniques that specifically counters against illusions would truly be able to go against them, the current you is still leagues away from them! Without my protection, you're just a blob of delicious cake!"

"Then why would you protect me? I don't recall asking for help?" Garen walked out of the corridor slowly, exited the complex entrance of his rented unit and began walking down the steps.

Black Sethe seemed to be speechless.

‘Do you think I wanted it? Isn't it all because I'm bound to you! I'm also a goner if you croaked, did you think I protected you willingly?!'

"And then?"

‘And then you actually thought about giving up practicing the Slaughtering Hand! Give up on making me stronger! This is actually an innate Secret Technique that would make both of us stronger simultaneously, yet you want to give up on it?!' Black Sethe suddenly fumed.

‘Do you even know how much more troublesome it would be after this? Do you even know how much effort I have to put in in order to take care of these trashes? You don't even….' He fell silent abruptly.

Garen's movement forward suddenly came to a halt, he'd lifted his left leg but it hadn't landed, instead, it was still dangled mid-air.

Suddenly his consciousness began to blur and everything around him seemed to be rapidly distanced, the sound of the cars, the ongoing foot traffic, the crisp chirping of birds, the warmth of the sunlight, all of it appeared to leave him suddenly. Once again, he fell into a psychedelic dream realm with no control over himself.

He had originally been standing at the roadside of the building while around him were streetlights, pedestrians and youths on bicycles, the green old truck that carried stocks, the stall selling fruits, the public bus which cruising by slowly, the gardener who was watering the plants and the white collars who were rushing for work.

But now everything seemed blurry, and he could neither see anything in detail nor hear anything clearly.

Garen felt like he'd suddenly entered a mute blurry world where everyone's faces couldn't be clearly identified. It was all blurry, and the ground was shaking and vibrating.

Bam!!

Suddenly, a strong force came crushing down on his chest.

Garen only felt that his chest went numb, it wasn't really painful, but he can hear his own sternum breaking. It was a really crisp, crackling sound.

He subconsciously wanted to swing both his arms around, but his body could not move at all.

There seemed to be someone screaming by his ears, screaming his name, but he couldn't hear it clearly as it was broken up.

Bam!

Another strong force came crashing on his left arm, his left forearm was broken instantly and was twisted into an unnatural angle. Oddly enough, Garen did not feel anything at all.

What he could hear was the increasing anxiety of the voice, as though that voice was screaming and shouting some things.

Bam!!

Once again, another strong force hit his shoulders, which made Garen kneel on the ground, he could finally clearly see what's been attacking him.

Just a few meters away from him was an unknown creature towering over him.

It looked like a clay doll lumped together from white clay that stood about 3 meters tall, with distinct limbs but no facial features, and all over its body were protruding dolls' heads and limbs. It walked very slowly, as though its movements weren't very agile.

It lifted its arm and Garen noted that there was no palm, no fingers, just a rounded end like a rolling pin. It then swung violently at him, aiming for his head.

Garen lifted his head, quietly looking on as the white arm came crushing down, his face was soon shadowed by the arm, but he revealed no hint of panic or horror.

In the instant before the arm hit him.

"Wake up!!" Suddenly, a loud voice rang at the side of the Garen's ears. As the voice roared, it carried a heavy tremor and loud thump.

Garen suddenly opened his eyes, he actually found himself standing on his original spot, asleep with his eyes shut.

He was still standing in his original spot at the entrance of the building, and the sidewalk was still bustling with the boot and vehicular traffic. Nobody paid any heed to him who had been standing there with his eyes shut, perhaps most of them thought he was getting a short shut-eye from his exhaustion in order to recover.

‘You were almost a goner.' Black Sethe's fatigued voice suddenly rang.

"what was that just now….?" Garen was slightly dumbfounded, he felt that his brain hasn't completely recovered, it was still murky, he subconsciously extended his arm to touch his right ear canal, it was wet inside with a viscous liquid.

As he took his finger out for a look, it was blood.

The bright red blood was very attention-grabbing under the shine of the sunlight.

Ka-crack!

Suddenly Garen felt a crisp ring on his shoulder, as though the bone was broken, and then the left forearm, completely fractured with a snap.

Lastly, it was the sternum, the successive crackling sounds made him feel stuffy in his chest for a while, and his sternum actually collapsed inwards in that instance.

Garen took a deep breath and he began breaking out in sweat.

The muscles around his body began moving and vibrating, the extreme precision of muscle and bone control was activated in an instant

Ka-clack ka-clack…

In an instant, a long series of joint crackles could be heard as his muscles contracted in waves, each wave producing a different amount of force much like an agilest and meticulous pair of hands which instantaneously realigned all his broken bones back in place. Afterwards, he then tightly wrapped them with his strong muscles in order to lock those bones in position.

This was the greatest level of self-body manipulation technique, a technique that could only come in handy when the body sustained severe damage.

Garen stood still as his body shuddered. The injuries all over his body have been stabilized, the body parts which had internal bleeding have been settled, and his wounds were closed as his blood began clotting, thanks to his strong blood-clotting ability.

"The Devourer is here and it's their formal army this time around, that was the White Claydoll, the regular soldier of the Devourer." Black Sethe explained while sounding fatigued, "any later and you might have died inside.'

Garen did not say a word.

"Do you know why in the dream realm, your body's physique was exactly as fragile as a regular person? That's not because you're too weak, but they were too strong…. An average White Claydoll's strength would still be over ten tonnes at their weakest, they are considered to be a pure destroyer in the dream realm, it's lucky that the Void Creatures have not fully recovered, if they were back then they would have mobilized at least ten White Claydolls at one go and completely destroy your dream, and then forcefully drag you into their illusory realm and then rear you like a pig to be eaten at any time.

Garen took a deep breath, it was the first time he'd sustained such heavy injuries ever since his transmigrated into this world.

Broken left arm, collapsed sternum, shoulder completely shattered, internal bleeding, all of this had happened in a split second.

‘I used my powers to forcefully pull you out of the dream just now, if you cannot get used to moving around the dream realm quickly, then you'd die at the hands of void creatures sooner or later.' Black Sethe seemed to be oddly fatigued. ‘We're lucky that the flow of time for void creatures isn't the same as ours; they'll need some time to move over from another dimension of time. What seems to be ten minutes to them would probably equate to our ten days or even a month, so you still have some time to adapt as soon as possible.'

Garen once again felt this familiar feeling, the sense of looming danger. Even though it was weak, he had not felt it for a long time.

‘Don't expect that you can get rebirthed after being killed by the void creatures!' Black Sethe's sudden statement shattered Garen's deepest mental assurance. ‘I don't know how your body could achieve these kinds of space-time attributes and be able to transmigrate into another dimension upon death, but I have seen this kind of physical properties among those people who were fearless as they thought death could not touch them, but do you know what their endings were like?'

He snickered lightly.

‘In the end, they were eaten by Void Creatures and not even a shred of their souls was left, this kind of transmigrating body properties are the Void Creatures' favorite meal.'

‘Mages were immeasurably strong, and among the worlds that fell under their power, there were a few that were transdimensional. This kind of technique wasn't anything they were new to, but they would still be defeated by the Void Creatures. I'd advise against any feel-good mentality.'

Garen stiffened his posture, as he got into his new car and slowly started the engine to drive to the house in the countryside.

He remained fully confident in himself; if he could train himself to be as mobile in the real world, then he was absolutely confident of meeting any opponents!

Black Sethe on the other hand, was only snickering.

The sky was full of fire-colored clouds in layers like a flight of stairs, it seemed to extend from near to far, as the colors got darker from butter yellow to murky gold.

At the borders of Grandor, in a red-roofed house at a T-junction.

Arisa and Isaros alighted from a little white car. Both of them were donned white skirts with silver buttons forming decorative lines.

As they walked up to the front of the house with its red roof and grey walls, with the fence in between them, Isaros looked up at the structure of the building.

The left half of the roof was slanted, whereas the right half of the roof was flat. The house's front had some red windows scattered about but on the far right was a cylinder-shaped building with a conical top protruding out, much like a miniature version of a castle tower.

"Pruyn should be referring to this place, there should be someone coming over later," Isaros murmured. " Arisa, you wait for me on top, close the car door properly and observe your surroundings, tell me when the time is right if you notice anything."

"Okay." Arisa understood the severity of the issue and nodded seriously.

Pruyn had distracted the troops that were after his life and he'd asked the sister to come pick him up. Even though this looked simple enough, they could not let down their guard at any moment, as that was the rule that had ensured their survival after all these years. Most of the time, when the situation looked safe, it was actually the most dangerous time for them.

Chapter 643: Followed 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

‘You have no idea how scary the White Claydolls are!' Black Sethe snickered.

Garen didn't pay much attention to him as he was concentrating on driving the car. He'd only recently obtained his license, but the way he controlled the vehicle was already considered quite skilled.

As the cars in front passed by, there would be cars from behind catching up to him, while the vehicles on both sides constantly sped past each other.

‘White Claydolls may be the most common troops among the Void Creatures, but it possesses an unyielding body with no regards to fatigue and pain, strong regenerative powers, and mighty strength. I reckon you wouldn't want to meet two White Claydolls simultaneously, as they can buff each other up to increase each other's strength. Furthermore, they do not have any acupoints, no nerves, and were designed specifically as a war machine against us mages.'

Black Sethe explained in a sarcastic tone.

"Are there any ways for me to temporarily gain speed inside the dream realm?" Garen suddenly asked, but his hands were still on the steering wheels, adjusting the car's forward moving motion.

‘Why would you ask this? Your own training is more important.' Black Sethe asked in confusion.

"If I got myself into such a situation where I can't move once more, wouldn't you die as I die?" Garen rebuffed, "It's a temporary solution."

‘There is, but it takes a huge toll on me.' Black Sethe replied.

"That's good to know." Garen's facial expression didn't change, "I felt that the attack just now was just a test and the real foes will come soon, you should be prepared."

‘Void Creatures' sense of time isn't the same as ours, so even if they wanted to launch a second attack, it wouldn't be this quick. I understand Void Creatures are better than you…'

Bam!!!

In a loud crash, the car made a sharp turn as it spun around while braking, violently carving out a distance of tire marks before it came to a halt while positioned perpendicularly to the road.

In that instant, Garen felt that his brain had become sluggish and his consciousness was fading swiftly, reverting back to the situation like before.

Sethe's voice could no longer be clearly heard, as though there was a thick cloth muffling it.

The sound of fire started crackling around him.

Through the car window, Garen could see that both sides of the cars were on fire and the flames appeared to engulf the sky. Not just the sides of the road, even random items on the road were burning.

The crimson red fire was dancing upwards, much like a red ribbon.

The surroundings and the situation on the road had quickly turned blurry, as the sky darkened all of a sudden.

Bam!

The back of the car was hit by a heavy blunt force and the entire car creaked loudly. The back half of the car had been flattened like an empty drink can.

Garen hurriedly flung the door open and ran out. As he turned around for a look, three White Claydolls that were about 4 meters tall were approaching him and were swinging their giant fists as they moved forward. Among the three, one of them was lifting its right leg from the car boot.

Garen felt that his body had become extremely slow to respond; both his legs no longer listened to his commands, and as he tried to run away with all his might, his legs did not budge at all, remaining rooted to his original spot.

‘Run! This is the illusory realm of the White Claydoll!' Sethe's voice was transmitted for a brief moment.

Suddenly, Garen was feeling energetic again, his body had returned to normal and everything was back under his control, even the surroundings have become clear in an instant too. He immediately knew this was Sethe's assistance, and he turned around and ran.

‘Damn it! Three White Claydolls, this is troublesome! You have to leave their realm as soon as possible, I'll tell you how to get out…'

Bam!!

Garen leaped onto a car that was parked on the side and stepped onto the car's windshield. With a curled up body and a bent knee, his entire body was wound like a spring.

He didn't even stop to listen to Sethe until he finished.

Badumm!!

In a large burst of noise, Garen suddenly bounced backward and was launched straight towards the three White Claydolls, much like an arrow that had been released from a bow.

‘You're courting death!!" Black Sethe shouted in anger.

Roar!!!

Suddenly, a giant blood-red creature emerged from within Garen's emotionless eyes, its horrifying roar erupting as air whipped around its body.

That was a dragon's roar!!

The Nine-Headed Hydra's soul consciousness had always laid deep within Garen's soul, merging with him was indeed the final apex predator's will, it was the ultimate desire to survive!

As the apex predator sitting on the top of the food chain, Nine-Headed Hydra had been bored of this peaceful world for far too long, and now it finally got a chance to rage.

The silhouette of the giant Nine-Headed Hydra appeared behind Garen, a horrifying silhouette towering over ten meters above ground with a blood red body and countless black smoke auras.

As Garen's right hand extended and gripped in one of the White Claydolls' direction, that hand seemed as though it was shrouded by the Hydra's heads and rushed at the four-meter tall Claydoll with a violent roar.

The Claydoll had also let out a muted roar, and it swung its fists ferociously at the unknown power ahead of it with full frontal force, even though its body size was vastly smaller compared to the Nine-Headed Hydra.

The Nine-Headed Hydra was a little over twice its size.

The two sides seemed like an adult preparing to joust with a child.

Ba-dum!!

Much like a thunderous thump from afar, the White Claydoll's arm was snapped, pushed back towards and stuffed into its body like an eraser.

A sudden red flush appeared on Garen's face and his right arm had wilted, as though all of its water content in his hand had been lost and it was left mummified.

He quickly swapped to his left arm, lifted it and swung towards another White Claydoll.

His hand moved at an extreme speed and with an accurate hit, it carried the Nine-Headed Hydra's rage and busted the White Claydoll's head with one punch.

With a thump, its head exploded and mud-like white liquid spurted out of its severed body.

The claydoll staggered backward a few steps and fell to the ground.

The final claydoll took a few steps back. Its face now had a terrified look as it was completely overshadowed by the huge, Nine-Headed Hydra, and it seemed to be trembling in fear.

As it observed two of its comrades being severely injured, it dared not stop and it turned around and began running towards the horizon.

Garen stood there without a shred of emotions on his face, he could feel his surroundings change once again; what seemed to be crystal clear have once again turned blurry.

‘You're a lunatic! Don't pull me in if you're seeking death!' Black Sethe's loud roar could be heard. ‘You actually dared combine with the soul of Nine-Headed Hydra! Do you think that kind of creatures' consciousness was easy to combine? That's a descendant of one of the top 100 Void Creatures, and you actually dared to combine with its soul! Count yourself lucky that you didn't get consumed immediately!'

"I'm all out of power," Garen spoke softly.

‘With such mediocre strength! And you actually scared away three White Claydolls! This is the biggest joke I've seen in my entire life!' Black Sethe said, seemingly surprised after being angry.. ‘If they had stayed to counterattack, then you would have completely perished! Even I can't do anything to help you!'

"Didn't we succeed in the end?" Garen readjusted his body which had wounds torn open due to the vigorous movements.

He then realized that he was still sitting in his car and his sitting position hasn't changed at all. The only difference was that the lifeforce in both of his arms had all been released, and they felt uncomfortably empty inside.

"I think I'll die sooner or later thanks to you!' Black Sethe concluded his rant.

"Don't you all idolize death?" Garen shrugged.

‘That's them, plus this isn't my actual body, it perished several thousand years ago and I am now merely an independent piece of memory.' Black Sethe answered impatiently, ‘You've drained all my strength too, we need to recharge.'

Even though he couldn't stop scolding Garen, Black Sethe actually couldn't suppress his excitement.

Garen, who didn't have the ability to even kill a single White Claydoll, had actually scared away three of them in that one instant of explosive power, this was completely out of Black Sethe's expectations.

This kind of bravery to meet his own destiny, the boldness to make the bravest decision in that instant and simultaneous execution, this level of decisiveness, this kind of complete confidence in himself.

Black Sethe could suddenly see the shadow of his several thousand years old main body in Garen in that instant.

Perhaps, he could indeed be the next Bloody King….

At this moment, in the illusory realm that was supposed to be destroyed and was engulfed in flames suddenly had a hole ripped open in space.

A skinny white arm slowly stretched out of it and grasped onto the boundaries of the hole.

" Al… My poor brother…" A gentle male voice could be heard.

Jiiii….!!!

Garen immediately floored the brakes, he then turned around to take a look, the Nine-Headed Hydra in his eyes kept rolling. In this instant, it felt as though his eyes have been transferred to another dimension's limit and could see something approaching.

‘What's wrong with you?!' Black Sethe asked in surprise.

Garen did not say anything for a while.

"Nothing." He started the car once again and sped towards his destination.

He didn't know why, but he could vaguely feel that something was resonating with his soul nearby. This uncomfortable feeling was especially obvious and clear.

**********************

Isaros nimbly avoided the glass shards scattered on the floor and frowned as she peeked at the second floor upstairs. There were traces of blood on the staircase and the handrails of the staircase have been destroyed, as though they'd been crushed by a heavy object.

She tip-toed upstairs step-by-step.

The scent of blood in the air got thicker and thicker.

Oddly enough, the blood stains on the floor were getting smaller; as she reached the second floor, there was almost no blood stain at all, but the air around had a very thick smell of blood.

The room was pin-drop silent, no noise was heard.

Isaros' cautious mind had taken over; she already knew that something was wrong from the moment she'd walked into the house, and the door was just a facade hiding the mess within the room that was littered all over with mostly smashed fragile items.

Suddenly, she turned around and instantaneously pulled the trigger on her handgun behind her!

Bam!

A gunshot was heard, and a black shadow evaded the shot quickly. Isaros had no way of knowing if the shot had connected with the target.

Chapter 644: Followed 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Isaros did not think too much and kept firing her handgun while she instinctively retreated.

Bam bam bam bam bam!

Her left hand was tightly gripping her dagger and she made a crescent-shaped slash in front of her as a defensive maneuver.

Firing a handgun while operating a knife simultaneously had almost become a second nature for her. Isaros' eyes followed the silhouette tightly as it sped around, but her handgun was almost unable to catch up to the opponent and could only barely hit its afterimage.

She saw that shadow circled around the second floor's living hall once, and then immediately rushed towards her at an incredible speed while it maintained an S-shaped evasive maneuver.

She fired two consecutive rounds that missed before she tossed the handgun aside and rolled onto the ground to avoid the pounce, then countered that attack by throwing the dagger out. She didn't even manage to see what the outcome was, but had already hidden in a room on the side and slammed the door shut.

With her back against the window, she quickly took out a few black colored parts from her pockets and assembled them with a speed which seemed like a series of afterimages was assembling it, and then taped it on the door behind her.

She then rolled over, ran towards the window in front of her and jumped out after smashing the window, while both her hands held onto the ledge of the window.

Just as she hung onto the ledge, the little device taped to the door started blinking red.

The black shadow suddenly barged into the room.

Ba-dum!!

A strong explosion happened instantaneously.

The flames engulfed everything in the room like a surging flood, including the black shadow. An immense amount of heat rushed through the windows with large clouds of smoke, and the interior of the house began burning following the large explosion.

"Beautifully done."

A composed, male voice was suddenly heard beside Isaros, with a hint of admiration.

She immediately turned to her side, while her right hand was positioned like a serpent to choke the opponent's neck.

Isaros had not anticipated at all that she would miss someone right next to her.

Pap!!

The fingers were accurately caught by her opponent, and the opponent licked her fingers.

Isaros was then able to see that person's true colors.

He looked just like a regular young male, clean, with a tidy attire and wore gold-framed eyeglasses, which made him look like a lawyer from a law firm. He looked gentlemanly, but his eyes had a hint of judgment. That black suit that he donned was definitely not low-class but was an elegantly-tailored suit.

This handsome man with fair skin had pitch-black irises like two magical whirlpools which carried an oddly strong attraction, making people unable to resist staring into his gaze.

"Hypnosis!" Isaros suddenly escaped the technique, twisted her body and her lower half then bent upwards before her body nimbly flipped back into the room. But that man seemed to be agiler than her and hopped into the room just right after her.

Both of them stood in the middle of the sea of flames.

"Such a beautiful lady… Outstanding, charming, seeing you feels like looking back at my daughter…" The man sighed with a hint of nostalgia. "If she wasn't killed by the damned light party, she would probably be as outstanding and beautiful as you."

"Blood Breeds have reproductive abilities too?" Isaros cautiously observed her opponent, while replying him in a casual tone.

"No, not Blood Breed, she was a pure human." The opponent didn't seem to be willing to talk more about his past, he was looking at Isaros, "To be able to escape my hypnosis, I suppose you're no regular human too."

Isaros kept feeling that this man seemed oddly gracious, this odd feeling made her feel extremely uncomfortable.

"No, you're wrong, I'm a pure human."

"Is it?" The man smiled. "My name is Laers, I'm the person in charge of this territory's secret party. I had originally intended to take a walk, but I would never have expected such an outstanding girl like you."

As Isaros felt that something wasn't right, the opponent's gaze turned stern, much like a beast's calm before pouncing on its prey, which made people put down their guard.

Suddenly, she dodged to her left.

Jii!!

She heard something being torn from the location where she originally was, but she didn't stop to look. As she hit the ground with her right palm to support her weight, she swept her surroundings with a windmill kick.

The pointed leather shoes on her were as sharp as the tip of a knife, which let out a sharp ferocious howl as it spun with a high velocity.

With two thumps, Laers was hit, but both his arms shielded his body with a speed exceeding Isaros'. Even he couldn't anticipate that his opponent would have such moves hidden, and it would have been too late to react if not for his own overbearing speed, which instead allowed him to proactively approach and hit her feet.

With two consecutive hits, his face seemed unwell. The elegance from before could no longer be faked, and his face slowly started to show a shred of impatience and ferocity.

With two bloody holes pierced on his arms, even though there was no blood flowing out, it was a thorough insult to a pure-blooded Blood Breed to be injured by a regular human.

Roar!!

He let out a loud roar and rushed at her after transforming into a black shadow, as he took advantage of the timing that Isaros needed to recover to close in on her.

Pap pap pap pap!!

The two of them had gotten themselves into a brawl. Isaros' speed was leagues below the opponent, but her attack accuracy was frighteningly pre-emptive as she has a honed sense of danger. She seemed to be able to predict Laer's attacks before they happened and launch a pre-emptive strike, which made Laers feel uncomfortable.

With a bang, the two of them knocked down the remaining wooden wall which had been blown apart by the earlier explosion and burst into the hall.

With a lunge, Isaros' finger violently slashed at Laers' right cheek, the poison on her nails instantly entering his body.

His face changed in that instant.

"How dare you!!" He roared and instantly gave up his plan to toy with his opponent, and a strong force suddenly flowed throughout his body.

His entire person was slowly dyed an odd hue of grey, while his skin became as tough as a boulder.

His speed has suddenly increased twofold, and just as he raised his right arm, it would hit Isaros' shoulder.

The immense power crashed upon Isaros' shoulder, sending her flying.

Laers turned into a shadow once again and closed in on Isaros, choked her and lifted her high. She could not do anything even as she struggled. His skin was as tough as a boulder and was nothing that a mere human could damage, even her dagger could only scratch the skin without dealing any significant damage.

Laers could feel the poison spreading within his body, and as he glared at Isaros in his grasp, he turned violent.

Bam!!

Suddenly, a large explosion erupted from the tiles behind his body.

The huge explosion flung away both Laers and Isaros at the same time.

Isaros took this opportunity to escape the opponent's choke, and she jumped out of the window pane after two coughs. Suddenly, a black shadow sped by and threw her downwards by grabbing her waist.

Bam!!

With yet another loud thump, her nose and mouth began bleeding, but the anti-stab garments that she wore before the entire incidents were useful in greatly reducing the damage that she received.

"Damn it!!!" Laers' voice could be heard from behind her.

Isaros' consciousness was beginning to blur, but the many years of fleeing from death's door had unfazed her, hence she turned her body away from her original position decisively.

Just as she rolled away, the flooring at her original position had been stomped through by Laers. The shards of wood and cement littered the ground floor.

The house had ignited once again at this point.

Isaros wasn't aware that she'd rolled into a flame, which ignited her body.

Flame, rollover, roar, sirens of a fire truck, a soft voice transmitted over a communication device.

All of these noises weaved together into Isaros' ears, as though it was a muffled orchestra.

In that instant, the scene where she'd practiced with Garen resurfaced. Those unknown emotions suddenly surged through her, as though it was merging with her innate prediction ability.

Aura began flowing around her slowly and after a few rolls, the flames on Isaros was quickly extinguished. By this time, Laers was already standing next to her, lifting her up by her neck again.

"You mortal! To actually humiliate me to this extent! Such accomplishment!" Laers smiled deceitfully, "Perhaps I should make you my treasured collection, keep it until… Jii!"

A crisp noise had broken his speech.

Laers was stunned with an unbelieving expression and Isaros slowly looked down at his chest.

That slightly darkened arm has been stabbed into his body, much like a spear piercing into his heart. The arm which was smoking and black was supposed to be clearly visible to him, yet oddly enough he hadn't noticed any movements from before. Just a light hit and his chest had already been pierced, as though his Blood Breed skin was a useless decoration.

"Silent Killing Art…" Isaros had a flashback of Garen showing her this technique, there was no ripple within her heart, her head was blank, ahead of her seemed to be the scene where Garen had pointed his dagger at her own forehead.

With a thump, Laers let go of Isaros and staggered back by a few steps. He shapeshifted once again into a shadow and disappeared from the scene.

In the house, there was only Isaros left barely managing to stand as she stared at her right hand, stunned. On her hand was a hint of Laers' blood.

Silent Killing Art.

Such a technique…. Was indeed too horrifying…

This was the first time that she'd felt the impression that the ordinary Garen was shrouded with a layer of mystery.

At this time, the sirens of the fire truck outside were approaching. As she snapped back into focus, she quickly jumped out of the window pane and nimbly landed on the ground with a forward roll, dispersing the majority of the landing impact. Without concern for her own injuries, she swiftly pulled open the car door.

Arisa came out from beneath the seats, she was frightened to see that her sister was covered in blood stains and burn marks.

"We have to leave!" Isaros said quickly.

Arisa did not dare to speak much, she immediately took over the steering wheel and left the location swiftly.

The house was left smoldering.

Chapter 645: Mask 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Near Gullivier University.

Garen did not encounter any more ambushes along the way. It was already nightfall when he arrived at his house in the suburbs safely.

"Boss." Under the guidance of Jay, a few of the newer high-leveled Black Uniform Organization members greeted Garen in an orderly manner.

Garen nodded, alighted from the car, and strode through the main door of the villa behind Jay and the others.

A few members of the Nighthawks opened the door for him respectfully. They led the way across the lawn and walked towards a piece of empty land behind the house.

There were a few lorries parked on the empty land. They were covered in black cloth that was pulled over tightly, making it impossible to guess what was hidden underneath.

"Boss, these are the goods that we gained this time," said Jay respectfully with his head bowed.

He'd brought a few of his subordinates with him and waited at the side for Garen to check the goods.

Garen walked in front and with the bright light from the light source beside him, he lifted up a corner of the black cloth. Large black boxes were revealed underneath.

He could vaguely feel a kind of potential energy that was entrenched within the box and constantly lingering there.

When he looked around, he noticed that the ten subordinates had dispersed on their own and were now keeping a close watch on their surroundings. Their chests were puffed out while their gazes were locked on the others around them.

"There is three lorries' worth of goods here, meaning that we have a total of 125 pieces. I will get the others back bit by bit and as soon as possible," Jay reported quietly.

Garen nodded happily.

"I trust you. Get someone to move all of the goods here into the villa. Besides that, get more people to manage the house, it's too lonely living here on my own."

"Yes, sir," Jay nodded quickly. He relayed some instructions to his subordinates quietly before a crowd of people walked inside instantly and began to open the boxes one by one to move the items into the villa.

There were flower vases, mirrors, cutlery, oil paintings, and even ancient music boxes. Various items were moved into the villa carefully and displayed inside one of the rooms under Garen's instructions.

'What do want these relics for?' asked Black Sethe beside his ear in a puzzled manner. 'The Void Creatures could return any minute yet you still think that you have spare time to fiddle with these boring playthings.'

"Can't you tell?" Garen did not reply but chose to casually ask him a question instead.

'Tell what?' Black Sethe obviously could not see the potential that antiques possessed.

"I prefer collecting relics," answered Garen indifferently.

The moving of the relics was finally completed at midnight. A line of people withdrew from the villa one by one after that. Under Jay's commands, a group of them remained to guard the villa while the rest got into their cars and returned to the Black Uniform Organization branch.

The Black Uniform Organization's headquarters were located in Africa while the Nighthawks' headquarters were established in America because of Garen. Sufficient manpower could be assembled from either location, including the elites.

Once everyone had left, Garen remained in the storage room that was used to keep the relics alone.

He looked at the dazzling array of relics. Some of them emitted potential energy while others were merely normal antiques.

He spent the rest of the night separating these antiques and relics by placing the useless antiques on the side and only removing the relics with potential energy.

Although there were 45 relics that possessed Potential Value, most of them only held a few Potential Points, while only three of them possessed a Potential Value of at least ten points.

One of these items was a mask. It was a peculiar, ancient red-black mask and although Garen could not detect its exact Potential Value, he could detect that is was definitely a high value of at least ten or even twenty to thirty points.

The timely delivery of these relics instantly improved his mood, while the condition of the wounds on his body had improved greatly as well.

'Other than their nominal collection and historical value, what other use do things like relics have?' nagged Black Sethe again.

Garen turned a deaf ear to him immediately. Just from being inside this room, he could already feel that his body was steadily absorbing the potential energy that the antiques and relics were emitting.

He glanced at the Attribute Pane at the bottom of his line of sight and noticed that his Potential Value was moving slowly and blurrily. Although it was slow, it was clear that the values were truly increasing.

He picked up a pocket watch randomly before all of the potential energy inside was quickly absorbed into his body. The cool and refreshing air currents flowed inside him from his wrists to his upper arms before rushing up his shoulders and finally entering his brain.

His Potential Points increased by three points instantly. Meanwhile, the remaining Potential Points continued to enter slowly. It would take at least a week for him to absorb all of the Potential Points from the pocket watch completely.

Absorbing Potential Points from antiques could not be done as quickly as killing things in the Totem World. However, it was beneficial because it was long-lasting and would arrive in a steady flow.

Garen looked out of the window and noticed that the sky was now somewhat bright. A whole night had passed quickly. The healing of his bodily wounds had begun to slow down in certain places because he had not gotten proper rest.

He glanced at the array of relics and antiques before him. Garen was too lazy to attend classes and decided to lie down in a pile of relics instead. He finally collapsed on an ancient but clean copper bed and fell asleep.

The fastest method of absorption was to be with these relics at all times.

***************

Time flew by quickly.

After a few months had gone by in a flash…

Under the night sky, a white sedan stopped in front of a detached villa on the outskirts slowly before a remote was used to activate the metal gates' automatic opening.

Garen sat in the driver's seat and drove into the garden of the villa unhurriedly. He passed a fountain and turned the car around under the maid's directions before driving into the underground garage slowly.

Bang.

He pulled the car door open and got down from the vehicle before walking out of the garage slowly.

At night, the sky was filled with clusters of glittering stars that resembled countless tiny pale blue diamonds that were embedded in the curtains of the night.

Garen was dressed from head to toe in a slim-fitting suit. He walked across the lawn before entering the main door of his own villa where the lights were shining brightly from within. Two people whom he had not seen for a long time were already seated inside.

Quentin and Xander.

Both of them seemed to be closing their eyes and resting, but when they heard the sound of the door opening and the footsteps, they opened their eyes at once and looked towards the doorway.

When they saw Garen, both of them stood up immediately.

"President," both of them greeted respectfully together.

Garen had only been focusing on absorbing Potential Points and practicing his Dreaming Technique with great concentration. Concentrating his own consciousness and attention while remaining clear-headed enough to recognize that he was dreaming was something that he could already achieve quite effectively. The thing that pleasantly surprised him the most was that these exercises seemed to help his own Secret Technique levels. When the Dreaming Technique upgraded, he could feel new developments throughout his Secret Technique levels, which had remained dormant for a long time.

There seemed to be new changes within the Slaughtering Hand that even Black Sethe had not anticipated. Garen's Slaughtering Hand was actually achieved by practicing the Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Evil Technique and was not actually a pure killing-type demonic technique. Although it had undergone strange changes, no one knew if these transformations were good or bad, and the only way to find out was to observe it step-by-step.

Within these few months, he had encountered countless raids by the White Dolls. However, when he had become more accustomed to handling them and had reached a level that was even more terrifying than the Combat World's King of the Century, it allowed him to discover the White Doll's weaknesses in a short span of time. This allowed him to cope with the White Dolls easily, while his upgraded Potential Points allowed his injuries to heal quickly. Once he was able to retain his consciousness and remain self-aware while dreaming, the White Dolls became insignificant to him even if two or three of them came at once.

The ability to remain aware in that state allowed him to use his Secret Techniques and other powers without any obstructions. Therefore, he was much stronger than his muddle-headed opponents that attacked passively.

Even without Black Sethe's help, he was currently able to handle a few White Dolls easily at once, clearly displaying the General-level powers that Black Sethe once mentioned. Within these few months, he had killed more than ten White Dolls consecutively.

However, all of his attention was now focused on the Void Creatures, making him completely indifferent towards the normal tasks of this world. He used his speedy regenerative powers to improve his life while pushing everything else to the back of his mind.

His body was currently able to constantly regain its initial qualities with the help of the relics. While upgrading himself continuously, he was also able to accumulate more than 200 Potential Points. If he had not used up all of the points on his physical body because points were useless in the Dream World, he would have used all of them to strengthen his mental self instead.

"It's rare for you to come looking for me. Did you come because of an important manner?" Garen instructed the maid to bring three cups of green tea. Although he was now living in a Western environment, he did not like drinking coffee as it left a sour taste in his mouth, and was not as comforting as tea.

Quentin's eyebrows were knitted together slightly. This beautiful and sexy girl had always been straightforward but was now clearly somewhat hesitant.

"It would be better for me to say it." Xander now resembled a normal young man that had become a part of society. He was dressed from head to toe in a well-ironed ashen suit, his hair was combed neatly and cleanly while only a little bit of his beard remained.

"President, we came to see you this time in hopes that you would mediate personally."

Xander's attitude was unusually earnest.

"Mediate?" Garen began to smile.

Up until now, he had begun restoring his body's natural qualities because of the large number of Potential Points within the relics. Accordingly, his body had begun to gradually upgrade the average values of his qualities. Currently, his each and every move seemed to emit a strong aura as if he possessed a gravitational force that attracted everyone's attention unconsciously.

"What aspect are you referring to?" he said as he looked at Xander calmly.

Xander always felt that Garen's eyes resembled bottomless abyss or whirlpools, and could not help but lower his own eyes unconsciously.

"It's about Hochman and Dahm."

"Hochman and Dahm?" Garen rubbed his chin. "Haven't they always had a good relationship with each other?"

"Last night at twenty minutes past nine, both of them officially declared war against each other," said Xander softly. "Both of them have lost their sanity and even opened fire and killed people in the downtown area brazenly. Both of their families have declared war with each other completely. Dahm even used his contacts to engage the special police forces, while Hochman dispatched some mercenaries immediately."

"They're both adults that have their own principles. As the situation has already reached this point, it will be useless for me to appear personally anyway. Once the grudge has formed, it cannot be resolved easily. Since they've already decided to make their moves, they have definitely considered all the other aspects already," said Garen calmly with a smile on his face. "However, isn't this a good thing? The strong should never shy from battle, and fighting is also another way to improve our martial arts."

Chapter 646: Mask 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

When they looked at Garen's deep and unmeasurable blue eyes, Quentin and Xander could feel a faint chill in the air for unknown reasons.

This mysterious president who had drawn them into the martial arts hall from the beginning now seemed to be completely unconcerned about the fight between Hochman and Dahm. Instead, his attitude showed that he was supporting it.

Hochman was currently known as the Boxing Overlord in the northern parts of America. During a fit of rage, he was once able to use his strength to break an iron pillar that was as thick as a thigh, showing that he had reached a terrifying, inhuman level. After he had crushed seven world-class boxing champions and famous underground combat fighters consecutively, his reputation reached far and wide. There was once an incident when a pistol was fired right in his face, but the speed of the trigger was no match for his quick fists. He sent his opponent flying with one punch and the man's entire upper body lost its form immediately before his internal organs and bones were turned into a sticky mess.

Meanwhile, Dahm was ruthless and malicious. He used fear and torture to rule over his group of subordinates. His underlings consisted of extremely vicious thugs, murderers, robbers, and other hardened criminals that were known to the public as 'Deadly Fists'. Likewise, he used his frightening and secretly cruel skills to kill others quietly, causing his subordinates and enemies to fear him greatly. He favored his underlings that possessed particularly muscular bodies and great strength but had a weird hobby that involved dressing up as a woman.

Both of them had already become the veritable underground rulers of the entire northern part of America. Their forces were omnipresent, and with the backing of both of their families, neither money nor the government could stop them at all.

"After all, both of them were the strongest members of our combat club…" said Quentin while trying to convince Garen. "Ever since the reputation of the combat club rose, the club members would always support and help each other to the point where they formed a large web of power relations. A year has passed since then and it has already developed into a large-scale network system today. As members, everyone should help each other progress so that our strengths can become more powerful. Both Hochman and Dahm were two of our most outstanding members, so we cannot…"

"So what?" Garen interrupted her. "The survival of the fittest is the way of the world. They made their own choices and I have no right to interfere."

Quentin choked up for a moment and was temporarily unable to speak.

"You taught and guided us past the threshold. Therefore, you are our Master," said Xander quietly from the sidelines. "Right now, you're the only person who can stop their fight."

"The only person in this world who can stop them is you," said Xander frankly. "I'm begging you." He lowered his head heavily and bowed deeply.

Quentin lowered her head and bowed while standing on the side as well. "We can't just watch while they kill each other. Please!"

Garen lifted his cup of green tea and sipped it gently.

Quentin sneaked at a glance at this mysterious man from the corner of her eye. His each and every move was completely incomprehensible to everyone else. Meanwhile, no one knew the origins of his extraordinary martial arts skills. While the prestige of his two disciples peaked, this mysterious and powerful man was gradually known as 'Holy Fist' by those around him.

However, although there were people who knew his family and other information, no one could understand how his terrifyingly strong martial arts came about.

Even though they had reached powerful stages now, both Hochman and Dahm restrained and downplayed themselves in front of Garen and continued to respect him.

The only one who could stop both of them was him.

Deep down, Quentin understood that. However, she was completely unaware that the real culprit that caused both of them to fight to the death was not someone else, but actually Garen himself.

Quentin knew about the terrifying techniques that she had learned from Garen's martial arts. They seemed like an endless path that allowed one to explore themselves infinitely…

She had currently achieved the third level of the Illusory Spinning White Jade, which was the Spin level. Although she was unable to reach the fourth level and remained in her current state, her strength was already sufficient to defeat all of her enemies outside combat club.

Her own family had started a boxing club, allowing her to clearly understand how terrifying the techniques that she had grasped truly were. After she'd accidentally overthrown two well-known boxers, she finally understood that the techniques she had grasped were terrifying murder skills that were actually derived from battle skills from countless fights. Neither mercy nor good intentions existed here, only death.

The Two-Faced Waterbird Fist that was concealed within beautiful and graceful steps were actually deadly murderous intentions.

In comparison, Hochman and Dahm had already started to create Waterbird Fist fighting techniques that were most suited towards themselves. Their powers seemed to constantly increase like a limitless rocket.

"How regretful." Garen crossed all ten of his fingers and laid them on top of the table. "The Two-Faced Waterbird Fist was a fighting technique that I had passed on to all of you. In reality, once it has reached a certain level, it will separate itself into positive and negative directions because of each person's own physical qualities. Only those with specialized talents and skills will be able to activate these special qualities. The fight between the Negative Two-Faced Waterbird Fist and Positive Two-Faced Waterbird Fist is predestined. Once they have defeated and killed their opponent and fused with the essence of their Secret Techniques, they will be able to upgrade themselves to a level that no one has ever anticipated before."

This was the first time Garen had explained the true meaning behind the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist to both of them.

"Negative and positive. This is the reason why it was named the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist."

This was the first time Quentin and Xander had heard an allusion like this, and both of them were unconsciously dazed after they had heard everything. They had always thought that Hochman and Dahm could only fight to the death because of personal grudges, but now… All of this seemed to be arranged by Garen from the beginning…

As fellow successors of the Waterbird Fist, both of them had finally understood the true secrets of this killing technique.

"You… what is your goal?!" Xander raised his head while suppressed anger flashed in his eyes.

"Goal?" Garen began to smile. "You guys thought that martial arts merely meant playing house? That strength could be achieved easily without having to pay a price? Perhaps you thought that you would be able to gain such frightening skills just by paying a small price? Don't be naive."

"The true path of martial arts has never included such a quick road to improvement. By practicing a martial art without aftereffects, they would have to spend at least ten years doing orthodox training to even dream about reaching your level. But you assumed that the martial arts that you were practicing could be considered of the same class?" sneered Garen.

"All shortcuts require a price to be paid in exchange." He stood up after he was almost done speaking. "Alright, it's late. Go home."

Both of them were currently stunned and in a daze. They thought back to the earliest moment when Garen had imparted the most powerful strength to them and the moment when they received everything before their minds become muddled once more.

They remained confused while being ushered out of the door by the maids, and only awakened from their trance while driving back on the road home.

No wonder they were forced to congregate around Garen for a period of time under the pretense of regulating their martial arts progress. They needed Garen to personally check their progress every time, and when they thought about it now, perhaps he was checking and getting rid of everyone's side effects.

Both of their minds were confused and numb for a while. Neither of them was concerned about Hochman or Dahm anymore, as they needed to go back and check on the conditions of their own bodies carefully.

**************************

Inside a little wooden house in an unspecified forest in Grano town.

Within a lush green forest, a little house was situated in completely silent surroundings, as if something was protecting this little wooden house that was built by this forest ranger.

"Are you crazy? You let two normal people come into contact with Lars? That insane madman?!"

Inside the wooden house, Pritto sat on the sofa while a beautiful woman with golden hair stood on the opposite side of him and looked on with an expression of disbelief.

"You actually gave such an important item to two normal people? I don't know what you experienced during this period of time, but actions like this simply make me see you as an unbelievably stupid idiot!" The woman's chest heaved continuously, making it obvious that she was extremely furious.

"I trust them…" said Pritto softly. A cigarette was held between his fingers but it was unlit.

"Barton's current goal is to pursue you and me. No one would think that the goods are not with us, but at the other place instead. As part of the Scarlet Moon tribe, we should not be afraid of our opponent's middle-level hypnotic control techniques. Currently, only you and I know this secret," Pritto raised his head quietly and looked at the woman.

"So you're not afraid that they'll be affected by the control of the hypnotic technique? Simply ridiculous!" said the woman in an annoyed tone.

"I've tried it. They have extremely strong will powers, and they've also undergone various types of training to resist it, making it completely impossible to control them," Pritto explained. "Besides that, they seem to know a specialized combat skill and possess extremely strong powers."

"No matter how strong they are, they're still normal humans at the end of the day. The Middle-level Blood Breeds can kill them with one look! Fine… Fine, fine…" The woman raised both of her hands. "Whatever, I don't care. Any decisions you make will be your own problem. Anyway, if anything bad happens, it will be your personal responsibility. I don't want to even think about caring about this anymore! Just do as you like!" She turned around and left angrily.

Only Pritto remained seated inside the wooden house. He smiled bitterly and coughed twice while a defeated expression crept across his face slowly.

"Frankly, I didn't want to drag two innocent lives into this. However, I had no other choice, and before I knew it, they were already involved."

*************************

Inside an unspecified private meeting room in Feinan City, a short distance from Grano, within the state of Faya.

None of the lights in the room were lit and it was pitch-black, while the smell of smoke wafted through the air faintly.

Two middle-aged men in black windbreakers stood in front of a window. Both of their figures seemed to blend into the darkness completely as if they were merely sculptures that posed quietly in front of the window amidst the cold and gloomy air.

"The operation has failed. Two normal people have been involved. They replaced Pritto and went to the coordinate point and even injured Lars."

"They're probably the subordinates of the other Blood Breeds. That fellow Lars is more concerned with saving face than his own life, and if news that a normal person was able to injure a Blood Breed gets out, not only will he be worried that others will make fun of him, but he'll probably also get more people to come over if he can't handle it. However, we can't drag this out any longer. The local Witches don't have positive attitudes towards us, so we'll have hurry up and make our moves. Do you know Pritto's whereabouts?"

"He should be with Cavenly. If we can find Cavenly, we'll definitely be able to find him as well."

"That's good. We must move fast. The other territories are almost done, we must not lag behind."

"Yes."

Chapter 647: Dream 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Inside a brilliantly illuminated golden hall.

Garen sat upright on the sofa with his eyes closed slightly, while his head and both of his arms were draped over the back of the sofa.

He had already finished absorbing the Potential Points from the relics. He glanced at the status of his own Attribute Pane.

'Garen Thomas.

Strength 2.9. Agility 2.9. Vitality 3.1. Intelligence 2.8. Potential 25648%. Soul Limit 30.'

He had neglected to increase his attributes equally but later used his increased vitality attribute to restore himself after incurring some heavy damage. Even though this had decreased his speed, Black Sethe remained confused after much thought, and could only assume that Garen possessed extremely powerful Secret Methods. After all, there were seemingly endless amounts of outstanding skills throughout the ages, and those that were created and initiated on one's own were not necessarily inferior in comparison to those of the past.

Garen closed his eyes. "My biggest problem now involves moving around in the Dream World. I don't need Black Sethe's help anymore because I can move around as I please, but this will only work when I focus my attention. Right now my biggest problem concerns the usage of my Potential Points. I still have 256 Potential Points but I don't know how to distribute them."

He had not anticipated that he would receive such huge rewards this time. These two hundred points were something that the Black Uniform Organization could only accumulate after many years. Unlike himself, they could not filter their attributes and talents, and would not dare to wantonly absorb Potential Values to strengthen themselves. They would only absorb these values slowly in times of need. However, this would cause various after effects that would make them suffer untold hardships. Many of them died young, while only Levi faced the least effects because his vitality was different from the average person's.

Garen had already confirmed that everything in the Dream World, including abilities and knowledge, could not be strengthened using Potential Values. Instead, they could only be trained and advanced step by step. Therefore, it was impossible to hurriedly learn the techniques of the Dream World.

His options were also limited.

Firstly, he could strengthen all of his physical qualities equally while empowering his strength in reality as well. This would be effective towards increasing his strength in the Dream World, as the body he used in the Dream World was still his own body.

Secondly, he could strengthen his skills and Secret Techniques. The Slaughtering Hand could be strengthened and advanced, and he could also choose other skills to improve as well. In the end, the Secret Techniques could be used to counter the Void Creatures, but he would need to pay attention to Black Sethe's lurking dangers.

Thirdly, he could focus on strengthening one particular attribute. Once that attribute had reached a certain level, special abilities and talents would appear the same way the Doublecast attack technique had appeared when his Intelligence had previously reached a certain milestone.

In Garen's perspective, although the Slaughtering Hand possessed strong powers, it also contained many hidden dangers.

Garen's thoughts wandered before an idea was formed when a certain Secret Method unexpectedly flashed through his thoughts.

By summarizing his personal experiences, he'd learned that two secret roads or points had to be added to the seven secret points to activate one's potential and create improvements within the Seven Star Life's Secret Point. Recently, he was constantly fixing and perfecting its contents in order to repair and gradually turn it into a complete set of Secret Methods and Secret Technique practices. The effects of every level were equivalent to forming a point of a star.

A Secret Method like this would strengthen his physical qualities equally. When he empowered his attributes and reached a certain level, there was a possibility that he would be able to reach unimaginable degrees.

Garen made up his mind.

He focused his sight on his Strength Attribute Pane immediately.

It remained there for three seconds before the values of his Potential Points decreased rapidly.

Meanwhile, his strength attribute increased from 2.9 quickly as 1 point of Potential Value would equal to an increment of 0.1 for said attribute. 2.9, 3.1, 3.2, 3.3… 4.1… 5.0.

Once his data card reached 5 full points, it did not continue to expand anymore. His other attributes were too low, making it impossible for them to continue increasing. Garen understood that this was because of all of his body parts that were linked together and influenced one another.

This 5 point strength restoration allowed him to vaguely feel the sensation of having plentiful strength as he had in the previous Totem World. Although it was not equivalent to the White Dolls and the explosive powers from the hidden life forces in both of his arms, his regular strength and movements had already reached a frightening degree. This was not merely a five-time increase of a normal individual's strength. Instead, the strength of his entire body had reached an extremely powerful stage. Once it exploded, it would be equivalent to ten times of a normal person's strength. This was decided by his Secret Technique state.

His state was the deciding factor that allowed him to move all of the strength in his body, as well as the strength in every inch of his muscles.

Even for a normal person, if they were able to release all of the strength of their muscles and unite it at once, they would be able to reach extremely strong degrees. However, regular people would only be able to gather the strength of their four limbs, while the slightly stronger ones would be able to add strength from their waist and back, and the even stronger ones could coordinate their four limbs.

If they were able to reach the next step, they could regulate and control every muscle and fiber in their body. At this level, they would be able to gather all the strength within their body, and this was the level that Garen was currently located at.

He had previously tested the Gene Limits of the people of this world. He'd used various Secret Methods to activate the potential of his experiments. Furthermore, he'd also used the Life Force of his arm to ensure that the other person would not die before constantly increasing their physical qualities. He discovered that they would stop increasing after 3 points, and if it went any higher, the components of the experiment's body would collapse immediately and even his Life Force would be unable to preserve their lives.

In other words, the people of this world which consisted of normal humans could only achieve the strongest levels of three times of the average physical qualities of a standard adult human. This was their Gene Limit.

However, Garen's own limits were constantly increased and strengthened by the Soul Seed as this was the crystallization of his efforts in the previous world.

After he had increased his strength to five points and consumed 21 Potential Points, Garen's sight fell on his Agility Pane once more.

Similarly, once 21 Potential Points had been consumed completely, he spent 19 points on Vitality, 22 points on Intelligence and ended up consuming a total of 83 Potential Points in one go.

"What a familiar feeling…"

Garen sat on the sofa while the muscles on his body began to tremble unconsciously, turning faintly red. His body size began to expand and become more muscular while unexpectedly becoming more streamlined as well.

The depression that had formed when he sat on the sofa was slowly beginning to sink lower as well. It was an obvious sign of his apparent weight gain.

Bouts of strength began to flow throughout his body and Garen soon felt that his body was becoming compacted. However, the powerful strength that surged through his body did not make it harder for him to move but made him feel more lithe and graceful instead.

He stretched his fingers out and counted them.

Tch!

A shroud of white gas flew out quickly. It was an air current that had been quickly released by his fingernail.

The white smoke struck the wallpaper on the opposite wall and hit it immediately as if it was a little hammer.

Garen glanced at his remaining Potential Points and noticed that there were only slightly more than a hundred points left. If he added them up, since his physical qualities had already exceeded five points, he would need a Potential Value of twenty points to upgrade one attribute. In other words, he would need a Potential Value of two points to upgrade each attribute by 0.1. This meant that the dividing line would be decided by the methods to produce qualitative change.

The hundred over points that remained were completely insufficient to increase anything. He looked at the data properly and noticed that there were 173 points of Potential Value left.

When he was bored, he had once converted his Strength Attribute Points into the equivalent strength units that he was familiar with in order to compare the strength levels between attributes clearly and conveniently.

The one that he used the most was the strength attribute. Therefore, the data that he converted and calculated was strength.

The strength limit of a normal person in this world was usually about 460 kilograms. This was the heaviest weight that they would be able to lift at one time, which was also the data limit that Garen had calculated after many attempts. Test values like these were plentiful within the mercenary world. Most muscular black men possessed a strength of about 300 kilograms and would be able to increase their limit by 46 kilograms through the activation of Secret Methods. Once they had passed the comatose period, some of their Life Forces would be depleted and they would suffer heavy injuries.

According to Garen's calculations, attributes were affected by one's worldly environment.

In theory, an increase of one's Strength Attribute Points in this world was equivalent to increasing the limits of one's strength data, meaning that it would be increased to 460 kilograms. This was the first time he had accurately represented the data conversion of attributes.

In other words, his current five-point strength was equivalent to five times of 460 kilograms. In theory, his limit would be 5 multiplied by 460 kilograms, which would equal to 2300 kilograms or 2.3 tons of strength. Being able to lift 2.3 tons of weight in one go was possibly his current strength limit.

Only Garen would be able to achieve limits like these. His current state allowed him to gather all of the strength in his body and utilize these limits as part of his daily life. Meanwhile, other people would only have extremely strong bodies, and once their Secret Methods were activated, they would barely be able to reach the level of his physical qualities even after consuming their life potential. Obviously, these were solely based on calculating their physical qualities without taking their Secret Techniques or Methods into account.

Therefore, even if other people possessed the exact physical qualities that Garen had, they would not be able to exceed their limits if they did not have the same martial arts state or activated Secret Methods as him. Instead, they would only be able to achieve sixty percent of their limit.

This strength was purely based on weight-lifting strength. In terms of boxing strength, Garen's five points of Agility would need to be added in as well…

The calculation of the Agility attribute was not as simple as multiplying the average person's speed by five. The speed limit of the human body possessed a data limit, and the value of the Agility attribute would increase on this basis. Garen had yet to calculate this carefully but he knew that adding one point to his Agility would be able to lighten and optimize his body's weight and dexterity. He could vaguely understand that Agility points were mainly used to lighten the bloat brought on by an increase in strength and prevent his body from becoming overly muscular.

In reality, he felt that increasing his current Agility and Strength did not improve his speed or movements too drastically, but merely got rid of the speed reductions that were caused by his strength.

There wasn't a huge difference between his current speed and previously before his attributes increased. However, if he were to lift two tons with his previous speed…

His current body weight was at least one hundred kilograms and his body size was not vastly different from the average person. However, his body was frighteningly dense. His previous punching speed was at least 20 meters per second when he released it quickly.

A speed of 20 meters per second for a strength of two tons meant that forces of more than ten tons would not be able to endure his blow. Coordination of strength and speed like this meant that he had already achieved a terrifying physical impulse. Of course, his skin and skeleton would need to bear the force of this impact.

However, an impact force that was produced by strength like this meant that regular cranes would not necessarily be able to achieve Garen's level.

Garen vaguely felt that among his own physical qualities such as his strength and speed, it was important to note which attribute broke through and surpassed the other more. Excessive strength and speed would cause great rebound impact forces and if he did not have strong physical qualities and physique to endure it, he would not be able to bear the force during the moment of impact with his opponent and would end up collapsing with them.

Chapter 648: Dream 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Meanwhile, Intelligence was related to nerve responses, memory, understanding and comprehension, imagination and other attributes. If these attributes decreased, it would weaken one's grasp of their own strength, while their body coordination abilities would be insufficient as well. Furthermore, the sudden changes within his body would produce many flaws throughout the smooth Secret Techniques and combat skills that he was once involved with.

In conclusion, all four attributes appeared to be independent and possessed their own important functions in reality. Garen had not fully comprehended it previously but was now beginning to fumble around somewhat clearly. After extensive consideration, he was able to increase all of his attributes equally. He could not exceedingly increase one particular attribute, as this would cause various burdens throughout his body, and was not as beneficial as increasing his powers in a balanced manner.

There were finally 173 Potential Points left, and Garen decided to distribute them equally among his four attributes, adding two points to each of them. All of his attributes increased to seven points and only 13 Potential Points were left while the rest was quickly used up.

He sat on the sofa and felt the changes in his body state.

"Looks like I'll need something to actually test the explosive limit of my strength…" Garen felt that he needed a comprehensive quality test. Strength and speed that were worth seven attribute points each was realistically equivalent to seven times of 460 kilograms, which equaled to 3.2 tons. His speed would probably remain the same, or perhaps it would increase slightly, but Garen would be unable to tell the difference. Frankly, if his agility had not exceeded his strength previously, his speed would not have exceeded certain limits. When he thought about it now, he realized some finer details. Agility was mostly used for increasing his dexterity and lessening his burdens.

The impact force of seven points of strength, when coupled with such speed, would surely cause strength of over a hundred tons to burst forth. The power that was created when strength and speed worked together was not something that could be added and stacked simply.

Garen raised both of his hands and looked at the translucent layer of epidermis that covered his skin. This layer of skin seemed thin but actually possessed extremely strong defensive abilities. This was another effect of upgrading all of his qualities equally.

This was the first time he had carefully calculated the allocation of his attribute points.

One attribute point represented a standard unit of an adult's data limit. This provided a huge help in allowing him to understand his own powers better.

'Have strange changes occurred throughout your body?' The sound of Black Sethe's doubtful voice echoed beside his ear. 'Have you studied a special Secret Method? I can feel that some big changes have happened throughout your body.'

"You could tell as well? This is a Secret Method practice that I came up with on my own," answered Garen casually. "I've been practicing it ever since I was young. It can strengthen one's physical qualities."

Although Black Sethe could tell that Garen was hiding something, he understood that everyone had their own secrets, and decided not to pursue the matter. Frankly, he could only faintly feel that Garen had undergone certain transformations but could not tell what they were clearly, and did not know how big these changes actually were.

Garen moved his fist and stood up from the sofa. The clothes on his back were now wrinkled and puffed, making occasional ruffling noises when he moved.

He returned to his bedroom and changed into an elastic singlet and shorts that he had found there. After that, Garen walked to the pool at the back of the villa and jumped in with a splash, spraying water everywhere before extending his body and swimming slowly.

Swimming was the best way to test his coordination abilities.

'Your body size seems to have changed. Tch tch.' At this moment, it was obvious that Black Sethe had felt the changes throughout Garen's body. 'I feel like you're a humanoid Transformer.' Apparently, he knew what Transformers were.

Garen smiled before pushing his head out of the water and shaking the droplets off himself silently. There were only seven points now. In the Totem World, he was once able to exceed a genetic standard of over twenty points. A strength of that degree was simply considered to be of a terrifying level, allowing him to crush ancient legendary beasts while they were still alive. He was also able to use his strength to tear those powerful Totems apart while they were still breathing.

However, he only had seven points now. It was unfortunate that he did not have any potential points left because he wouldn't have to worry about Void Creatures at all if he could restore himself to his Totem World state.

'It's fine if you don't want to talk about it,' Black Sethe staggered the conversation. 'You have to be more careful now. I can sense that the Void Creatures are about to launch their new attacks soon. How are your technique practices coming along?'

"Still fine. I'm able to move in the Dream World naturally now. However, I can feel that the consumption is quite great, not physical power but a different type of mental attention instead." Garen raised his head and swam across the surface of the water slowly while answering Black Sethe's questions quietly.

'That's normal. The Dream World consumes your subconscious attention. You have not trained yourself enough in that aspect and that's why you get tired easily. It's completely unrelated to physical strength, but is connected to your brain's concentration abilities instead,' Black Sethe explained. 'In order to move naturally, you'll need to move on to the next step. When you're performing activities in your dreams, the important part is to depend on a fixed base and focus all of your concentration and attention there. I noticed that your hands are your base. Now, you'll need to observe the Dream World carefully without focusing your attention on one specific place for too long. Instead, you should scan across the area quickly before focusing on your base and hands again. This way, you won't be affected by strange thoughts that will cause you to break away from your focused state.'

"Base?" Garen repeated the important points once again.

'Of course. Didn't you notice? Everyone -- pay attention -- everyone can be easily taken to different and unknown places by their messy and wandering thoughts in their dreams. Sometimes, strange sensations will form mysteriously which will suddenly take you from one place to another. Your Dream World is decided by your thoughts. Since your thoughts often change in your dreams, you will often form connections when you see something, and these associated things will quickly become the reality of your Dream World,' Black Sethe explained.

'But, did you notice?'

"What?"

'When we're dreaming, whenever our thoughts associate with something negative such as our fears and the things that scare us, those things or scenarios often show up faster, and may even approach you.'

Garen leaned against the side of the pool while his eyebrows furrowed slightly.

"Are you talking about how the things we fear end up becoming real?"

'That's a suitable description. You're right. In our dreams, the things we fear will often occur. When a worry appears while we are dreaming, it's very likely that these worries will amplify quickly before becoming a real part of our dreams.'

"What are you trying to say?" Garen raised his furrowed eyebrows.

'There's actually a reason behind this,' Black Sethe explained. 'The Dream World is formed by the brains of living creatures like ourselves because of a reaction between the external and internal consciousness. When both of these combine together, it forms an unpredictable and uncertain environment. It will produce certain reflections and manifestations both externally and internally. For instance, when the surrounding temperature increases while you're asleep, it affects your body temperature as well. In your dreams, you may think that you're in a hot environment such as a desert or a dry and humid house. These are the effects of the external world on the body. Meanwhile, harmful effects will not just appear instantly. If the occurrences are too intense at any moment, you will be startled awake at once. Of course, other than external influences, your own consciousness will affect your Dream World as well.'

Garen nodded his head slowly and pensively.

Meanwhile, Black Sethe continued speaking. 'Our Dream Worlds will quickly alternate and manifest different things when it is influenced by the minute changes in our bodies and consciousness. This creates infinite changes within our Dream Worlds despite their seemingly illogical characteristics. These things happen because the changes influence these two aspects extremely quickly. Moreover, the things we fear are more likely to happen, and whenever these things peep into our Dream Worlds, they will quickly produce specific effects when they discover your weaknesses and loopholes that will drown you within your own fears. Most of these things are Invisible Creatures which resemble spiders that specialize in seizing your consciousness.'

"So what does this have to do with the next step of the technique you were talking about?" Garen asked in response.

'You need to understand this principle clearly,' informed Black Sethe. 'As long as you understand this principle, anyone can achieve perfect control of themselves in their environments through step-by-step self-exercises. You're like a normal human being in these aspects and areas. Actually, you're not even equivalent to a normal human in that respect. Our Ancient Endor race has the slowest progression speed…'

"Go on." Garen was unconcerned about this personal attack. If his talents were insufficient, he would make up for it with hard work.

'In the Dream World, the most subtle effects towards your body from the outside world such as your sleeping position, comfort levels of your pillow, temperature of the weather, or even things like mosquito bites, bodily illnesses, and even the effect of cosmic rays passing through your body, earth's magnetic field and the slightest change in air flow will form changes in your Dream World. Your senses will cause everything to appear. Therefore, you must understand that our Dream Worlds will be influenced by our association abilities and imaginations, including external stimuli. Your next step is to distinguish these influences in your Dream World and separate out the harmful ones that don't belong there.'

"That's possible?" Garen felt that this was all very complicated. There were so many effects that were interwoven with one another, and distinguishing one from the rest would be an extremely difficult task.

'It's obviously very difficult, but this is an ability that a Void Pursuer must possess. You must do this, or else you will be eaten by the Void Creatures until no part of you will be left,' explained Black Sethe calmly. 'If you're able to do this by practicing it for long periods of time, you will be able to form physical instincts slowly. Your body will then be able to use its instincts to naturally remove and get rid of all of the harmful influences including cosmic rays and magnetic fields, allowing it to enter a brand new, pure level. Even regular people with normal lives will be able to experience certain changes.'

"Is there a method to do that?" Garen continued asking.

'You can try using your memory. Each person's own Dream World is based on the changes that are created within their own memories. We will often produce a natural sense of familiarity even when we encounter our subconscious memories. However, if people or objects that you've never seen before appear, you'll need to watch out.'

"Watch out for what?"

'They could be an external influence from certain harmful things like Void Creatures… Of course, it could still be something that we know as Invisible Creatures.'

"Invisible Creatures?" Garen noticed that this was the second time that he had heard Black Sethe mention them.

Chapter 649: Traitor 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

'Yes, Invisible Creatures exist in every world. They don't exist within the same timeline as us humans and their concept of time is drawn-out, making their lives almost endless. They are similar to Void Creatures in this aspect, and we once assumed that Void Creatures were merely extremely strong Invisible Creatures from another world.'

'To return to our main point, most people are unable to see Invisible Creatures with their naked eyes. This term is used as a general name for a creature of a certain species from a particular territory. Therefore, all of the living creatures that exist within the areas and worlds within that level are simply known as Invisible Creatures because they are creatures that we cannot see. You already know that humans like us can only see light within a very small range and spectrum. There are other vast areas that we cannot see. Hence, this world and universe are still considered to be very dark in our eyes. Within some of these dark areas, there are many unimaginable life forms that are living there. These include some of the things that you should be familiar with, such as the consciousness of large trees.'

"Large trees have consciousnesses too?" This was the first time that Garen had heard a viewpoint like this. However, he had experienced many things, and this did not shock him too severely.

'Yes. Many plants have different timelines from us. Their awareness and movements are slow and drawn-out, meaning that their every move and stretch can only be done once every few months. Their consciousness comes naturally, and whenever we come into contact with the consciousness of creatures like these, we should not approach them too closely because they have always possessed extremely hostile feelings towards humans. You know the reason behind that. Therefore, although any of these plants possess age-old consciousnesses and experiences, as well as other precious knowledge, we can never attain them.'

"But then, why do some people see scenes that they have never witnessed before in their dreams, while others are rumored to have dreamed of seeing things that would happen in the future?" Garen continued asking.

'This is not something that you can understand now. It's better to learn this step properly first before resuming. Furthermore, I'm not all-knowing. The universe is mysterious and both time and space undergo endless changes, making it impossible for anyone to see through them completely. What we need to do now is to simply achieve the things that we desire," Black Sethe threw out his final profound sentence before turning silent.

This was the first time that Garen had come across a theoretical system like this. One-third of a human's time was spent on sleeping and dreaming, and the supposed dreamless sleep was merely regular sleep where a person forgot their own dreams, as it was impossible for someone not to dream at all.

The human body had undergone many years of evolution and abandoned many unnecessary functions. Since dreaming during sleep still remained, this phenomenon could not be without reason. Garen suddenly realized that his understanding of his own body was still far from satisfactory…

After pondering in the pool for a long time, he finally rose from the water slowly before a maid came over, wiped the water off his body and wrapped him in a towel.

He sat on the white deck chair beside the pool. Behind him were dense green thickets and clumps of grass, while little lamp stands were placed on the white brick borders around the entire swimming pool, giving off pale yellow light that looked like small cylindrical lanterns.

Garen chose to lie on the deck chair while looking up at the starry sky. The night breeze blew gusts of cool, refreshing air towards him.

In the left side of the brilliantly lit villa, two hired maids could be seen sweeping the rooms and changing the curtains.

Unconsciously, Garen closed both of his eyes slowly before the sensation of drowsiness drifted through his mind.

During his moments of blurriness, a dull noise echoed beside his ears suddenly.

Bang!

He opened his eyes at once before noticing from the corner of his eye that a white object was rushing towards him.

His body rolled away involuntarily and he somersaulted beside the pool a few times before finally landing steadily at the back entrance of the villa. When he turned back to look, he noticed that a familiar shadow was reflected in his eyes.

At the area where he was laying earlier, a gigantic five-meter tall White Doll was standing there. It resembled a toy figurine that was molded with plasticine. Numerous doll arms, legs, and heads were jumbled up inside its body, making it look extremely strange.

"White Dolls again?" Garen moved his body for a while because he knew that he was already dreaming. Long-term exercises allowed him to focus his consciousness and move freely in his dreams.

'Be careful, this Doll is unlike the previous ones. It seems to belong to the squad leader level.' Black Sethe's voice echoed beside his ears softly.

"I know," Garen nodded.

The White Doll took long strides towards him. It made big steps on the surface of the swimming pool but seemed to be walking on smooth glass instead as there were no signs of it sinking at all.

Its chubby head was devoid of all five sensory organs. There was only a little white doll's leg that was protruding outwards like a white horn.

'The squad leader level White Dolls possess at least two times the strength of the normal dolls. You must be careful,' said Black Sethe seriously.

Garen did not reply. He dodged and moved towards his right quickly and evaded the strike from the White Doll's fist.

Kachak!

When the White Doll's fist hit the floor, it seemed as if it had struck a surface that was made of either ice or glass. It formed numerous cracks throughout the floor.

Garen put on the bath towel and circled the White Doll. This big fellow had slow movements, and although its recovery abilities were alarming, as long as he was careful, it was not difficult to get rid of it. Before this key moment, he would've needed to be extremely careful to prevent himself from being sucked in by the White Doll's speedy fists and attacks.

However, that was not necessary anymore.

'Their movements are becoming more complicated. For some reason, I can smell an unpleasant smell. It's a very familiar yet indistinguishable smell, so you'd better be more careful,' said Black Sethe vigilantly.

Clang!

Suddenly, a strange, dull knocking sound could be heard.

The White Doll's movements had stopped, and it stood on the side and looked at Garen quietly.

Clang!!

There was another dull noise.

Clang! Clang! Clang! Clang!

The sound continued to ring out rhythmically and continuously.

It sounded as if numerous metallic sounding drum beats were sounding off simultaneously while being blended with many other noises.

Throughout the areas surrounding the pool and villa, the forest seemed to faintly transform into a twisted and blurry high wall that was covered with dark whirlpools.

Numerous gigantic figures walked out of the dark whirlpools slowly before it was discovered that they were similar five meters tall White Doll squad leaders as well.

These Dolls surrounded Garen while the surface area of the pool had seemed to expand in the blink of an eye. It had become much broader, allowing the Dolls to stand on top without having to squeeze with one another.

"They're being serious this time, huh?" Garen lowered his body slightly while his gaze became more intense.

'You'll die if you're not careful,' replied Black Sethe. 'Pay attention to their mud sputtering. Don't let their white mud touch your body.'

Six White Doll leaders surrounded Garen and forced him into the middle.

'Each of them has enough strength to produce at least four tons of impact forces, so don't meet their force with even more force!' reminded Black Sethe frantically.

"Four tons?" The corners of Garen's mouth curled before his right foot stomped on the ground suddenly.

There was a banging noise before a white stone that was a meter long was sent flying from the ground, before finally being caught in his hand.

Shh…

After a violent hissing noise from gushing air, Garen's body bent backward like a crooked bowstring. His chest rose up high while strong air currents formed something that resembled a white cyclone near his cupid's bow.

Bang! Boom!!!

The stone in Garen's hand was maniacally flung at the speed of lightning. It spun through the air speedily like a white loop and rushed towards one of the White Dolls.

A dull banging noise was heard.

The White Doll collapsed on the ground at once. Its entire upper body looked as if a bomb had exploded there. It was completely smashed, making it impossible to see its initial shape.

Pfoo…

Garen exhaled slowly while shrouds of white gas surrounded him. The muscles throughout his entire body were slightly raised and were somewhat larger than before, while a slightly black and extremely glossy texture now appeared all over.

'Shit… Did you take some sort of drug??!!' said Black Sethe finally exclaimed in a hoarse voice while stunned.

Garen remained silent and walked towards the side of the villa before accurately striking a stone pillar that was as thick as a person with his fist.

After a banging noise rang out, the stone pillar broke and was immediately single-handedly held up by Garen. He lifted it at once as if it was merely a large stick.

Two Dolls had just charged over from behind him with their large white fists positioned to viciously smash Garen's head in. At the same time, white mud droplets were constantly dripping down their bodies, and whenever the mud fell on the floor, pungent and choking fumes would form there at once.

Before the white fists could strike Garen's back, a crashing noise could be heard near both of the Dolls when they were violently struck by the white stone pillar. The stone pillar broke and turned into dust immediately while the Doll's bodies were smashed into two halves at the same time. They turned into a mess of disintegrated white mud mid-air.

The three remaining White Dolls who were unfazed by their comrades' deaths worked together and charged towards Garen. They attempted to use their large sizes to smash Garen while boiling mud bubbled all over the surface of their bodies.

Garen moved his body to the side and swung his right leg suddenly. He used the tips of his toes to draw a sharp arc suddenly while releasing unimaginably loud and sharp hissing air noises.

The moment his toes touched the White Dolls' bodies, it seemed like a sharp blade had sliced through melted butter, immediately halving the White Dolls.

Tch tch tch!!

Garen drew a large semi-circle in front of himself with his toes that release a sharp whistle when it sliced the three White Dolls into six parts. All six pieces of their large bodies collapsed on the ground heavily, making dull noises as they fell. However, their life forces were strong, allowing them to continue rolling and struggling on the ground while attempting to piece their bodies back together again.

However, Garen immediately stretched his hand out and shot a few more stones at their heads. These little stones possessed bullet-like explosive forces when they were shot out, and were able to blast the three White Dolls' heads to smithereens instantly.

Suddenly, the entire area surrounding the pool began to quieten down as everything returned to a peaceful state.

Garen shook off the white mud that had sputtered on his body. His bath towel had been corroded to rags, but the skin on his body was still completely unharmed as these were the terrifying results of achieving seven points of physical qualities.

He took a few steps towards the White Doll corpses and collected all of their Void Cores.

'Your powers…' Black Sethe suddenly had no words to describe Garen anymore. This person who was once clear-cut in his eyes was now had a thin layer of malicious air about him, making him mysterious and unpredictable.

In the beginning, he was almost killed during his fight with the White Doll foot soldiers. However, he was now able to get rid of six leaders on his own. A difference like this… He did not understand Garen at all anymore.

"It feels different from before," said Garen suddenly.

Black Sethe returned to his senses and suddenly smelled the pungent smell again. It was obvious that it was a sweet smell but for some reason, he still felt extremely repulsed whenever he sniffed it.

Throughout their surroundings, the White Doll corpses on the ground gradually disappeared while the area fell into silence once more.

'Be careful! Dodge towards your right!!' Black Sethe suddenly felt an extremely dangerous threat charging at them from the front. Its speed was unbelievably quick like a lightning bolt. Even a blink would be insufficient to describe its speed!

That ray of white light burst forth ten meters in front of them and appeared in front of Garen's face instantly.

Clang!!!!

A loud metallic noise that sounded like a collision could be heard before shrouds of white smoke exploded and formed a ring of dark clouds and dust.

Both of Garen's arms were crossed in front of his body while his palms were gently but determinedly pressed against a large silver sword. The blue veins in both of his arms were raised while the muscles in his entire body swelled up fiercely. Meanwhile, a squeaking noise could be heard continuously when he used the strength in his palms to struggle with the sword.

Below his feet, two large spider web cracks broke through the solidified water and extended throughout the entire surface of the swimming pool.

'You… Actually caught it?!!' Black Sethe yelled in complete disbelief.

Chapter 650: Traitor 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Amazing sword technique…" Garen's eyes were brimming with light.

He waited until the mist dispersed. He then saw a tall and slender female figure standing behind the silver mark knife, which was three meters long and planted in the middle of the pool.

She was a strange lady. She has a sensual body as both her chest and butt were protruding out, and she was in a milk-white dress without any sleeves. The skirt was split from both sides like a cheongsam, revealing her pale and delicate legs.

Her hair was black as ink. She put away her sword as she turned it one round in the air before piercing it into the ground beside her. The sword was pierced deep into the ground and stood firmly.

The strangest thing about her was her face.

She was wearing a light black metal mask. On the left, it was sad and on the right it was happy.

"Al… My beloved brother." As the woman opened her mouth, a deep male tone came out instead of a woman's. In addition, she was speaking in Ancient Endor's language which Garen was very familiar with.

"The traitor… even the traitor has appeared… What kind of luck do you have!?" even Black Sethe's voice sounded strange. "This isn't someone you should be facing at your level!!"

Garen was expressionless as he ignored Black Sethe's outburst.

Sigh…

He exhaled a stream of white gas and then he inhaled deeply. Afterimages of his right hand appeared in front of his chest as he spontaneously jabbed an acupoint at the center of his chest.

Pew!!

The muscle there sunk in as it formed a deep socket before a jet of air was expelled out of it.

Garen's body suddenly expanded as his hands turned black. His skin was like a black metal, solid and hard.

"Who are you?" Garen asked in a deep tone. "And who's Al?"

"The woman laughed lightly. Her laugh was as light as a bell peal. Although it was a laugh of a girl, the moment she opened her mouth, a male's tone came out.

"You have the blood of my brother, the Void Nine-Headed Dragon, flowing in you. Did you not know that? Its soul and will are even fused into your soul. I have been searching for so long,"

She reached out her right hand. Her jaded fingers were long and mellow and as she flicked her fingers, a yellow copper coin appeared out of nowhere. There was a ferocious dragon head imprinted onto the coin and the other side of the coin was a pattern of three rings connected in series.

"I finally found its blood. It shall be mine. "She chuckled. "I am what you and the others know as the traitor… the traitor who would rather become a void creature."

"She's an Army Level! Every traitor is at least an Army level!" Black Sethe's voice sounded beside Garen's ears. "She's the upper general who commands a huge army of void creatures! It would be fine if my body is here, but…"

"Are you here to kill me as well?" Garen stared at the opponent as he growled.

"Kill you?" she started laughing as if she heard something very ridiculous. "This is not called killing… this is purifying. We of the Void has always been enemies to the Underworld Civilization. There's no room left for discussion, no?"

"Fighting against the strong is always my dream." Garen moved his leg and strode towards the opponent. His footsteps were heavy and powerful as the dream world trembled with every of his step.

"Interesting…" The opponent stopped smiling as the gaze under the mask finally took him seriously. "Looks like you're an outstanding person from the Underworld. Back in my days when I achieved the Eighty One Magical Slash, among all the strong ones, only Caps has the same pure fighting spirit as you."

"The opponent was once an elite who practiced Secret Technique. Every traitor was once an outstanding person in the Mage Civilization, so you have to be careful! Their Secret Techniques are definitely one of the best." Black Sethe reminded him softly.

Garen didn't need Black Sethe's reminder, as he could already feel that the opponent was the same as him. She was already above the level of King of the Century and her Secret Technique had achieved the realm of the legends.

In this world, among the Secret Techniques that he practiced, excluding the Slaughtering Hand, the Seven Star Life Secret Technique combined with his battle skills was his strongest technique. The Two-faced Waterbird Fist Technique and the other normal battle skills would probably be ineffective against this level of opponent.

Against an opponent of this level, any secret methods or techniques that were simple could be immediately understood and similar techniques could be created by them. It was to the point where they could trace thousands of secret techniques to a single source. In this realm of Secret Techniques, they were without a doubt at the level of Master.

Only a unique, delicate, complicated and powerful secret method was something they could use and others couldn't. In the legend, there even were Masters who would purposely add in many disruptive techniques to blind the opponent's vision.

As the two of them stood still while facing each other, the dream environment started to fall apart as cracks started to appear. The swimming pool's scenery started to tremble and black pieces started to fall away. It was as if the surrounding was set up with clothes and backdrops.

"Unfortunately… You haven't reached the peak that you have imagined… Your body is still too young." The woman whispered. "Ten years."

"What?" Garen raised his hand and was prepared to open the second star's acupoint. The opponent's invisible aura was giving off so much oppression that he could barely breathe.

"I'll wait for you for ten years, in hopes that you can reach the peak." The woman continued. "If…"

Kaboom!!!

With an explosion, countless black rubble pieces flew behind Garen as he leaped towards the enemy, like a terrifying predator going after its prey.

"I don't need ten years." He muttered.

In the dream, two black and white figures collided with each other.

"Second star!!"

Garen's body expanded once more and he was now at least two meters tall. His skin was black and he looked like a metal giant. He rushed towards the woman with both of his hands aiming at her.

He, who had activated the second star could produce hundreds of metric tons of force at this high speed.

His hands were weapons as hard as steel as it clashed against the lady's huge mark knife.

In an instant, the mark knife started to vibrate at high speed like an electrical saw as it moved up and down. A strange stickiness came from the sword and was stuck to Garen's hand. To be precise, it was more like biting down on him.

Garen's hands pressed hard against the mark knife. As both of them started to vibrate at high speeds, sparks started flying all over the place.

A few hundred tons of force was instantly placed on the woman, pushing her back far away.

"Dragon's Spine Slash!" Her face was filled with excitement. It was the battle exhilaration when a strong fighter met another strong fighter.

A mysterious white light which resembled a sword suddenly came out behind her and was going towards Garen's neck. It was like a huge dragon's tail whipping towards him. In this instant, the strength she released was even stronger than Garen's.

The light was incredibly fast, and Garen's hand was glued with the big mark knife and wouldn't budge at all. He could only see the light coming his way and he could do nothing about it.

Without time to think, he instantly bent backward, steadied himself and stomped onto the ground with his right leg.

Boom!

Mixed with the explosion, countless rubble fragments from the ground were shot out at high speed. However, the woman didn't care in the slightest as the stones freely pummeled her body; there was no marks of injury on her at all.

However, Garen's objective wasn't this. A huge amount of rubble flew straight at the side of the light and upon collision, the original direction of the light was shifted.

Then, Garen immediately used all of his strength and struck the woman's knee.

Two of them were separated by the reaction force.

The dream was completely shattered as both of them were left standing in an empty space. There was nothing left in their surroundings but darkness.

"I have underestimated you…" The woman said after realizing the strength from the last attack as she glanced at the surrounding.

"Unfortunately, the environment couldn't withstand our battle. I'll see you again. My name is Nadia, remember it…"

'Nine-Headed Dragon Queen Nadia…" Black Sethe's voice appeared once more.

"I'm Garen," Garen announced his name as he stared at the opponent who was slowly slipping into the darkness.

"Garen, we will meet again very soon…" Nadia's voice came from afar as her voice volume gradually decreased until nothing could be heard.

"You're in deep shit. The Nine-Headed Dragon Queen was one of the traitors in our generation. She has eighty-one lives and every death would increase her strength by one fold. At the end of her life, she would be eighty-one times stronger than before. It's something that can't be imagined!" Black Sethe seemed to recall the days of the past.

Garen suddenly recalled his days in the Totem World where he'd first obtained the talent of the Nine-Headed Dragon. With the Nine-life Talent, he could revive nine times, but compared to Nadia, the difference was too much.

"Eighty-one times…" Garen's current strength was quite close to the peak days in the Totem World. Although his body's attributes weren't as good as back then, activating the second star of the Seven Star Life's Secret Point would double his current attribute, which was about twenty-one points. However, he would have to increase the life force of his Slaughtering Hand in order to meet the exhaustion of such skill as his body's regeneration wasn't enough to activate the second star. As for the remaining third, fourth and even the last star… the current Garen wasn't able to obtain such power as the activation of each star would require a lot of life force. With his current storage of life force, he wouldn't be able to activate beyond the second star.

Chapter 651: Relearn 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Kachak!

With a clear, crisp sound, Garen, who was laying on the deck chair, immediately opened his eyes. He didn't know when he'd fallen asleep on the chaise longue.

He massaged his head as he slowly got up, while pain shot through his body.

"Just now, was that real?"

Black Sethe's voice immediately appeared.

'If you wish to die you can take it as fake. Even the legendary Nine-Headed Dragon Queen Nadia has appeared and you even set a time and place to fight again in the future. Tsk tsk… I wonder how brave you are, this is not the right way to seek death.'

"If I don't make an appointment with her, would she let me go?" Garen calmly got up.

'Of course not.'

"Then there's no difference right?"

Garen stood up from the deck chair. His surroundings were silent and only the chirping of crickets could be faintly heard. The dark forest beside the swimming pool looked mysterious and quiet beside the yellow light.

A female servant was sitting near a door behind the villa as she held onto the door half asleep. Her head was almost at the top of the towel on a small round table beside her.

Garen recalled the situation that had just occurred. It was as if everything was just a dream.

He walked around the swimming pool once and didn't see any trace of destruction. It was completely normal.

Suddenly, his eyes focused on a white chair on the right side of the swimming pool. He squatted down and slowly picked up a small item underneath it.

It was a coin and seemed to be made out of some sort of a metal. It had three circles connecting each other in series imprinted on it.

He flipped over the coin and saw an image of a ferocious dragon head on it.

He immediately recalled back the coin in Nadia's hand before she left.

'This is a coin left behind by her, which will act as a marking and token. With this here, you'll never be disturbed by any normal void creatures until she finds you again.' Black Sethe explained.

Garen gently held the coin tightly. He felt that he had seen this sort of material from somewhere before.

Suddenly, he recalled his memory where he obtained a relic from a black-shirted man and one of the relics was a mask made of a similar material. However, that mask was light black whereas the coin was yellow copper. He wasn't sure why but he felt that these two were connected to each other.

"What is this? What is it made of?" Garen asked softly.

'No idea. Perhaps it's something Nadia created after joining the Void Creatures. Ever since she became a traitor, she would hand out this coin before she officially kills her target out of respect. Why do you ask? Who cares what this is made out of?" Black Sethe couldn't comprehend his thoughts.

"Nothing." Garen didn't say much further.

It looked like he had to start searching for relics from all over the world… He wasn't sure when would Nadia's next visitation would be, but it shouldn't be late.

He kept recalling that mask. His instinct kept telling him that he could obtain an unexpected result if he were to investigate that mask.

**************

In the universe of the void dream, in the endless darkness, two figures swiftly appeared like comets flying across the darkness and breaking apart as both of them were shining brightly.

This was the black dream zone where no one had ever set foot in before. It was the realm between the void and reality, where all consciousness and dreams were created. It wasn't a place in the Material World yet it could affect the Material World.

Two white comets trailed long white tails as they brought light to the darkness.

Within the white lights were two thin and tall people, both male and female. The man's eyebrows and hair were red similar to of fresh blood. He had his hair combed up and was wearing a white cloak with a black circular thorn imprinted on it.

The girl had waist-length blue hair which was smooth as satin. Her facial features were very beautiful but her gaze was dead. Upon closer inspection, she didn't seem to have pupils at all. Instead, what she had were two blue crystal beads. She was in a light blue soft armor with a rippled white metal texture on the side. Overall, she looked beautiful as the soft armor streamlined her body contours as if she was wearing a skintight blue dress.

"This is Nadia's black dream zone. She must be nearby." The man whispered as he used the Ancient Endor's language. "Elfie, do you see any movement?"

The blue haired lady seemed to be trying to listen for something. After a while, she frowned.

"She seemed to have fought with someone… The opponent is definitely not your typical opponent. Both of them were separated when the dream shattered and Nadia left afterward. Her current whereabouts are unknown."

"Who could fight against her?" The man frowned. "Even the white dolls are hard to handle."

"I don't know. Ever since we gave up our flesh and entered the dream world, my eyesight has become poorer over time. I've validated it myself that I'm fine if I were to search for other stuff, but it's different when it comes to Nadia. I suspect that she may have found a way to deal with my ability."

Elfie whispered.

"We are different from those Void Creatures. They're able to absorb energy from the voids of the dream and we can't."

"The other hunters should have their own ways to solve this problem, right?" The man asked.

"I don't know if they're other hunters. Perhaps there's only the two of us within this vicinity… We haven't heard anything from the Headquarters for many years." Elfie softened her tone.

Both of them became quiet as if they didn't have the mood to speak any further.

In the legends of many worlds, the Nine-Headed Dragon Queen Nadia was a forbidden name and she had a lot of names.

The Good and Evil Devil, Mother of all Dragons, Giant Dragon of Destruction, Spirit Realm's warrior, etc…

Her power seemed to be endless as she would come back twice as strong with every death. They had been pursuing Nadia for countless of years and had experienced immeasurable agony and hopelessness.

Countless of hunters have died in her hands. They were once Nadia's friends and partners and that was the reason why they had been left unharmed each time. However, this made them even more eager to pursue her so that they could find out the reason why she had betrayed them.

However, Nadia seemed to be avoiding them at all costs.

"There seem to be auras of other hunters here in this world…" Elfie suddenly spoke.

"Other hunters? Is it Prophet Camado? Or is it Flame's Sicke? Perhaps Giant Sisyphus?" The man asked softly. These people were hunters they'd met within the past few years. Although they were not as strong as Nadia, each of them had their unique escape methods, which was the main reason why they still lived to this day. Perhaps, along with the rest, they were Ancient Endor's remaining hunters.

The remaining hunters were most likely unqualified normal hunters. They were commoners whose Secret Technique had yet to reach its peak and they usually worked together to fend off the void worms at best. As for the white dolls or void devourers, they were not something these hunters could hope to fight against.

No matter how strong they were in the Material World, they would be just fat meat waiting to be cut apart without proper training in the Dream World.

Among the remaining adherents of Ancient Endor, only they were able to freely track Nadia's whereabouts in the Dream World while fighting against the Void Creatures. They were the protectors of the remaining adherents.

The pride of the remaining Mages might end with their generation.

************

Within the dream world in a certain black zone.

Gas bubbles similar to red balloons suddenly appeared in the area. They were about fist-sized each and soon expanded as if they were being inflated.

Soon the red bubbles had a surface area of about one kilometer.

Inside the bubble.

Nadia was in a white dress and had the huge silver white mark knife in her hand. She was standing quietly on a bloody battlefield, which was the scenery inside the bubble.

There was a crimson crescent moon in the sky of the ancient battlefield. There were no stars and the sky was dyed rust red. The surrounding was filled with black hills and gullies as blood kept flowing in between the hills and gullies. The sound of the flow was very lively.

As time passed, Nadia closed her eyes, waiting for something.

After a few days, blood started to fly everywhere on the black ground in front of her. What came out from the ground were pitch black giant dolls slowly climbing out from it.

Growl…

They growled loudly as the ground split apart while they crawled out. Their heights and shapes were similar to the white dolls. What differentiated them from the white dolls was that they were equipped with thorny black armors from head to toe. It was very strange.

These black dolls were at least six meters tall. They formed a line instinctively as if they knew how to order themselves up. They were so densely packed that no one knew how many of them were there.

"Nadia?" Suddenly a man's voice came from afar. "Why have you come to this place? This is my nest, not a tourist spot for you to sightsee."

"Nothing. I was bored so I came for a walk." Nadia opened her eyes as she said calmly. She glanced at the group of black dolls. "Is this your newly recruited team? They look very annoying…"

She then held her three-meter long sword tightly.

"They're so packed together that they're annoying!!"

With a click, the sword was unsheathed from the ground.

"Three Light!"

Before she finished her sentence, three silver white lights shot out, forming into three groups of vortices, which headed their way towards the black dolls.

With Nadia's leg as the epicenter, three silver vortices with a diameter of tens of meters shot out. These vortices were like silver mouths as they went towards the black dolls.

"Nadia!!" The man shouted with rage as his voice was mixed with the cries of the black dolls. The three vortices started to devour the whole team and within tens of seconds, only broken limbs were left of the black doll army as they were all destroyed.

Chapter 652: Relearn 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"Why? Do you have any comment?" Nadia put away her big sword as she asked calmly.

That voice didn't say any further but it tried to hold back its raging growl as much as possible. It was like one was about to shout as loud as one could but held back.

Nadia raised her head and looked at the sky.

"The weather is bad and it's making my mood bad too. So annoying…" She stomped hard and the whole red bubble started to crack open. The surface's thin film started to crack from the sky above her and propagated outwards.

Boom!

The bubble suddenly exploded like a glass ball.

The voice cried out in pain and it didn't dare to speak another word. In the darkness, only a vengeful gaze from a pair of red eyes stared at Nadia.

He understood that she could be talked through if she was behaving normally. However, when she'd gone crazy, he would be seeking death if he were to speak further on.

Nadia never cared if he was the same kind as her. Everyone knew that she had killed a lot of Hunters and Freelancers, but only the Void Creatures knew that the number of Void Creatures she had killed was far more than the former.

"Considered myself unlucky! I'll treat this as a natural disaster!" This Void Lord was apoplectic but he knew that he could only accept it. There was no living being which was able to kill Nadia as she had eighty-one lives that would make anyone feel hopeless. If she were to be ambushed once, she would instantly revive and become twice as strong. Perhaps the mages in the ancient era who stood at the peak, the Demon King Level Mages or Great Abyss Level Void Creatures were able to fight against her. However, those beings in the legend had passed away thousands of years ago. Only a few true spirits were left in the Mother Stream but those were nothing to be compared with.

Nadia had always behaved based on her mood which changed on the go and no one could understand her. Hence no one had really understood her behavior but everyone knew one thing about her.

That was to not anger her when she was feeling down.

This Void Lord had just come back from another dream zone. He himself possessed terrifying powers, which far surpassed the base Nadia. If she were to use half of her strength at her eighty-first life, perhaps she could win against him but they had never fought against each other before.

However, Nadia was the kind of person who would fight with you to the death if she was in a bad mood. She was purely crazy for battles. Imagine a person who was about your level was willing to fight against you to death on a whim. Furthermore, Nadia was much stronger than this guy.

No one was willing to face such a situation. The Void Creatures had long lifespans hence no one would fight each other to death on a whim.

He didn't voice out anymore as he quietly left the place.

Nadia was floating alone in the void, surrounded by the pieces of the red gas bubble. She then casually vibrated her long sword, forming a layer of white light, which pushed away all the debris. She then, with a bored look on her face, floated away into the darkness without any destination.

A faint blood signal could be detected within the void. It was her only path that she was firmed on. It was the blood of her brother, AI the Nine-Headed Dragon's blood. As long as she followed this trace, she would eventually arrive at the dream that she'd set foot in before. Afterwards, she would force herself into reality based on the coin she had given earlier.

After Nadia disappeared, two white comets flew into the dream zone. It was two mysterious people in white cloaks.

Two of them looked around them suspiciously and didn't notice any trace of Void Creatures.

"It's the aura left behind by the Nine-Headed Dragon Queen. This is troublesome. We should take a detour."

"This is what we can only do. What an unlucky day. If everything goes to plan, we would have arrived already."

"Being impatient won't solve the problem."

After conversing softly, both of them took a detour and went on their way in a different direction.

As freelancers, they had memorized the auras of any strong character. Only the strong freelancers were able to face against such a powerful character. The rest would avoid her at all cost.

***************

'Are you really trying to abandon the Slaughtering Demon Technique?'

Black Sethe asked hopelessly.

Garen was sitting on his knees in one of the quiet rooms in the villa. His body was covered in a transparent aura as he closed his eyes and immersed himself to complete concentration.

"I'm not abandoning it, but I won't learn it further." He whispered.

'Isn't that the same as abandoning it?' Black Sethe felt hopeless.

In front of Garen was a black copper mysterious mask.

This mask was a relic that had been able to provide him with the most potential points. He found it and placed it by his side.

It had been at least ten days since he fought with Nadia and Garen had gathered the Void cores that he had obtained these past few days. This item was strangely solid as if it had some sort of unique effect. It surprisingly had amazing effects in treating the pollution and damage caused by the void creatures.

'The Void core. It was able to strengthen the capability of the hunters or you can convert them into life force and absorb them.' Black Sethe explained softly. 'The hunters are generally powerful in the Secret Technique realm. Although there is no minimum threshold, hunters without power or capability will die in the hands of the void creatures. The hunter's characteristics will practically change the moment they've sworn to the Mother Stream.'

"I can already feel it." Garen nodded as he reconstructed his Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Technique in an attempt to improvise the portion that this world did not allow. There was a slight difference between this world's physics and the previous one's, causing the potency of this evil technique to be greatly reduced. He wasn't able to create powerful icy blue halberds, but it was still very useful in other parts.

He was trying to take out this most primitive portion.

The Void core seemed to have some sort of mysterious effect on him as it could give him an endless supply of spiritual power to his consciousness. This allowed him to think at a rapid speed. At the same time, these cores were slowly shrinking.

As Garen started to comprehend more and more, he could feel that his consciousness was flowing towards the void creatures. The Void cores seemed to have given out some sort of a radiation as his consciousness was getting more similar to those of the void creatures. This change wasn't something bad as this allowed his consciousness to achieve a calmer and faster state. To someone who practiced Secret Technique, this was an ideal state for him to understand and deduce the Secret Techniques.

Garen started to understand why some Martial Adepts would side with the Void Creatures. The main difference between the hunters and traitors seemed to be their Vow. The Hunters seemed to have vowed towards the Mother Stream to kill the void creatures for eternity.

His thinking became more and more active as his thinking in terms of the Secret Technique was very instinctive.

The core of the Northern Trident Frost-Fire True Water Technique was swiftly kicked aside and to his surprise, he found out that the core of it was the seeds of both of the Living Secret Techniques he had obtained in the ancient ruins.

This portion of the information that could be used anywhere in every world, was surprisingly about the seeds of the Living Secret Technique he obtained previously.

Garen wasn't sure how long he had meditated, but when he had cut out the entire portion of the evil technique, he realized how strong the creator of the Living Secret Technique was.

"So this is the true purpose of the seed…" Garen finally understood why the Living Secret Technique resembled a seed. It was because it could grow according to the different laws of different worlds.

It was just like a seed, which would grow differently under different soils.

Garen finally understood this with the help of the Void core. Black Sethe was still complaining in his ear. He seemed to be trying to persuade him to turn back and continue learning the Slaughtering Demon Technique.

However, he had already found out the way to turn the Slaughtering Demon Technique's stored life force into nutrients for his new Living Secret Technique.

Garen sat on his knees in the middle of the room as he recalled the core knowledge of the Living Secret Technique.

Suddenly, he opened his eyes and stared at the air in front of him.

In his vision, he could only see two bright dots which no one knew when they'd appeared. They were floating up and down in front of him. One was dark red while the other was deep blue.

The icy blue bird spread its wings. The huge bird had a beautiful, long tail feather as if it was the Phoenix from the legends. It had a tremendous amount of cold emitting from it and its beak was the seed.

On the other hand, the dark red was in a devil's shape. It had a long pointy tail and was covered in fire. It was behaving like a gentleman, giving off an elegant and seductive vibe. In front of the devil was a dark red cross sword, which was the original shape of the Metal Living Secret Technique's seed.

"Perhaps these two represent the knowledge of the Secret Techniques that can be used in any world." Garen realized.

He had once chosen the wrong path and chose to learn the Slaughtering Demon Technique which had wasted his time and energy. Now, it was time for him to reaffirm his direction. He had learned a few things from learning the Slaughtering Demon Technique and had a deeper understanding of some theories. Furthermore, the Slaughtering Demon Techniques possessed the effects of storing life force, which could be used as a backup storage to recover his injuries, similar to the Nine-Headed Dragon's Nine-life Talent which could increase his survivability.

He now possessed his own invention secret skills, the Seven Star Life's Secret Point, through which he could attain a terrifying height without any Secret Techniques. Once he learned a new Secret Technique, his prowess would achieve a new height and he would attain more strength to slowly surpass the strength he'd possessed in the Totem World.

Chapter 653: Mysterious Mask 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen stared at the two glowing dots floating in front of him. He hesitated slightly when he realized that these two lights were not physically real but images by his brain.

He was lucky that he was able to merge out a powerful technique last time, but he couldn't be lucky every single time.

He focused his gaze as he reached out his hand to touch the icy blue seed.

As he finger touched the icy blue seed, a familiar Secret Technique image appeared in the Attribute Pane in his vision. It was an ice sculpture of a bird which spanned its wings wide. Its wings were very elegant as its body was covered with frost, just like the legendary blizzard phoenix.

'Unnamed Living Secret technique: First grade (Ice type Living Secret Technique, total of four grades)'

Garen remained his expression as he felt a coolness spinning in his inner body. After that the coolness spread out with a terrifying amount of coolness all over his body, skins and organs included. This formed into a huge and complicated web.

It was as if he knew what he was doing. The soul seed had reconstructed his body since young and in addition to Garen's incredibly high physical attribute, Garen instantly learned it. The tough understanding and will of the Living Secret Technique were given to him without hardship.

'You really have done it!' Black Sethe shouted, 'And it's a Living Secret Technique!'

The Slaughtering Demon Technique diminished quickly as the Living Secret Technique grew. The Slaughtering Demon Technique was supposedly the one which swallowed the Living Secret Technique. However, under Garen's delicate control and management, he was able to completely control it, allowing the Ice Living Secret Technique to swallow it instead.

The demon technique that he had learned had already reached an advanced level and he had instantly grasped the foundation of the Living Secret Technique. He would have to slowly grind it out in the future as he had to slowly reconstruct his body to his needs.

'You're crazy! Do you know how long it is required to train yourself to reach back your current level? You abandoned the Demon Technique and the stronger your Living Secret Technique is, the life force you are able to store decreases, which makes your activated Seven Star Secret Method weaker! Your overall strength will become weaker and weaker! You're literally committing suicide right now!' Black Sethe shouted as she tried to persuade Garen to turn back.

"I don't need something impure," Garen replied calmly. Although the additional life force was useful to his Seven Star Life's Secret Point, this alone wasn't the reason he decided to switch his path as he knew that Black Sethe's Demon Technique definitely had a hidden trap that no one knew.

Instead of walking on the same path, he took a bet and relearned everything. He hoped that he could obtain more Relics to absorb the potential points before Nadia appeared. He couldn't have won against Nadia with his previous strength, to begin with.

As his path was getting more complicated, he decided to choose a path that was pure.

***********

"Garen hasn't been replying lately." Jason was unenthusiastically helping Trish beat the eggs with the egg beating machine, which was stirring the eggs in a big bowl.

"You're in your twenties! You don't even have a girlfriend and now I have to worry about your life." Trish was busy in the kitchen. She wanted to create an egg pie but he felt that she'd messed up the procedures.

Jason, on the other hand, was standing at the entrance of the kitchen and was about to carry the beaten eggs to her.

"Little Vivien too, ever since she'd entered puberty, she's started to not respect me as her brother." He said with a very bored look.

"Isn't that because you've done something wrong somewhere?" Trish didn't have the time to tend to her son's dilemma. "Teenagers are often rebellious. However, I'm more concerned when you will go to school. Your university's semester should be open by now right?"

"Who knows? I'm currently not interested in attending university." Jason said.

"This is not something that depends on your level of interest…" Trish turned her head around, revealing her gloomy face. "If you don't go to school, I will call Garen this moment and I'm sure you understand what comes after. Do you remember how much you've cried after you got beat up by Garen in your twenties?"

Jason then raised his hand up to show off his biceps.

"Call him, I'm not afraid of him anymore." He looked at his muscles in satisfaction. "Look at my muscles, I'm already at 100kg."He flexed as he tried to show off his muscles.

"Oh my god." Trish didn't know how to answer to her eldest son as she and Emmer weren't into muscles at all. She wondered how she had given birth to a son who could only think of muscles.

"By the way, the building at the edge of the town caught fire. Did you know?" Trish asked. "I heard that the people there saw the Isaros sisters."

"No. I was with them the other day swimming on the beach. Why would they go to where the place where it caught fire." Jason replied innocently.

"It's best if that's true. The police officer came to inquire about it. Even the officers in the city came to investigate. They're preparing something but I believe the Isaros sisters wouldn't do such a thing like causing a fire. They simply do not have the intention. I will talk about it with the city councilor John so that they won't accuse an innocent citizen."

Trish casually spoke her mind.

"Okay," Jason replied casually as well as his eyes were brimming with happiness. "I'm going to watch the competition today. It's the Battlefield Cannon! I can't miss this!"

"Just go." Trish was completely speechless with regards to her son.

Jason smirked as he ran back to his room with his tight black T-shirt and jeans. The door was slammed and soon a huge noise from the computer could be heard. The sound of the competition had rung.

Jason gently opened up his curtain as he looked at the window from another building afar.

The building was all white and the curtain on the second floor was opened up as well, revealing a cute red-haired girl's face. She was Arisa.

Jason smirked as he pulled out his index finger and thumb, signaling an OK gesture.

Arisa's face was brimming with happiness as nodded excitedly at Jason before letting the curtains fall back down.

After a while, Jason's phone started to vibrate and he immediately rushed towards his phone and looked at the screen.

It was a message from Arisa.

'I've sent the pictures to your email. With my reputation on the line, these are definitely sexy. All of the pictures were taken when my sister is changing clothes.'

'Thank you so much!!!' Jason was delighted as he replied immediately. He then clumsily rushed towards his laptop and opened his email. Behold, he saw an email with a huge attachment attached to it.

'Do you want something even more erotic?' Arisa sent another message.

'Yes!' Jason replied. He was literally holding onto his phone as if it was the most precious treasure.

'I need you to help me on something…'

'You name it! As long as it's within my capability I will do it to my fullest!' Jason browsed his email as he placed the pictures into a hidden folder and named it as Arisa - No. 0. He then sat alone on one side and smiled immorally.

'Get me the latest picture of brother Garen. I want the latest picture and stop using those old pictures to reach the quota. There were a few old pictures of him from the previous batch you've sent me.' Arisa was very dissatisfied.

'But he hasn't been back recently. I can't do much here.'

'Aren't your hacking skills very good? Take more pictures of him.'

Jason pondered for a bit and then he quickly opened a hidden folder, archived the files inside and sent it over to her.

In the other room, Arisa smiled wickedly as she received the folder. After browsing it, she transferred the pictures into a hidden file and renamed it as Garen - HD.

"Hehehe…" Arisa started to laugh satisfactorily.

"Arisa! What are you doing? Can you please help me take my towel for me." Isaros's voice called from the bathroom.

"Okay!" Arisa quickly returned to her lady and elegant vibe. She tidied up her look before going straight to the bathroom.

Arisa was very smart as she was able to settle the whole ordeal with just a few lewd pictures of her sister. She even managed to obtain a few high definition sexy photos of Garen.

The whole process was perfect!

The crystal clear water was freely flowing down from Isaro's body as she closed her eyes while standing in the bathroom.

Ever since the battle with the Blood Breed Lars, she had obtained some rather complicated injuries. Since she didn't have recovery abilities as good as those Blood Breeds, it took her more than a month to actually recover to a rather normal state.

She didn't want to get caught in such a complicated matter. She'd only wanted to help Sir Pritto with a small matter and push everything back to the Blood Breeds so that she and her sister could return back to the peaceful and quiet life.

However things didn't go as she expected, instead of settling down, everything became worse. She got snared even deeper after the fight with Lars.

Within a month, she had been ambushed by vampires three times. These vampires were like ashes as they kept interrupting her during her rest and recovery. She received the news from Pritto that these vampires were sent by Lars. He refused to let other Blood Breeds meddle as it seemed that being injured by a Mortal was too embarrassing for him. He specifically said that he would settle the matters alone to obtain back his reputation.

The bad thing about this was that Lars had lost his cool. When a true Lower-Level Blood Breed and district person-in-charge had lost his cool, it meant that he would do anything necessary to achieve his goal.

The good thing about this was that Lars had blocked off other Blood Breeds who wanted to dirty their hands in this mess.

Isaros understood very well that Lars would come after her very soon.

As she stood in the hot water bath, she unconsciously raised up her right hand. With her hand as sharp as a knife, she gently cut through the fog around her without any noise.

"Since I can't avoid this, then I will face it head on." Her resolution woke up from her exhaustion.

*************

Knock knock knock.

After a rhythmic knock on the door, The white villa's door was opened, revealing an elegant woman.

"Please come on in, Master is in the study room on the second floor." A female servant in white clothes said softly to the guest.

Hochman entered the villa with a calm expression. His bodyguards, one female, and the other male tried to follow him in but were blocked off by him.

"You guys wait outside."

Two of them were stunned but lowered their heads and waited outside.

Hochman entered the living hall on the first floor. His muscles were very streamlined and he was at least two meters tall. Even his shirt couldn't cover up the muscles on his body as each and every fiber was clearly streamlined out. His hair was combed back and he was in a purple-black suit. His black shirt was slightly open, revealing a purple crystal necklace pendant on his chest.

Chapter 654: Mysterious Mask 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

He walked up to the second floor. As he took a turn, he heard the door open once more at the bottom.

"Welcome, Master is waiting for you on the second floor," The female servant said once more.

Hochman leaned forward and looked down and saw Dahm in a red shirt entering the villa. He had a smile on his face and his lips were dark red as if it was a solidified blood clot.

Dahm was much stronger than before. As he raised his head, they looked at each other and the atmosphere froze.

The bodyguards started to panic as they clutched nervously at the guns strapped at their waist, ready to fire at a moment's notice.

"You're early." Dahm smiled as he waved at him.

Hochman nodded his head slightly.

Two of them greeted each other as if they were at a friend's house. Then, both of them walked to the second floor.

Similarly, Dahm placed his bodyguards outside of the villa just like Hochman.

Both of them stepped onto the brown floor as they walked to the study room at the far end of the floor. Hochman then gently knocked on the door.

Knock knock knock.

"Enter." A gentle and calm voice could be heard from inside.

The door wasn't locked. Hochman pushed the door open gently. The room was laid with a layer of thick grey carpet and it felt very soft when stepped onto. There were two yellow lights standing on each side, giving off a bright yellow light.

The whole room was grey in color, including the wallpapers, tables, and chairs.

At the center of the room were a long table and two leather chairs.

Garen was sitting at the far end of the long table, facing its side as he looked at something. He only turned around and smiled when he heard noises.

As they entered the room, Hochman sat on the leather chair on the left. The chair was curved to fit a person's back smoothly. There even were golden textures on its side that couldn't be seen if one didn't take notice. It was a well crafted yet low-profile chair.

Dahm entered the room and sat in the other leather chair.

Both of them noticed a row of old picture frames and oil paintings hanging on the left side of the wall.

"These are my collections of relic oil paintings and some ancient photos. They're all old items." Garen smiled and explained. He was in a big white robe, similar to of pyjamas which made him looked relaxed and carefree.

"Is there anything for you to call us here?" Hochman maintained his gaze and asked softly.

The servant handed out three cups of fragrant coffee and immediately left the room afterward.

"A small problem." Garen crossed his hands as he smiled.

He raised two of his fingers, indicating the number of issues.

"First, I need you to do me a small favor." He opened the drawer on the table and took out a black metal mask.

The mask looked rather unusual. It was expressionless and slightly black in color. The forehead portion of the mask was densely packed with small eyes as if it was covered with small worms. It gave off a rather mysterious yet frightening vibe.

Garen placed the mask in the center of the table.

"If possible, get me the original version of this mask. Naturally, you can send over the fake versions to me."

Hochman took up the mask and glanced at it before placing it back down on the table

"No problem. If my network finds anything similar, I'll send it to you."

Dahm took up the mask and looked at it.

"No problem here as well. If it's very rare, then I can't do anything as well. I hope you understand."

No matter how one looked at it, with each of them arriving at such an advanced level, they had already known the tricks Garen used to control them. The Two-Face Water Bird Fist's most secret cheat was that it required Garen's aura and soul seed's aura to continuously offset it. So their Two-faced Water Bird Fist technique was limited by Garen. No matter how dissatisfied both of them were to this, they couldn't do anything before finding a way to bypass this issue.

"Alright." Garen nodded. This mask was one of the relics that were able to give him the most potential points. With this mask, it was able to give him a third of his needed potential points. This was the reason why he viewed it as an utmost importance.

After some of investigation, he found a terrifying truth.

This mask was also a fake, but it was created quite a long time ago. There was a record of such mask within the black-shirted man's records. This masked was called the Black Copper Mask, which had about twelve fake masks. According to the legend, every mask had a clue which led to the location of the real mask. If he could obtain all the Black Copper Masks, then he would be able to obtain the legendary original Black Copper Mask.

This was a secret discovered by the black-shirted men. Only Levi and a few higher level knew about it.

However, Garen accidentally found out that it possessed a tremendous amount of potential points, which made him interested in the mask.

"Secondly." He looked at the two people sitting in front of him. "Quentin and Xander came for a visit. They weren't here for the annual inner circle Secret Technique sparring adjustment. It's related to you two."

The whole room was in complete silence, both of them didn't speak up at all.

"Regarding the issues between you two, I do not wish to meddle in. You have your own circles, lives, and judgment. An outsider does not have the right to butt in. It's just that Quentin and the other members came to beg me so I'm placed in a tough spot." Garen said.

"I understand." Dahm smiled. "As long as Hochman agrees to reconcile, I have no issues."

"I'll consider it." Hochman closed his eyes and replied coldly.

"We are a group, a family. The fist technique is what that gathers us together. The path we take may have been different, but please don't forget the friendship we once had." Garen said calmly.

While both of them were laughing coldly in their mind, they put on a good appearance on the outside.

"I'm glad you two understand." Garen nodded satisfactorily

"I heard that Master has been looking for a quiet environment to learn a fist technique recently. Hochman and I have bought an ancient styled palace building located in East Asia Nappu Mountain. We have decided to gift it to you to show our appreciation towards your teachings." Dahm said sincerely.

Both of them seemed to be up to something as both of them spoke to Garen as if he was a legendary figure.

They had heard the rumors of a powerful martial artist in the combat club but didn't try to find an explanation for it, in fact, their every action had hidden motives in them. However, as they increased their strength and advanced to higher heights, they thought they could clearly see Garen's true potential. However, it was once blurred off again as they could feel Garen's aura which was similar to theirs. That aura was so big and powerful, it felt like it was an endless sea.

Furthermore, Garen's mood swung a lot. At times, he's cruel and cold-hearted and at times he could be gentle and peaceful.

Hence, they could only listen to him even though they wanted to betray him.

"Palace?" Garen felt strange. Technically, they were still students. No matter how much they skipped classes, they were still students in their twenties. However, when he saw their gaze and in addition to the intel and news he had obtained, he vaguely understood their intentions.

They planned to build a fist technique sect and make use of the powerful and mysterious technique to expand their power and authority. This would turn them into the main branch and increase their renown in the combat world. They would then stand in the position of the owners and main branch, a huge position.

They could even have the intention of readjusting the whole combat world.

After all, when their Two-Faced Water Fist Technique combined with their physical strength, they had already surpassed the limits of humans. This kind of strength was without a doubt something everyone would covet.

They had the dream of opening the first sect.

Garen suddenly understood the intention of these two. Both Hochman and Dahm were trying to come out with their own styles of Two-Faced Water Bird Fist technique.

"Alright. Since it's a gift from the two of you, I will accept it. That place can be a meetup point for the higher-ups of the combat club." He nodded as he accepted this luxurious gift.

Since he was currently mastering the Dream Technique, he would require a quiet environment. He'd recently learned that the attacks of the void creatures were able to harm surrounding living beings. In order to avoid the void creatures harming innocents, it was a good idea for him to choose a secluded area to train.

"Then I shall take my leave." Hochman stood up and bowed slightly.

"Me too. I have other matters to deal with." Dahm stood up and said lazily.

Frankly, when the two of them were facing Garen, a person whose face seemed flawless, they couldn't help but feel a sense of oppression from him. This made them very uncomfortable, which was the reason why they never stayed long here.

"Go, remember your promise," Garen said softly.

Both of them nodded and left the room.

As the footsteps distanced, he looked at the mask on the table. Instinctively, he reached out his hand and gently placed the mask on his face.

Somehow, from the moment he wore the mask, he could feel his aura start to change.

The Void Creatures started appearing in his dreams. The change was rather complicated, which was a totally different world from the material world.

At first, Garen had suspected that he'd been feeling unwell, as the Material World hardly had any supernatural phenomenon.

He put down the mask and examined it carefully but didn't find anything strange about it.

"This mask.." he could faintly feel that there was a mysterious secret hidden in it.

'It feels like some sort of magnetic field.' Black Sethe spoke. "This mask has a strange magnetic field as if it could change the brainwave of a living being."

"Alter the brainwave?" Garen was interested and Black Sethe seemed to progress rapidly as well as he absorbed the knowledge of this world. This world was too different from his previous world. The current world was set in a scientific civilization so there were a lot of things he needed to pick up.

The mask's surface was rather coarse as Garen took out the yellow copper coin Nadia had dropped earlier and felt its texture.

'This world's law is very solid. The forces between the particles are incredibly strong and a supernatural force would require a tremendous amount of energy to surface in the Material World. Even Nadia's overwhelming strength in the Dream World will immediately shrink in this world. She definitely had used an incredible amount of force to affect reality within the Dream World to leave a coin here.' Black Sethe said softly. 'Similarly, this mask which is able to display such supernatural phenomenon on its own means that it has a huge secret hidden within it.'

As he rubbed the mask and coin, Garen started to think deeply.

Chapter 655: Suppress 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Bam!!!

In a wide and spacious cathedral, a black figure was instantly smashed into the wall, like a butterfly stuck in a spider's web, his arms wide open, and he was held there by the countless green strands of web silk shining on the wall behind him, completely immobile.

He opened his mouth wide and roared wildly, but he emitted no sound whatsoever. This figure was completely pitch black, as though his whole body was made of black shadows, and he had no face at all, only a tiny bit of white light that could be seen inside his mouth when he opened it wide.

"What kind of a dream is this?" Garen stood in the center of the cathedral, confused. He felt as though there were gazes looking at him from all directions, but when he looked that way, he could not see anyone except himself, there was only the black figure stuck on the wall.

This was his first time having such a dream, he had not seen any of the things around him, and he could be a hundred percent certain of that because none of the patterns on the cathedral walls gave him any sort of strange feeling.

"Black Sethe?" He called out softly, but there was no response at all from inside his mind.

He looked up, glancing at the black figure struggling on the wall, that person was roaring wildly and madly, trying to break free from the webs. But that strange Green Death kept tightening its hold on him.

Garen tried his best to remain focused, and not let himself be distracted by everything happening around him, otherwise, the dream would devolve into a mess again.

He paid attention to his surroundings conservatively. The cathedral was blurred and bleary, he could obviously see the patterns around him, but when he tried to look closer, it was all a blur.

There were tall golden human statues standing on either side of him, each of them clasping a sword that was pointed at the ground tightly with both hands, each of them more than ten meters tall.

Garen lifted his legs and walked slowly inside the cathedral, he walked until he was underneath that stuck human figure, and he reached out his hand to touch that huge green silk web, but unfortunately there seemed to be a transparent piece of glass between him and the web, so all he could feel was a hard and smooth surface obstructing him.

Wooo…

All of a sudden there was a minute sound by his ear, and Garen's vision blurred slightly, his eyes losing focus.

"Mmgh…" He opened his eyes, and slowly straightened up from the reclining chair.

That dream just now was so realistic and strange, that he could remember it clearly even after waking up.

He was lying on a sofa in the second-floor living area, the alarm on his phone was ringing rhythmically. That was the alarm clock he had set beforehand.

Yanking his pajamas, Garen got off the sofa and stood up, it was completely quiet in the little living room, the maids had all gone to sleep. It was night time, the curtains beside the large open glass windows billowed in the wind, the night breeze puffing in and out of the balcony outside.

Garen walked to the balcony and looked outward.

Some of the little twinkling lights in the distance were fixed, others moved, and only a couple of the shops on the opposite street were still open, the rest were all closed. Occasionally there would be a few motorcycles revving past, breaking the silence of the night.

He picked up his phone from the coffee table, there were messages from Raffaele, from his parents, and even one from Jason, asking him when he was going back for a visit.

There was one more message, this one from Baldy.

After that guy went blind in one eye, he had always been angry at Levi's daughter, yearning for revenge, but under Garen's intimidation, he never made any real moves. His personality, however, became more and more violent.

Garen tapped the message from Baldy.

'Got some news about the Mask, there's a mask like that in a European old-money family's collection, showed up at a private auction once. We're communicating with the people now, hoping we can buy it, but they seem pretty firm that they're not planning to sell the mask. Looking for another way now.'

The message was sent last night at 11 pm. Garen glanced at the time now, it was 3.15am.

It should be 8 or 9 in the morning where Baldy was.

Garen sent a message directly.

'You can reveal a bit of your identity, if they're willing to sell it, then they can be considered a friend of the Nighthawks to some extent.'

After waiting for some time, there was a prompt response from the other side.

'Boss, this might be real hard, we Nighthawks don't have much of a market in Europe, the main places have all been taken up by the mercenary groups here, if we were in Africa that's fine, but here… Though we seem to have a bit of a breakthrough now.'

'Let them state whatever conditions they need, as long as it's not over the top, just agree to it, but remember the bottom line.' Garen replied.

'Understood.'

Garen put down the phone, by now he was already beginning to sense something different about the Black Copper Mask. After he put on the mask, he could still feel wisps of potential values streaming out of the mask, getting absorbed into his body.

Before this Garen clearly remembered that he had absorbed all of the potential value, but now there were new wisps of potential power.

This greatly increased his curiosity in the Mask.

*****************

"I promised you, Barcetina. I would not interfere with your private life before you turn twenty." In a luxurious study, a white-haired old man was talking to a young woman in a deep voice.

"You are nineteen now, you'll be twenty soon, and you'll have your twentieth birthday. I, your mother, and your grandmother, all hope that you can take the family business upon your shoulders." The old man paused, "You like collecting, we let you, you like fighting, we support you, and you also like movies, all of that is fine. But. You must be very aware that your future is not like that of your friends. Our business, the business your ancestors fought for, all of it is your hands to control, to protect so that it does not all go to waste. This is your responsibility as a member of this family. This is also the price you have to pay for all that you enjoy."

The young girl wore a white T-shirt and ripped jeans, looking just a normal delinquent girl. Her features were broad and rough, her face even looked like that of a boy, there was no hint of beauty in it anywhere, she was one of those types that people would be hard-pressed to find a way to praise.

Her skin had large pores, was neither fair nor dark, and was instead a dirty yellow. Her short hair was dry like dead grass, she had small eyes, a large nose, and a large mouth, as a girl in the spring of her youth, she had indeed inherited all her parents' flaws and none of their strengths.

Just then she was listening to her grandfather's lecture, but her heart was calm.

"I'm not twenty yet, right? I know what to do after my birthday." Barcetine replied calmly.

"We're worried you don't understand." Her grandfather retorted. "You need to know what's important. In this world, power is the strongest thing, the sharpest weapon. The second is money, everything else that you've been chasing until now is meaningless."

"It's not meaningless." Barcetina argued, "Once you reach the top of any field, you are powerful and dazzling."

"So what? Our connections can bring you world-class movie stars, world-class fighting trainers, the best antiques. They are the cream of their fields, but they can only earn a few dozen millions, a hundred million at most, and they're still controlled by masterminds like us, they fade, cool down, and are forced out of their field, it's far too easy to shut them up." The old man replied carelessly.

"The people won't be fooled that easily." Barcetina frowned.

"You're wrong." The old man shook his head, "The people can't see the truth of the moment, that's why they're the easiest to fool. This is the digital age, anything real can become fake, and anything fake can become real."

"Forget it, I don't want to argue with you, I understand what you mean. I'll be prepared." Barcetina stood up, patted down her jeans, turned around, and left the room.

Coming out from her grandfather's place, she drove her car down a shaded little path slowly, for some reason, there was deep resentment in Barcetina's heart.

Faced with her large family, her own power seemed so small, and so weak. The social circles that she had worked so hard to build were no more than a joke in her family's eyes, they could easily destroy all the connections she had, and isolate her completely.

But she did not succumb, she loved collecting and fighting, and she would use a ton of money and energy on those two every year.

Taking out her phone, she called her good friend.

'Hey, is that Cam? How are things going with the newest exhibition?'

'What? Something happened at home, so you probably can't make it?'

'Fine, fine, then how about we meet in the afternoon, and walk around a bit? Just treat it as a walk to de-stress, you have something urgent? Okay…'

Hanging up, Barcetina called another number.

'Kris, what are you doing? What! Are you moving house? When? I'll pick you up right now!'

'No need? Alright, alright…'

Another friend had suddenly become cold.

Barcetina could already feel a huge net woven by her family slowly close in on her, and she was powerless to resist.

Clenching her teeth, she called yet another number, but this one did not even go through, nobody picked up.

Friends, fellow enthusiasts, members of a club, the Collector Association's number, either they did not pick up, or they had all sorts of bad news. Most of the members of the Collector Association she started even quit all at once, and the Association was on the brink of collapse

Bam!

"Bullshit!"

Barcetina smashed her fist into the steering wheel, and the car stopped abruptly, followed by the sound of emergency brakes behind her.

Her circle was so frail, none of them could withstand the pressure from her family, that was the pressure coming from all forms of society, heavy and suffocating.

Without stopping, she tried all the different phone numbers, but the calls were either met with despairing silence, or wayward rejections.

Slowly, she extended her reach to anyone she had ever met or called. She called all the numbers, one by one, but the results were still exasperating and hopeless, the web of connections that she thought was wide and complicated only looked vast, but it was still controlled by her family's power, without any exceptions.

Her emotions grew more and more despairing.

In the end, with her last ray of hope, she called a number.

It was the number of a stranger she had met in a friendly fighting competition in America. She was trying to find a place where a family could not reach.

Chapter 656: Suppress 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The other party was just a fighting enthusiast who tried to buy an antique from her, they had talked a bit at a private exhibition of hers, and upon discovering that they had quite a lot to talk about, they exchanged telephone numbers, so they were acquaintances at best.

'Hello? Who is this?' There was a deep male voice from the other end of the call.

'Is this Mr Kaedun? Do you still remember me? I'm Barcetina.'

'Barcetina? Oh… it's Miss Barcetina! How are you? Have you decided to sell that Mask? The price is negotiable.' The other person's tone grew passionate. Barcetina perked up, there was finally someone who did not reject her. After a series of neglected calls and direct rejections, her emotions had gotten more and more frustrated.

Her heart calmed down temporarily now, as though she had seen a loophole in her family's web, before this even the people who had already agreed to exchange or sell antiques with her had all rejected her, even those who wanted her antiques all changed their tacks, they had either been pressured, or they were given something even better. She had finally found someone normal now.

'About the Mask, you're… still willing… to buy it?' Barcetina asked carefully.

'Of course!' Kaedun replied matter-of-factly, 'Why don't we meet up somewhere, you decide where! I'll fly there as soon as possible.'

'Sure! Make it the Stone Gate Street in New York! There's a pretty good restaurant there. When you're there, give me a call, and I'll tell you exactly where to go.' Barcetina seemed to find a ray of hope, and her mood also brightened quickly.

"No problem!"

*****************

Several hours later.

Carlilo Cafe, Stonegate Street, New York

The impatient duo had both increased their speed in unison, and as a result, both of them arrived at the location more than an hour before their agreed time.

Sitting at the tables furthest inside the cafe, Baldy Kaedun and Barcetina stared at each other wordlessly, and for a while, they did not know what to say.

They sat at the right side of the cafe, and they could hear the sounds of other customers chatting around them, as well as the sounds of the waiters clearing tables and greeting others.

The cafe had pretty decent ambiance, illuminated with a soft, pale yellow light that created a warm and gentle mood.

"Looks like we were both early." Barcetina spoke, putting her hands on the table, as she noticed that he had also tried to speak before pulling back. "I'll confirm with you again, you really are willing to make a deal with me?"

Baldy nodded.

"Of course, is there any problem?" He looked slightly confused.

"Alright, then, let's discuss the details." For some reason, Barcetina felt as though her body was suddenly a lot lighter, like an insect trapped in a spider web that finally pulled away slightly from its death trap, and could finally catch its breath.

The two of them began to discuss the details about the Black Copper Mask's market price, perhaps out of gratitude for this tiny lightness in her heart, Barcetina took the initiative to reduce the price by one third, confusing Baldy somewhat.

After some questioning, Barcetina finally told him about her situation.

"I want freedom! I want to do the stuff I like! But I can't accomplish even something as simple as that." She lowered her head, solemn but with a slight hint of pain. "I'm now an upper-level professional wrestler, I don't want to give that up just like that."

After understanding Barcetina's situation, Baldy seemed to think of another friend of his, and there was a new hint of understanding in his eyes.

"I really sympathize with your situation, Miss." He thought about it, "If you just want some space that is not controlled by your family, if possible, perhaps I could introduce you a combat teacher, I guarantee this person won't be controlled by your family."

Barcetina thought that his tone seemed to be slightly mysterious.

"What teacher? Are you sure you know how vast my family background is?"

For a moment there, she felt as though Baldy Kaedun's identity had also gotten somewhat mysterious.

"You'll like him." Baldy laughed, "But the teacher I'm introducing to you may be very strict, unless you really like fighting, and are willing to put in a lot of effort, it might be best if you don't agree."

"No problem! What condition do you have in exchange?" Barcetina asked quietly.

"There is no condition, this person is also my teacher, he respects anyone who is dedicated to martial arts and strives to grow stronger, so he would be willing to teach them his techniques. But he has to be selective too, so if you don't pass, he won't teach you." Baldy was naturally talking about Garen, it was not just him, Jay, his wife Hera, and all of the other Nighthawk higher-ups were all looking for potential trainees for Garen, these trainees needed to love and aspire towards martial arts, and they also needed some background behind them, so that they were worth using and raising.

The poor became scholars and the rich became fighters, it was difficult to achieve any real accomplishments without money and resources.

Garen got the others to collect such trainees so that he could teach them all sorts of secret techniques as a basic means to control the way his power grew. By using the connections of these disciples of his, he could rapidly search for the Black Copper Masks all over the world.

Barcetina was just one of the many candidates.

The two of them settled on a time in the cafe, then Baldy left the place and got into the car his driver drove up to him. Only then did he take his phone out from his pocket and glance at the message on it, it was from Barcetina's family, and it seemed to hint at a threat.

"They dare to threaten me? They really think we're honest and legal salesmen." He laughed coldly.

"Wanna teach them a lesson?" The driver sniggered.

"Just give them a slight warning. After all, this ain't our turf." Baldy replied casually. "Whoever sent the message, just destroy one of their arms, don't go overboard."

"Got it!"

They had always been lawless bastards, as the bosses of the African mercenary scene, and with the terrifying reputation of the Nighthawk King behind them, most violent groups would also be wary of them, now that they were on someone else's territory, they were polite enough not to provoke the hosts, but now someone dared to challenge them.

These mercenaries were all warmongers who carried their heads on their belts, they were extremely familiar with killing others, and some of them even moonlighted as assassins in their spare time, so now that someone had come barking at them of their own accord, these criminals that even the international police had several files on were naturally even more revved up and ready.

Coincidentally, now that the governments were busy with the Blood Breeds' internal conflict, trying hard to suppress all those murder cases, this was the best time to make their move.

********************

Casually flipping through the photographs and information on the table, Garen looked through the ten potential candidates that his subordinates had picked out for him.

There were boys and girls, the ages ranging from their teens to twenty.

Putting their appearances aside, they all came from powerful backgrounds, and they were all very interested in fighting and combat, so they were perfect targets for him to control.

Under the lamplight, Garen picked out a few from the photos and put them aside, these were the ones he could do with or without, as for the rest, he could let Xander teach them alone, then he would just go and remove the side effects himself.

To these young people who were passionate about fighting, they craved adrenaline, liked to go on adventures and discover new things.

Faced with a secret technique that could make them terrifyingly stronger within a few short months, he believed that none of them would able to resist such a temptation.

They needed the primers so that they could truly walk the path of the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist, and so that they could see the effects of their strength. The intense pleasure during training that surpassed even drugs would surely keep a vice grip on the young people's hearts.

'Your plan is not bad, and it will help expand your influence, but what is the point of such influence? It would take a bit too long, and Nadia could show up at any time. The scent of that coin is the location marker, and the will of the Nine-Headed Dragon's Blood in your body is also a signboard to lead her to you. She will be here very soon. Then I'll see how you deal with it.'

Black Sethe was raining on his parade beside him. He did not know that Garen could use the potential power in the Mask to strengthen himself.

Garen ignored him, this person got more excited the more attention he got.

He separated the photos into two stacks and asked the Nighthawk member waiting outside to come in, take the two stacks of photos and info out, and pass them to the specified people.

Only then did Garen stand up, leave the room, and enter a vast sealed room with lead-coated walls.

This room was one that he had specially made, the walls and floor were covered with a layer of silver lead, and there was a small square white platform in the middle of the room, with that yellow-copper Dragon Head Coin set on top like a shrine.

Closing the door with a bam, Garen walked towards the platform the coin was on.

Boom!

All of a sudden, Garen felt dizzy, and it was as though his vision went bleary, making him stop three meters away from the platform.

He did not know when it started, but there was a thin white mist coming from the platform, it was like water vapor, spiraling above the coin, slowly forming a terrifying dragon head image.

Roar!!

The dragon head roared at Garen, it evidently made no soundwaves, but Garen could still hear that deafening dragon's roar.

'That's the location signal the coin is constantly emitting, you can try to suppress it.' Black Sethe suggested, 'That way you can effectively lengthen the time Nadia needs to get here.'

Garen nodded, he knew that he had been pulled into a dream by the coin's scent, this coin was reacting more and more obviously recently, and the power it leaked out was also getting stronger, Nadia's scent kept leaking from the coin, affecting all the surroundings and creatures around it.

After a maid was pulled into the world of dreams by that coin and nearly starved to death there, Garen got someone to create a quarantine room like this, specifically to cordon off the coin's gradually growing forces and impact.

"You are merely a dead thing."

Garen's eye narrowed, and he took one step forward.

Boom!!!

A large cloud of dark blue frost power burst out from behind him, the frost power rapidly converging and solidifying, forming an image of a terrifying Nine-Headed Dragon.

Roar!!!

The nine dragon heads roared ferociously at the white dragon head.

For a moment, the whole room was filled with the blue and white mist.

'You can't stop me…' Nadia's voice came from the white dragon head, filled with killing intent.

Garen ignored her completely, sitting down cross-legged, closing his eyes slightly, the dark blue mist behind him beginning to surround the white mist emitted by the coin.

Chapter 657: Scramble 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Elvin, England, Europe.

There was a white mansion in the outskirts, the mansion’s roof had a serrated pattern, the doors and windows were all arch-shaped, and occasionally one could see round pillars supporting the building.

A black person in a white shirt and black slacks was going in and out of the house.

There were green grassy yards all around the mansion, each patch of grass trimmed unnaturally tidily.

The sky was cloudy and dark, the sun covered by clouds, making the atmosphere somewhat oppressive.

On the grass, an old black man with a red tie was casually surfing the internet on his phone, he sat in a chair under an umbrella to block off the sun, but his gaze kept wandering to a bunch of pretty women playing nearby in front of him.

As a black man, and as the boss of England's largest antique and relics field, he had started the Bailey Group. Having accomplished such a result in the world of the white people, Kabb already had more than enough to be proud of, so all that should be left was to sit back and enjoy a carefree life.

But Kabb was not so relaxed at all, now that he was fifty-two, he was currently facing the second largest problem in life, aging.

He was barely past middle-aged, but he was feeling far less energetic than he used to be, and his spirit was also constantly weakening, this feeling of constantly shriveling away made him panic.

Luckily, he had discovered an earth-shaking secret from a rival group as it collapsed, this secret might be an important turning point for his life from now on, he could not afford to let it slip by.

"Boss, it seems like someone's interfering with the mask that we're after." A subordinate walked up to him and spoke quietly in his ear.

"Someone's interfering?" Kabb frowned, "Who?"

"The Neo Black Uniforms, they have the Nighthawks behind them, it's a bit troublesome." His trusted aide Medis had an extremely powerful information web, and would not be wrong about this kind of thing.

"They also know about the mask?" Kabb asked quietly, still pretending his eyes were on the ladies.

"Yes, unfortunately." Medis nodded.

"That’s troublesome, I am bent on attaining all twelve masks, the Nighthawks are number one in Africa, get Viper to deal with them. Contact the Primary Colors for me, the White Phoenix would surely be willing to greet this new force that’s undermining their authority."

Kabb instantly thought of ways to deal with this, not only was he the boss of England’s largest antique corporation, he was also the unifier of half of England’s strongest violent groups, every move he made was enough to influence the entire English underworld.

"Yes." Medis backed down, head lowered.

Kabb, however, began to quickly recall all the information he had about the Nighthawks, they did not have many members, but they were the most mysterious, and they had that powerful mastermind known as the Nighthawk King behind them. This was enough to make him wary, that person was powerful enough to brazenly attack the Primary Colors, he was dangerous and extremely invasive.

*****************

On a passenger plane from Elvin towards Berlin, Germany

The passengers were all groggy and sleepy, some were reading their newspapers quietly, some had put on sleeping masks, a few young people were gathered and playing cards, the stewardesses were threading through the aisles, asking questions and checking on the passengers.

In the four seats on the left at the back of the plane, there were four young people sitting in a row and playing some sort of table game, one of them yawned slightly.

"How much longer before we reach?" This person put down the game pieces in his hand, his expression absolutely bored.

"Soon, soon, I can feel the plane descending." A girl said flippantly.

"You say that every time."

"Don’t you feel more hopeful when I say that?" The girl replied nonchalantly.

"Aihhh…"

Another person put down their pieces, "Just go ahead and sleep, you guys, there should still be more than twenty minutes."

He turned around to look at a man by the window, this man wore white leather pants, and a T-shirt with black and red stripes, his skin was fair, and there was a series of golden earrings on his ears.

"King, what should we do when we get there?"

"Just follow the old rules, this mission is slightly more difficult, you guys be careful. The opponent is Hera of the Nighthawks." The man called King replied casually.

"The Nighthawks are very active in Africa, there are more wars and conflicts there, so it can’t be easy to build a reputation over there. But on that note, these complicated city areas belong to us, Viper, if they want to beat us here… hehe."

The four of them were the true form of the whole Viper, as one of the top ten mercenary groups in Europe, nobody dared to underestimate their hidden ambushes and killing intent.

"Hera has five powerful generals under her, and she herself is one of the Nighthawk King’s three most trusted aides, so we must not underestimate her ability, no matter what, everyone has to be more serious this time, after finishing this job, all of us can go back and play however we want."

King told them softly.

"No problem.""Of course!""Let’s f*ck ‘em sideways!"

The three of them started yelling.

"Every member of the Nighthawks has powerful ambushing power, and they are all very alert as well, try to be quick, you can’t give them any time to resist. Their combat power is all very strong, do not try to engage in close combat with them."

"Understood!"

This time, Viper had not only accepted the mission from the Bailey Group, there was also the Primary Colors’ bounty, in this operation against the Nighthawks, they were joined by a few more of the top ten mercenary groups in Europe, each of them was in charge of one of the Nighthawks’ independent members.

The Black Uniforms’ Jay, the Vice Commander Baldy Kaedun, and his wife Hera, each of them had an elite mercenary troop targeting them, to make sure this operation was completely foolproof.

And then there was the strongest mercenary group, Blackfire, out of the hunt everywhere for the Nighthawk King’s whereabouts.

This time the Primary Colors were really determined, they had tossed out two billion pounds at once, just to make sure the Nighthawks were thoroughly exterminated.

An invisible web was surrounding the entirety of the Nighthawks. In this web, there were several people who had crossed swords with Levi before, and there were some who fought Kaedun himself as well, they were all monstrous elites. They were so professional, that some of them had a thousand faces and you could not tell which one was real at all, some were top-level bomb experts, with bombs everywhere. Others were computer hacking prodigies, wherever there was a surveillance camera, as long as it was connected to the internet, those could be their eyes.

There were all sorts of elites, and their supremely powerful combinations had taken on many high-difficulty missions before, most of them even had experience with the supernatural.

And even so, the Primary Colors still secretly sent out powerful people, allegedly strong mercenaries who had been modified through experiments, specifically to deal with the Nighthawk King if he shows up.

This operation was like a web covering heaven and earth, giving their target no way to escape.

Although King sounded serious, the truth was he already knew in his heart, that if nothing out of the extraordinary happened, the Nighthawks were finished this time.

********************

"What!? Our stuff has been stolen?" Jay’s eyes immediately went cold, staring at his subordinate in front of him. "Who did it?"

"It’s Ohio Silk from Europe, they left their signature mark." His subordinate reported quietly.

Chack!

The glass in Jay’s hand shattered, and the transparent wine flowed out of his hand.

"Ohio Silk… The number two assassins’ group in Europe, huh? What’s the meaning of this? Do they want to declare war on us?" His face darkened.

His subordinate did not even dare to breathe loudly in front of him, just lowering his head and freezing still.

"Boss, let’s just fight it out, I’ve always wanted to see what these European scrubs could do. They were just so f*cking cocky at the banquet last time!" A young red-haired man leaned on a wall inside the room, and spoke casually.

"I’ll go with Tran, and take fifteen of our elites, that should be enough to solve our problem." Another woman in the room said quietly, they were Jay’s left and right hands respectively, they were always hanging around Jay even when they were in the Nighthawks, and now that they had swallowed up and were controlling the Black Uniforms, having learned the fistfighting skills from Jay, their strength increased tremendously. After undergoing such cruel training, their bodies’ stamina had achieved a terrifying and extreme level, such that they were the elite fighters just behind Jay among the Black Uniforms.

"There’s no rush… Since they dare to make a move directly, they must surely have considered our response in it as well." Jay was never an impulsive person, he mused over it, then picked up the phone to call the other members of the Nighthawks.

After a dozen or so minutes, he put the telephone receiver down, his expression dark.

"As expected, this is an operation targeting the entire Nighthawks, things have gone wrong on Baldy’s and Hera’s side as well, I suspect that our opponent will make a move immediately. You guys go and mobilize your men immediately, get them on their guard! It’s highly likely they will strike tonight!"

Hearing those words, his subordinates grew solemn as well, looks like this situation was not good.

"Tell the lower ranks, if we get past this, everyone will get at least a hundred thousand USD as a reward, depending on their contributions," Jay promised generously.

His two subordinates started chuckling loudly.

Bang!!!

Suddenly there was a gunshot, and the three of them got down to the ground instantly.

The only person who could not react in time was the subordinate who had come to report the problem, his temple was pierced through, blood spraying, and he toppled backward.

At the same time, deep bullet holes appeared on the tables, the sofas, the chairs, all the holes appearing at once.

It was just one gunshot sound, sounding like the explosion of firecrackers, but the result that appeared was at least caused by several dozen guns shooting at once, and they were all high-powered guns as well.

Jay rolled onto the ground like a snake, and darted underneath the metallic table for cover.

He could hear the tapping and consecutive explosions above his head, who knew how many bullets were raining down onto the table.

This was the Black Uniforms’ headquarters, and the enemy actually had the ability to assault them all the way here… add that to the strength of this firepower, and he could not help a chill rising in his heart.

****************

In the pitch black sealed room, Garen sat cross-legged on the floor, his eyes tightly closed, and the platform with the coin right in front of him.

Ever since that day, he had to come in here every so often to suppress Nadia’s scent tracking.

The original scent of the coin got more and more terrifying, and now anyone in a five-meter radius would get pulled into a dream, Nadia’s energy would suppress their spirits until they were confused and barely conscious. But with Garen’s constant suppression, this increase in its power was finally controlled, Garen kept using up the energy on the coin, greatly delaying Nadia’s identification of this area.

Strangely, by using the Nine-Headed Dragon’s will to fight her in this dream state, Garen could clearly feel his secret technique training progressing even faster than before. This resistance was like a sharpening stone, making his Living Secret Technique stronger and stronger, and he soon reached the peak of the first level.

Chapter 658: Scramble 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After sitting cross-legged in the darkness for goodness knows how long, Garen slowly got up, arranged the white night robes he was wearing and walked out of the room, faintly hearing the dissatisfied roar of the Nine-Headed Dragon behind him.

There were several subordinates guarding the door, but they seemed not to hear anything at all, they wore the same uniform, all in white casual clothes, and one of them offered up a black box to Garen respectfully.

"Boss, this was just sent here. It was sent by Vice Commander Kaedun."

Garen nodded, and accepted the box.

There were pale golden patterns embedded in the surface of the black box, like so many disorganized lines, but upon closer inspection, there was some rhythm to them.

Opening the lock with a smack, Garen saw a slightly black copper mask in between the black silks, the mask was expressionless, its forehead covered with countless eyes, and he could vaguely see the detailed skin-like linings all over the surface, intricate and realistic.

"The second one…" Garen reached out his hand to caress the mask lightly. Wisps of cool potential energy instantly surged into his palm.

He just felt it roughly, but he could already tell that this mask would have a total of more than forty or fifty potential points, and what made him happiest was that this mask itself had the ability to constantly produce potential power, it seemed to be able to grow more as well as store a certain amount of potential value.

If even a forgery can achieve such an effect, who knew what it would be like if he collected all twelve forgeries.

Garen touched the wrinkles on the mask carefully, feeling the wisps of cooling energy surge into his hand, according to his initial estimates, a Mask would produce about 0.1 potential points worth of energy every day. That way, if he had twelve Masks, he would automatically receive one potential point every day, this was undoubtedly a huge sum in this world that was woefully low on potential points. And over time it would become a very substantial amount.

"Did Kaedun say anything else?" Garen asked.

"During the afternoon the day before yesterday, Lord Jay and Lady Hera were ambushed, Commander Kaedun had gone out personally to send the Mask, so he managed to avoid the ambush and countered the enemy instead, capturing two of their members. After some interrogation, they said that the strongest group in England, the Bailey Group, had goaded the Primary Colors into moving." His subordinate reported quickly.

"The Bailey Group?" Garen repeated this noun again. "How’s the situation? Right now."

"Not very good, Lady Hera was grievously hurt, now Commander Kaedun has rushed over to deal with matters, and Lord Jay sustained heavy losses, although he is fine, he had lost at least half of his men in the ambush." This subordinate had recently become Garen’s information specialist, not just him, but there was another small group that was founded specifically to be something like a meeting of strategists, everyone in the group had their own roles, but once there was an emergency, they would band together to solve the combat club’s and Nighthawks’ problems.

They usually planned all sorts of strategies for Kaedun, Jay, and the other leaders.

The vast amounts of information would also be transmitted here endlessly, after they reach a conclusion, the results would be sent quickly back to the various leaders. This was basically a strategy room.

Of course, these people were all elites that Garen, Kaedun and the others invited from all over, some of them were even university lecturers, or even lecturers from Garen’s own university, but after practicing the Waterbird Fist and feeling that drug-like pleasure, they could no longer leave the combat club. These people were mostly all like that, although they were intelligent, when faced with the temptation of the Waterbird Fist, they were still willing to stay in the combat club and strategize for Garen.

"The Bailey Group, the Primary Colors…" Garen was starting to feel a little ticked off, to be honest, these three subordinates made things a lot more convenient for him, in the incident with the Stone Clock of Fortune, they had given him quite a haul. He had only gotten one Stone Clock himself, but Jay even snatched several more for him, saving him a lot of energy.

And this time, Kaedun found him the second mask as well. If he had to look for it himself, it would take a lot more time and energy, after all he did not randomly attend private exhibitions.

If he wanted to continue training without worries like this, while constantly obtaining more potential points at the same time, it seemed that he would need to move a little bit this time.

Before this, due to the trouble caused by the Void Creatures, and his need to deal with the Nine-Headed Dragon King Nadia, he did not intend to meddle with reality too much, he did not want to waste his time and energy on reality, but it seemed that he had no choice.

"Gather up the Nighthawks, everyone gather at Kaedun’s place, but be careful on the way." He thought for a bit and directly gave his orders.

His subordinate beside him recorded what he said, word for word.

"Also, list down all the factions that are attacking us this time."

Looks like he needed to upgrade Baldy and the others soon, otherwise it would really be troublesome if he had to do everything himself.

It just so happened that he had recently perfected the Shooting Shadow Secret Skill, turning it into the Shooting Shadow Secret Technique, it had a whole array of secretive yet overwhelmingly powerful killing moves, and it also inherited that intense training pleasure from the Waterbird Fist, while also having the soul primer added to it, so the whole Shooting Shadow Secret Skill had become a powerful demonic secret technique on the same level as the Waterbird Fist.

Baldy and the others had already trained the Shooting Shadow Secret Skill to an extremely high level, the three leaders had all reached the highest level, the Shooting Shadow sixth level, so if they started training the complete version, they would progress abnormally quickly.

Garen had already unified the two secret techniques he created, forming a Book of Demonic Secret Techniques, otherwise known as the Demonic Book for short.

The Two-Faced Waterbird Fist and the Shooting Shadow Secret Technique, these two legacies would become the martial arts at the core supporting the Demonic Book.

Thinking back on it now, Baldy and the others were somewhat too weak, after they worked so hard for him over the past few years, they got less tutelage than Hochman, Dahm and the others, so this was rather unfair to them.

Garen decided that in order to counter the way the Shooting Shadow Secret Technique could only assassinate, he would create another proper secret technique, to make up for what they lacked in head-on battles. Just like this time, once they were ambushed and put on the spot, the three main leaders of the Nighthawks could not unleash their full potential, the opponent just pushed them like that, revealing no weaknesses.

The opposite of Shooting Shadow was Light Speed, both had to do with speed, and with that Garen already had some ideas.

‘You’re going to deal with trivial matters? They’re just subordinates, they won’t grow without experiencing some setbacks. Even if they die, that just means they’re not strong enough, they have a better foundation and starting point than these people and still can’t beat them, that’s not your fault.’ Black Sethe spoke.

"You don’t have many subordinates in Ancient Endor, do you?" Garen retorted.

‘Are you trying to say that I could never gain widespread influence with this attitude and style?’ Black Sethe immediately understood what he was thinking.

"Influence is only there to make things more convenient for me, I just need to help a bit and I’ll have my subordinates do the rest, compared to a life swamped with trivial matters, which would be better and more convenient for training? That would depend on what each individual thinks."

‘Don’t tell me you really are collecting antique masks just for that insignificant bit of energy on it?’ Black Sethe was no fool, of course he could tell something was wrong with Garen’s intentions.

Garen did not reply.

"Get me flight tickets, I’ll head to Berlin myself tomorrow."

"Yes."

Garen picked up the Mask, turned around and walked into another quiet room, he needed the time to completely absorb the Mask’s potential value, so that he could use it to increase his secret technique level.

***************

Elvin, England

Bailey Estate

It was a bright and sunny day, with no clouds in sight.

Kabb sat in his study, dressed in his night robes, wearing his reading glasses to read the information he had carefully.

After he finished reading it, he put down the info and mused for a while.

"How’s the situation with Viper?"

Medis, who was sitting opposite him, replied quickly.

"The opponent is very stubborn, Viper lost several people before they could grievously injure Hera, but unfortunately they still could not catch nor kill her."

"What about White Phoenix’s side?"

"Baldy Kaedun was lucky, he was out on an errand and not in the base, he just left a man to take his place and watch the base. All they killed was a replacement, and instead Baldy counterattacked, seriously hurting and capturing two men, they probably know by now that our Bailey Group is involved. Boss, you best be prepared." Medis reminded him.

Kabb nodded.

"The Nighthawks are still considerably obstinate, as expected of Africa’s number one mercenary army, just the three masterminds are individually as powerful as one of Europe’s top ten mercenary groups. With such power, if they were gathered together, perhaps even our number one Titan would not end up much."

"Indeed." Medis agreed.

"The Nighthawk King’s reaction would probably be to gather everyone, right? The location would either be where Baldy is, or Berlin, where Hera is. We don’t need to guess, Baldy is the vice, he actually controls the whole group’s power, and Hera is his woman, judging by his character, he would not stay silent once his woman’s been attacked, so he would surely make for Berlin."

He picked up another file and read that as well.

"There might very well be a reason why the Nighthawk King does not show his face publicly, in the Stone Clock of Fortune incident, he also only officially showed up after his subordinates were crippled, evidently he has something limiting him, so it’s most likely that he remains hidden for now, letting Baldy and the others gather and come up with a plan."

"This is just a possibility, what if he does show up?" Medis asked.

"That’s fine too." Kabb smiled, "Berlin is your territory, no matter how strong he is, he’s just one person, and besides the elite fighters of the Primary Colors are still waiting for him, if necessary, you can help him out a little, you must make it secretive and hidden, to show that we were forced, and the Primary Colors’ White Phoenix are their true enemies. We cannot interfere too much, just act as though we’re observers, as long as we don’t participate of our own accord, no matter who wins or loses later, at the most we’ll just spend some money to call it quits. Try your best to let the Primary Colors face the Nighthawks, remember, we were forced to join, it actually has nothing to do with us. It was actually the White Phoenix who asked for our cooperation."

Kabb’s gaze turned unreadable.

"That way, we can earn and profit, and the risks wouldn’t force the other side to retaliate in desperation, their greatest enemy is the Primary Colors Group after all…"

"Boss, you’re hedging risks here…" Medis said with a laugh.

"It’s a bit like that." Kabb was surprised as well, but then he started to laugh as well.

Chapter 659: Confrontation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

After the two of them laughed for some time, Kabb picked up the coffee on the table and sipped from it.

"However, on that note, do you have clues about the Nighthawk King’s identity?"

Medis nodded.

"After you mentioned this point, I began collecting information about him from all channels. After analyzing the flight times and using our intel to thin down the possibilities, we have obtained a list of people in that period of time who might be the Nighthawk King. The information we got is slightly strange."

"Oh? How is it strange?"

"Judging from the flight intel, the Nighthawk King probably booked his ticket through someone else, but in the incident with the Stone Clock of Fortune, he did not hide his appearance, so after making some comparisons, we discovered the true identity of the Nighthawk King."

"Is it very surprising?" Kabb looked at his usually calm and cunning old subordinate and friend, somewhat surprised that this man would be shocked by the Nighthawk King’s true identity.

"It is rather surprising." Medis nodded, "Garen Thomas, twenty years old, a second-year student at Gullivier University, a very mysterious person, hard to trace, he’s the president of the combat-oriented combat club in school. His father is a university lecturer, his mother a psychiatrist, his family is a thoroughbred academic family, with nothing at all to do with violent groups."

"All the more reason for us to be wary!" Kabb said abruptly, "I’ve met someone like this before, one of the heads of an Italian mafia clan is also a teenage child, he looks cute and innocent, but he’s a young prodigy, ruthless in his methods, and anyone who dares to look down on them will pay a hefty price."

"Understood." Medis nodded,"Then what do we need to do?"

Kabb touched his chin.

"This Nighthawk King Garen, he’s probably the key to truly controlling the Nighthawks, have you heard the rumors about the Nighthawks?"

"Yes, do you mean the rumor that the Nighthawk King alone can control everyone in the Nighthawks using certain methods?"

Medis had evidently heard about this before. He mused quietly for a while, organizing his thoughts before he continued.

"The Nighthawks’ growth is clearly evident, it might look a lot hazier to other powers, but to large groups such as ourselves and the Primary Colors, it’s impossible to hide their growth patterns. It could be said that they could only break free from the White Phoenix and form the Nighthawks after Baldy Kaedun paid a visit to Grano, where Garen was, all those years ago. It is also highly likely that Garen took him under his wing since back then."

"Tell me, for a normal kid to control an international mercenary for so many years without the latter having any intention to rebel. What methods could he be using?" Kabb asked quietly.

"He could make an ordinary mercenary into a top-level elite in the mercenary world within a short time, besides." Medis continued, "The combat club that Garen joined also increased in strength exponentially after he joined, the previous pillars of the club made Garen their teacher, and are learning martial arts from him."

Kabb’s fingers and joints rapped the table rhythmically.

"In that case, it seems that this Garen has a method to quickly make others stronger, be it the Nighthawks, the combat club, or even himself. For such a young man in his teens to control an international mercenary group, he must surely have an absolutely powerful way to control them. Tell me, if we can find this manipulation method, as well as this strengthening method, wouldn’t we be able to create a powerful team that belongs solely to us in a very short period of time?"

Medis nodded solemnly.

"It is very likely."

"I will leave this up to you, Garen must have a secret! And it is surely something extraordinary as well, I have a feeling, we might be able to get something better than we imagined from him." Kabb said with a straight face.

"I’ll go investigate right now." Medis understood how important this was as well, and stood up, "I will try to communicate with him, maybe I can get more direct information."

"Go."

*******************

In the vast black cathedral

He was surrounded by blurry walls, and could only faintly see the patterns shaking and flickering.

Garen stood in the middle of the cathedral, there were many giant golden statues on either side of him, the statues’ hands held their large swords, their heads and gazes lowered, as though they were protecting something.

At the very deepest end of the cathedral, there was a huge green silk web on the wall. This web was actually growing and growing, like vines, slowly growing thicker and denser.

And in the middle of the web, there was a pitch-black human figure.

"Here again." Garen looked around him, confused.

This dream seemed so very realistic, so much so that he could barely tell if he was in a dream or not. And every time he entered this dream, even his connection with Black Sethe would be severed.

That black figure kept struggling in the silk web, roaring soundlessly, but it was useless, every time he struggled, he would still be held there by the silk webs, held firmly motionless.

Garen trod on the smooth black marble floor, walking towards the deepest end of the cathedral, and soon he was standing underneath that large silk web.

He looked up at the black figure, and reached out his hand to touch the silk web holding the man captive, but as with last time, there was something like glass between the web and his hand.

His hand could not touch the web directly.

"This is my second time having the same dream." Garen frowned, he looked all around him, but did not find anything else out of the ordinary. The black figure that was stuck there did not seem to see him at all, and kept struggling futilely, not even looking at him.

Garen turned around and looked towards the large cathedral doors, those were tall and pitch-black metallic doors, a full dozen meters or so tall, they looked heavy and sturdy, embroidered with many strange patterns.

"This is the last temple." Suddenly, there was a deep male voice from behind him.

Garen turned around abruptly and saw a beautiful woman in a white dress walking towards him slowly, the woman’s long hair danced, and she held a huge silver sword in her hand. The large, long sword formed a sharp contrast with her body, only over a meter tall, and made it hard to imagine that her petite body could drag that sword, more than three meters long, so easily while she moved.

"Nadia." Garen recognized her, Nine-Headed Dragon King Nadia.

"Speaking of which, even when we first met, we never talked properly face to face like this. You’re suppressing my tracking ability, so I had to figure out this method to get around this problem." Nadia obviously looked like a girl, but spoke with a man’s voice, giving off an extremely eerie impression.

"What do you want to say?" Garen said calmly.

"That old man hiding in your body, he’s the memory remnants of an ancient fighter, right?" Nadia said softly, "That sort of memory is the most untrustworthy, I was nearly trapped by this thing back then." Nadia seemed extremely bored, walking up to Garen’s side, and looking up at the black figure in the web.

"You must understand, even if you’re suppressing the time I descend upon you, that day will still come. Rather than waiting fruitlessly for death, how about you join me under my command? Abandon your physical form, such a thing is no more than a restriction to us, we exist merely in wills, and are that much freer than you imagine."

Nadia spoke alluringly in the Ancient Endor language.

"We are practically immortal, as long as our souls do not reach their limit, we will not die. In comparison, the limits of the physical body are far too insignificant. Even the best metals will rot. What’s more a shell of flesh?"

"What benefits will I get from becoming one of you?" Garen retorted.

"Oh, there are too many, many of the invisible creatures are everlasting, they have accumulated countless knowledge and experience, once you have cast away your body, it will be easier to communicate with and learn from them. Plus, by existing as merely a will, you can exchange countless knowledge in an instant, you can travel freely through dimensions, just like how I have pulled you in here now, when in fact we are miles and miles apart." Nadia replied casually, "Stronger, more perfect. Isn’t that what you’re after?"

"I have a soul with space-time attributes, all of that is meaningless to me. I have plenty of time to slowly accumulate sufficient knowledge." Garen was unfazed.

For some reason, neither of them had any intention of fighting here. They just stood there, talking to each other obediently and quietly.

Nadia laughed. "Your will is very pure, but you can’t do it just because you think you can." He(1) looked Garen up and down, and her smile deepened. "You seem to have a secret, or rather an advantage, this advantage makes you fearless, you do not sense danger in any situation at all. And you also have extreme confidence in yourself, this confidence is already bordering on ignorance."

"Ignorance?" Garen arched his eyebrows.

"That’s right, or rather you are blind to the world." Nadia’s expression was condescending, "I really want to know, what on earth could this secret of yours be?"

Garen’s heart was calm, his largest advantage was his terrifyingly powerful natural Ability, the power to turn anything in reality into attributes and skills.

Using potential points, he could constantly make himself stronger, power up his attributes, and the ability to turn things into skills saved him a lot of time, as for everything else, it was all built on these two matters at the core.

Be it his secret techniques, or the secret methods and secret skills, the core to everything was actually this Ability of his, it was his Ability that worked with his space-time body to give him constant power.

Nadia’s gaze swept over him, giving him a faint sense of a threat.

"Everyone has a secret, I am also extremely intrigued by the secret that allows you to grow exponentially stronger every time you die."

Garen’s tone did not change at all.

"Did you know?" Nadia said suddenly. "This is an ancient temple, it’s an illusory area projected by the Mother Stream in the world of dreams."

"So what?" Garen did not know what she meant by saying that.

"In here, Void Creatures can avoid being suppressed and hurt by the Mother Stream, because it’s just a projection, and also, those with space-time bodies can hunt each other’s cores…" She looked at Garen mysteriously, "As long as you get the other person’s core, you can obtain all of their memories."

"I really want to know, what is it that allows you to stay so calm, allows you to look disconcerted no matter what happens…"

Before she even finished speaking, all of a sudden, Nadia’s body turned into a white shadow, dashing at Garen.

Her large sword danced and spun, creating an extremely piercing wail, like a huge silver wheel three or four meters in diameter, sweeping towards Garen’s neck like lightning.

"Eight Directional Chain Slash!!" Nadia yelled, and eight sword flashes shot out from behind her again, the silver sword flashes surrounded the silver wheel, forming a giant silver flower that crashed towards Garen relentlessly.

The eight huge sword flashes followed the turning of the wheel, slicing towards Garen at high speeds, as though intent on cutting him into pieces.

Translator’s Note:

Not sure if it’s a typo or another gender-fluid character… Probably the former.

Chapter 660: Confrontation 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

"First star!!" Garen howled as he released the Seven Star Life's Secret Point. However, he was one step late, and Nadia's powers were now much stronger compared to the last time they had met. Her speed had also exceeded his expectations, making it impossible for him to react in time at all.

After the first star was released, the sword flashes and the silver wheel collided with each other at the moment when her physical qualities increased rapidly.

Boom!!!

Both of them crashed against each other and the sword flashes burst into pieces instantly, turning into countless silver fragments that sprayed everywhere before becoming a metallic windstorm, nailing numerous fragments into the walls messily while releasing ear-piercing screeches.

Garen was violently sent flying as well. He crashed against the transparent wall where the silk screen was located with a ‘bang'. He felt a burning sensation in his chest at once, while a dense and sticky stench wafted out of his throat.

Although he could not feel pain in his dreams, Garen knew that he had suffered internal injuries this time.

Such amazing speed…!

Garen could not keep up with Nadia's speed at all during these few moments. He placed both of his arms in front of his body hastily but was barely able to block her attacks.

Both of his arms were badly mangled and limp to the point where it was impossible to see their original shape.

"This is Absolute Speed." Nadia walked towards him again while dragging a large sword. "I use the Ominous Space Path to speed up this move, allowing it to alter time and space momentarily. You're already destined to be hit when I use this move."

She moved the long sword in her hand casually and immediately positioned the tip of her sword horizontally in front of her body while supporting the blade with one hand.

"This secret technique stresses absolute speed. The faster your speed, the stronger its power. I received this knowledge from an ancient existence in one of the worlds. Your techniques are pitifully lacking because you engage in isolated research alone without expanding your horizons. Your rate of progression is far too slow…"

Boom!!

Before she could finish speaking, a silver sword blossom bloomed immediately. When he saw the knife blossom, Garen tried his best to release the second star but remained dizzy and blurry-eyed. His body met with a violent collision before he was sent flying horizontally.

Silver light danced in front of his eyes, making it impossible for him to see Nadia's figure clearly.

This move, Absolute Speed, was impossible to counter. At its moment of release, Garen could already feel that he was going to be hit. Attacking and receiving the attack were both done simultaneously, leaving only a short space of time in between. For instance, when Nadia released her attack move, Garen would already be in the state of receiving the attack. Once Nadia finished this attack move, Garen would have been hit completely, making it impossible for him to evade it.

Although he managed to crawl up without feeling any pain, his body seemed to be bleeding. The blood flowed on the ground and spread everywhere.

After spitting bloodied phlegm out of his mouth, Garen stood upright. Although the second star's frighteningly strong physical qualities allowed him to suffer less severe injuries this time, he still broke a few ribs.

"Third sword." When he heard Nadia's voice, a silver light lit up in front of his eyes immediately again.

"Third star!! West Phoenix!!" Garen knew that bad things were in store. He howled maniacally and stretched both of his palms forward immediately while a phoenix's ear-piercing cry could be heard behind him. Powerful forces rotated around a mysterious orbit, creating air currents that transformed into a pair of transparent wings.

Both of Garen's hands tore through the air before he pressed his palms together and pierced the area in front of him furiously.

Terrifying powers flowed through his blackened muscles and moved towards his hands in wave-like layers. His muscles rippled and flowed towards his palms continuously as if his entire body was transferring something to both of his hands.

Clang!!!

A sharp metallic noise could be heard as though an unimaginably heavy large metal hammer had violently struck another impossible hard item. It released terrifying sound waves that sent tingles throughout everyone's bodies.

At the center where both of their bodies met, two hands and a large sword wheel had collided with each other suddenly. Time stopped for a moment before a frighteningly strong air current shook the surrounding area. It resembled a violent dynamite explosion that sent both of them flying wildly.

Garen could already feel that he had been hit at the moment of his attack. However, he continued to go forward and deliver his attack. The West Phoenix Fist was a combat technique that he had created on his own to gather and synthesize things. Its abilities included gathering air currents in its surroundings, creating resonating sound attacks that could disturb the state of mind and form large force fields with countless air flows.

"How foolish." Nadia's voice echoed over again, but no one knew when her figure had appeared standing in front of Garen. The air currents and white mist dispersed before she pressed one of her hands against Garen's right eye steadily.

Tch!!

Her fingertips stabbed inwards at once.

Suddenly, Garen felt the feeling of permanent loss creep into his body.

He wanted to hide but that technique stopped him again.. When Nadia attacked, he had already been hit, before a dangerous and threatening air shrouded around him instantly.

His figure leaped ten meters away instantly, but once he stood still, his right eye exploded instantly.

He could see the blood and fluids from his exploded eye dripping on the ground before him.

However, Nadia's figure was now standing in front of him again while her finger was extended towards his left eye this time.

"Fourth star!!!" Garen had no time to think twice and released the fourth star immediately instead. At this moment, a shock wave that could be seen by the naked eye exploded from his body suddenly.

His body had suddenly leaped upwards, reaching a terrifying height of almost three meters. His skin had turned completely black and was giving off a metallic sheen.

"Die!!" Garen howled, completely ignoring Nadia's finger that was pressing against his left eye. Both of his arms struck forward like a large black hammer that brought on terrifying strength and speed that were combined with each other at this moment.

When Garen's hand smashed against Nadia's head, her finger was already poking at his eye socket in an attempt to stab through his head completely.

Hnngh!

Nadia groaned softly and retracted her finger before touching both of Garen's fists firmly.

When the distance between them grew closer, her powers would become greater. She was getting closer to renewing her strength and had no need to fight with Garen to the point where both sides suffered serious losses.

She just needed to wait for the right moment.

Bang!!! Hmm hmm hmm…

Dull vibrating noises echoed throughout the church continuously while Garen stood on the spot and panted. He had violently smashed both of Nadia's arms and broken them with the terrifying strength of his own arms and pierced through her chest brutally while his opponent looked on with a disbelieving gaze.

Fresh white blood sputtered out from Nadia's body. It splashed on the ground and mixed with Garen's red blood that had been spilled earlier. Both of them mixed with each other mysteriously, proving that they came from the same bloodline.

"This… What type of strength is this?!" Nadia was in a state of utter disbelief. Initially, Garen had only possessed a few tons of strength, but once he released the fourth star, he was able to produce terrifying impact forces.

He possessed at least a few hundred tons of frightening strength! Maybe even more!!

"I underestimated… Your Secret Methods," she said with much difficulty while blood dripped from the corners of her mouth.

Garen tore downwards with the strength of both of his arms and tore her into countless pieces of bloody flesh instantly. Strangely enough, these fragments floated in mid-air before weakening and disappearing quickly.

"I was careless… You won't have such good luck next time." Nadia's voice echoed through the air.

Garen knelt down on the floor with a ‘bang'. The aftereffects of releasing the fourth star were finally felt and his entire body was spasming, making him feel as if he could not control his body at all anymore.

Both parties had suffered serious injuries this time. It was impossible for Nadia not to pay the ultimate price, while Garen himself had suffered serious injuries and given up an eye in exchange. But for some unknown reason, Garen could feel unsuppressible excitement surging from the deepest part of his heart continuously.

His life had been peaceful and boring all along. But from this moment, it had become vivid and colorful.

He could see that his world was turning quickly, causing unimaginably strong feelings of happiness to flow out of his heart.

"This feeling…" He looked at both of his hands. They were badly mangled and his palms were almost devoid of flesh, leaving only his bones. However, these terrifying wounds could not suppress the longing he felt for the next battle.

Garen could not help but laugh quietly. These joyful feelings that bubbled up from the deepest part of his heart made it impossible for him to hold back his laughter.

Boom!

The sound of a loud crash rang out beside his ears.

The room was filled with darkness and silence.

Garen crossed his legs and sat in front of the coin. His right eye exploded into a cloud of bloody mist instantly while crunching noises could be heard from his arms and chest. His bones had fractured immediately as all the injuries that were inflicted on him in his dreams were restored throughout his body at once.

Bang bang bang bang!!

A string of continuous explosions could be heard. After every explosion, Garen's entire body ached to the point where he trembled for a moment.

‘Nadia came looking for you! Damn her!!' yelled Black Sethe angrily. ‘That wretched slut. She actually dared to launch a surprise attack on you! She ambushed her own junior who had yet to perfect even one Secret Technique!!'

Heehee… Heeheehee…

The room was suddenly filled with the sound of bloodcurdling laughter.

Garen lowered his head while fresh blood dripped out of his right eye socket slowly and drew a bloody red line down his cheek. However, the corners of his mouth remained curled upwards.

‘What are you laughing about?!' Black Sethe felt his entire body turn numb when he heard it.

"Isn't this really interesting?" said Garen in a low and raspy voice. "Life is finally not as boring anymore…"

He stuck his tongue out and licked the blood at the corners of lips while a potential point was quickly added to his Vitality pane.

Instantly, the wounds on Garen's body began to heal at a pace that was noticeable by the naked eye. His broken bones connected themselves back together speedily while his severe internal injuries healed quickly and stopped bleeding as well. Meanwhile, new skin grew over the bruises on his arms in less than ten few seconds.

Everything except his eye.

Garen stretched his hand out and touched his right eye. Although that space was completely empty, waves of extreme pain assaulted his nerves. However, strong feelings of joy continued to wash over him in waves, purging the dull and bored emotions that had filled his mind.

It was impossible for his eye to be restored…

He understood this truth and knew that it was impossible for potential points to restore organs that had disappeared completely. They could only heal injuries, but could not regrow severed limbs.

But that was unimportant. Compared to his boring life, injuries like this were merely new invitations which Garen did not mind at all.

Black Sethe was unable to say anything else. He had seen Garen's injuries, these terrifying injuries that were enough to let any normal person meet a violent death instantly, but Garen had apparently returned to normal instantly. Moreover, these feelings and this excitement towards killing and life or death combat…

Chapter 661: Soul Seed 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

An individual's true perseverance could only be seen when their life teetered on the fine line between life and death. It was truly a terrifying sight.

Garen had undoubtedly achieved this. He had faced his fears calmly and had even looked down upon them without the slightest care in the world as he'd already encountered too many life-or-death situations.

Perhaps he wouldn't have been able to restrain himself from trembling when he'd first encountered death in the Secret Technique world. However, his current self was no longer the weak and useless normal person he used to be in the past.

Black Sethe was completely unable to understand Garen's feverish excitement. He could never resurrect into a living being with a physical body again as he was merely a set of incomplete memories.

‘You…' He opened his mouth and attempted to say something, but was unable to speak in the end.

Garen inspected the state of his body once over. Although his right eye could not be restored anymore, more than half of the other wounds on his body had healed.

"Nadia…" he murmured quietly before reaching his hand up and brushing his empty right eye socket.

This was the first time he had suffered such serious injuries ever since he'd accomplished his martial arts. Nadia was truly an ancient master, and the slight difference between their powers allowed her to injure him to this extent.

However, this battle had allowed Garen to understand one of the desires in the deepest part of his heart.

Fighting with strong opponents, fighting determinedly with every ounce of his willpower, raising the stakes between life and death, scaling to even higher peaks, enjoying fights, and pursuing battles. All of these were the natural instincts that he had been concealing within the deepest part of his heart all this time.

Garen stretched out both of his hands and looked at the scars that marked his arms. The physical pain in his flesh continued to reverberate inside him, but the intense stimulation and joyful feelings had disappeared completely by now.

The first time he saw the difference in power between Army Level masters clearly, according to Black Sethe's descriptions, he understood that there were separated into five different levels in Ancient Endor which included Soldier, Team, General, Army, and the highest level of Demon King.

This was determined by the Void Creatures' levels. He was currently at the third level of the General level while Nadia belonged to the Army level, meaning that they were only one level apart.

Within the Void Creature world, a difference of one level represented absolute suppression. Numbers were utterly meaningless as the suppression of the levels were fatal and ultimate, without any leeway for resistance.

"Even if I did manage to almost restore my powers to their peak levels in the Totem world, there would still be a large gap between me and Nadia." Garen finally understood that although Form 6 levels of the Totem world seemed to possess extremely powerful strength ranges, these results were tied to the strength of the world itself in reality. The strength of the Totem world was far from the strength of this current world. Therefore, the Form 6 levels of the Totem world were merely equivalent to the strength of the General level.

"How great is the actual difference between a single level?" Garen asked suddenly.

Black Sethe became silent for a moment as he knew what Garen was about to ask.

‘The difference between you and Nadia lies in your inability to integrate all of the strength in your body properly, making it impossible for you to unearth your full potential. In reality, you also have the same Nine-Headed Dragon's Soul Will that produces Nine-Headed Dragon's Blood naturally. However, unlike Nadia, you were unable to unearth the terrifying resurrection abilities and talents.'

"Unearth all of my abilities and talents?" Garen asked again.

‘Yes, your abilities are varied. Nine-Headed Dragon's Will, the Living Secret Techniques that you practice, and the numerous martial arts that you learned in the past have not completely fused together in reality. You need to get rid of the weeds and keep the flowers. The Secret Techniques in your memories are one of those "weeds". You understand them thoroughly but are unable to fuse it with your own martial arts fully. Therefore, your only choice is to create a Secret Technique that you can fully call your own. Pay attention, since this is something that will be fully yours, deciding on a direction beforehand is the right way to find the path that is most suitable to yourself which will lead you on your way.' Black Sethe was not lying to Garen this time but was answering his question honestly instead.

Garen began to ponder.

Indeed, it was true that he had been learning everything in an extremely varied manner all along. Meanwhile, he had always been drifting with the tide, without a true main thread. One of the reasons was because he was unable to find a path that would constantly allow him to go in the way of justice. However, another reason was that he had not persevered through from the beginning to the end.

In the Secret Technique world, he had learned a lot of Secret Techniques and modified them many times. Although his power and strength had increased, they were actually not pure enough and were extremely varied instead.

In the Totem world, he learned about various Totems and modified himself to the point where he seemed like neither man nor monster, and even fusing his soul with the ancient Nine-Headed Hydra's (1) will. This made it even more varied, and he was only able to reach peak levels in the end because of a lucky coincidence.

The things that Black Sethe had said were not wrong. Garen had not found a path that he could walk on continuously all along.

"Do you have any suggestions?" Garen muttered to himself for a moment before finally asking his question.

‘Ancient Endor has disappeared for many years. However, the Void Creatures have flourished vigorously once again. Perhaps this is predestined,' Black Sethe sighed. ‘Although my suggestions may be suitable for others, they may be unsuitable for you. Therefore, you should just fuse everything you have learned so that you can truly grasp your future in your own hands.' This sentence sounded as though he was speaking from the heart, without concealing anything.

‘Ancient Endor views the Demon King level as its peak, leaving us with three paths. Each path is sufficient to lead you there.'

"Which three paths?" Garen's mind stirred while he continued asking.

‘Life, death, and chaos,' said Black Sethe softly. ‘Living Secret Techniques, Dying Secret Techniques, and the Chaotic Secret Techniques that can be found between life and death. These three paths hold everything, cover everything, are vast and boundless, and contain our knowledge and understanding of the universe and the world.'

He continued, saying: ‘If I'm not wrong, the unknown Living Secret Technique that you are altering now should be the Hellfrost Peacock's Living Seed.'

"Hellfrost Peacock?" This was the first time Garen had heard of such a creature.

‘Yes, it is the 32nd strongest Void Creature that went extinct long ago. It is a legacy seed that was extracted and purified by the Warlocks from Mother Stream's True Soul imprint in exchange for paying a heavy price. Your Secret Technique uses its seed as its core, allowing it to continuously develop and evolve while growing. Its final road is actually the final growing stages of the Hellfrost Peacock.'

"In other words, this Living Secret Technique allows people to emulate powerful Void Creatures and evolve like them?" Garen seemed to detect certain hidden meanings.

‘It can be said like that. The Warlocks' observation and research allowed them to identify the existence of the strongest beings. While learning to emulate them, some of the extremely tyrannical Void Creatures also became their modeling subjects. This Secret Technique became the Living Secret Technique seed that the Warlocks released later, and is considered as the strongest path to walk on the road of life.'

"Will it be able to reach peak levels?" Garen asked.

‘It's possible. The Hellfrost Peacock is strongest at the Demon King level. However, the probability of this is extremely low as there is only a very low probability that the Hellfrost Peacock itself will be able to achieve the Demon King level. It is impossible to compare a real Hellfrost Peacock with a human body that is practicing to be and modeling itself after a Void Creature. Therefore, the peak of this Secret Technique should be Army level,' explained Black Sethe.

‘Without vast knowledge and a deep understanding of the true terrors of the Demon King level, you will never be able to reach that realm. Each of the Void Creature's grades is extremely strict, and leaping across them is frankly more difficult than touching the sky. Have you finally understood how precious my Slaughtering Demon Technique is?'

Garen's expression remained unchanged. Getting rid of the Slaughtering Demon Technique was something that he did not regret at all. Regretting past actions and being half-hearted were meaningless, a waste of time, and not part of his nature at all.

‘That was actually a high-level Demonic Technique that was equivalent to the Demon King level! It's hopeless to even think that you'll be able to find a Secret Technique like that ever again!' Black Sethe began to bewitchingly persuade Garen again.

Garen shut himself off from Black Sethe's nonsense immediately. He focused his attention on his own state instead.

He glanced across his Attribute Pane where the name of the unknown Secret Technique was now changed to the Hellfrost Peacock Technique. Meanwhile, while his knowledge regarding high-level Secret Techniques increased, he was gradually able to estimate the limits of Living Secret Techniques. Hence, the contents of his abilities in his Attribute Pane had gradually increased as well.

‘Hellfrost Peacock Technique: Level one beginner (There are five foundation levels, three evolved levels, and eight levels in total). Once the exercises of each level have been accomplished, the bloodline will be purified to allow one to gradually draw close to the Hellfrost Peacock's physical qualities before finally achieving the highest state, which refers to its limit, the Army level.'

Although the other information was still unknown, this was still much better than before.

He glanced at his potential points and noticed that there were only ten points left. He had used two or three points to heal his body but did not pay attention to the exact number, as the injuries that he'd sustained this time were too serious. Not just the injuries from fighting Nadia, but the terrifying consumption from forcefully releasing the fourth star was a fatal consumption as well. If he didn't have potential points to make up for it, he would've had to give up ten years of his lifespan in exchange.

He stood up and walked to the doorway of his room before opening the lock gently and pulling the door open.

On the other side of the door, a maid ran over hurriedly. Her face was confused at first, but when she saw the horrible condition of Garen's mangled right eye…

Ahh!!

Alarmed cries and terrified screams rang out continuously. The other maids in the villa stared at Garen with petrified expressions. They had gathered over from his surroundings. Some of them came from downstairs while others rushed over from the backyard. A large crowd had gathered around Garen instantly.

Garen furrowed his brow and watched as a few of his subordinates parted the sea of people and walked over. He retrieved the Black Copper Mask that he had placed on the bookshelf earlier and wore it on his face at once.

He raised his right hand slowly and spread all five of his fingers outwards.

"Fantasy Fist, forget…!"

After a low rumble, mysteriously alluring and gentle noises could be heard from Garen's right palm suddenly. These noises sounded like both the rippling of a harp and the tremors of a violin that released the seductive melodies of sea sirens.

Within the entire villa, all of the maids and subordinates were attracted by this music. Soon, their attention was unconsciously diverted towards Garen's right hand.

The entire second floor of the villa turned deathly quiet at once. Nobody made a sound and all of their faces remained dazed while they stared at Garen's right hand, unable to move their sight.

When he closed his palm gently, the music stopped suddenly. Garen put his hand down and touched the mask on his face.

Clap clap.

He clapped both of his hands, making crisp noises. Suddenly, all of the dazed people on this floor woke up instantly.

The crowd was obviously somewhat confused and unsure of what to do. Some of them were completely unaware of the reason why they had arrived at the second floor suddenly. They hesitated for a moment before two maids stepped forward.

"Master, do you have any requests?" asked one of them softly.

Everyone noticed the traces of blood that were sputtered on Garen's body and the Black Copper Mask on his face. However, no one could remember why he was wearing a mask. Their memories of Garen's blinded right eye had disappeared from their minds completely as if they had never seen it.

Translator's note:

(1) 九头龙 here refers back to the Nine-Headed Hydra, because Garen is reminiscing about the Nine-Headed Hydra in the previous Totem world, and not referring to the current Nine-Headed Dragon.

Chapter 662: Soul Seed 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

This was the power of the Fantasy Fist. By using air currents and sound wave vibrations, he was able to slightly adjust another person's brain nerves to wipe out memories from a certain time period completely. The Fantasy Fist was known as the most mysterious and terrifying fist technique because of this key aspect. Although it did not possess extremely powerful abilities, these frightening effects were enough to scare the majority of normal people.

Although Garen did not specialize in this fist technique, his superior understanding of martial arts allowed him to use the first technique that involved forgetting without any problems.

"Nothing. All of you can go downstairs now," answered Garen casually.

"Yes," answered the maids and subordinates immediately before leaving.

Once all of them had left, Garen returned to the study and got someone to serve him a cup of green tea before he sat on the leather chair alone.

The mask on his face was the second Black Copper Mask that he'd just received. It was an exact copy of the first mask. Its main characteristic was the clusters of eyes that covered the forehead area. If it wasn't for its ability to constantly absorb potential Qi, it would be very difficult for Garen to differentiate between the first and second mask.

His eye had coincidentally been wounded and now he could wear the mask to conceal his injuries while also speeding up the process of absorbing potential Qi.

He sat in front of his desk and entered a password into the heavy lockbox below.

After a short clicking noise, the box opened.

Garen retrieved a black hardcover notebook from the box and placed it on the table before opening it gently.

The white paper of the first page was filled with his own handwriting.

‘Two-Faced Waterbird Fist, divided into Negative Fist Technique and Positive Fist Technique.

First level —— Jade. It is reminiscent of white jade, undeniably smooth…'

The words there were clearly written in simple American English, but when it was arranged in a sentence, it gave off a faintly exquisite and seductive sensation. These handwritten words seemed like an incomparably gorgeous white jade beauty that was able to attract anyone's attention at first glance with her half exposed pale breasts and flirty poses.

It possessed extremely seductive abilities that made others feel as if their blood vessels were about to surge impatiently.

Garen picked up a pen and continued writing in the notebook.

He had recorded most of the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist's information in this notebook. While recording this, he organized all of the profound mysteries that he had learned about the Waterbird Fist once more. Unconsciously, he could feel that his martial arts were slowly but surely improving.

While he was writing everything down, strange icy blue auras with traces of Soul Seed Qi dispersed around him slowly. This mysterious and icy Qi filled the entire study. Earlier, when his subordinates were about to enter to report new information, they unconsciously felt chills running through their bodies when they reached the doorway, causing them to stop in their tracks as they were too afraid to even knock on the door.

While Garen continued to write slowly, the Two-Faced Waterbird Fist itself was soon pruned fully, allowing it become an extremely pure Demonic Technique. Moreover, Garen was organizing and adjusting his own martial arts while he wrote, causing his aura to release itself and overflow unconsciously before gradually entering this notebook.

Since more than half of the Waterbird Fist's records were already written, Garen continued to write about Shooting Shadow Secret Techniques. However, he would stop writing occasionally when he discovered certain inconsistencies regarding the Shooting Shadow Secret Techniques. He would put his pen down and ponder slowly.

He used this notebook to record and compile information and referred to it as the Book of Demonic Secret Techniques or the Demonic Book for short.

Garen had originated from the orthodox Secret Technique path. He was exceptionally well-versed in the right path of Secret Techniques but did not have much contact with Demonic Secret Techniques. This method of writing everything down allowed him to gain a deeper understanding of his Demonic Secret Techniques. Strangely enough, when he was writing the Demonic Book, his own aura would integrate into it slowly, causing this Demonic Book to be somewhat out of the ordinary.

Garen was looking forward to the changes that would occur in his martial arts once he'd finished writing this Demonic Book.

Black Sethe had once said that this organization method would deepen his understanding of martial arts. Since he was an individual who possessed a Soul Seed, once the organization process was completely finished and the effects of the Secret Techniques on the soul were dispelled, the purification of his own martial arts would occur.

Purifying his martial arts would allow his Secret Techniques to reach a new level. Perhaps this Demonic Book could help him form a second Soul Seed as well.

Garen had these vague feelings.

He was unsure of how to practice the Demonic Secret Techniques. It seemed as though it could not help improve him at all and could only strengthen the power and killing abilities. However, whenever he practiced Living Secret Techniques and upgraded his level, he noticed that his physical qualities would improve while certain specialized abilities and qualities would sometimes be given to the practitioner as well.

Regarding the Hellfrost Peacock Technique's abilities, he was looking forward to them as well. However, the first beginner's level would not upgrade his abilities at all. Instead, it would simply change the nature of his aura from the characteristics of the black Slaughtering Demon Technique to the icy blue frost-type aura.

Therefore, he was looking forward to level two and above even more.

Under the bright yellow desk lamp, Black Sethe slowly and silently condensed himself into a human-shaped black mist figure behind Garen. He looked on quietly while Garen wrote of the profound mysteries of Secret Techniques inside the Demonic Book while complicated expressions flashed in his blood red eyes faintly.

Through the knowledge and understanding that Garen had learned, he was able to see the complexity of his findings. Although the starting point was not too high, this relentless willpower and valiant bravery in the face of death caused Black Sethe to unconsciously think of his own body.

He could see that the Demonic Book was gradually being infected and polluted by his soul's impurities. These impurities were the poisonous substances that were expelled from Garen's soul. They seeped into the Demonic Book using methods that could not be seen by the naked eye and gradually transformed this normal notebook.

Meanwhile, the Qi of Garen's soul was slowly changing as well because it was constantly being purified. The image of the Demonic Book was unknowingly being condensed by his subconsciousness, forming a Demonic Book that was filled with the depths of his will and soul. That Demonic Book continued perfecting itself while he organized everything in reality.

‘Once he has perfected this Demonic Book completely, perhaps the day will come when his second Soul Seed is formed.' Black Sethe had already made these assumptions internally.

Once three Soul Seeds had become his fuel and backing force, there would be a possibility for him to strengthen and push his Secret Techniques to the next level. This was the greatest use of the Soul Seed. Perhaps there would come a day where he would truly be able to push himself to the Demon King level.

Furthermore, it could also increase the limits of one's physical qualities, modify characteristics, and even create Living Secret Technique Seeds… There were numerous functions.

The Soul Seeds encompassed rules and knowledge, possessed an awareness of the universe, and also had its own True Soul imprints.

It was similar to the Hellfrost Peacock Seed that was formed by condensing some of the Hellfrost Peacock's Soul Seeds. It contained the Hellfrost Peacock's awareness, understanding, and knowledge of itself.

Garen had heard Black Sethe's explanation on the uses of the Soul Seed before this. He wrote them down in the Demonic Book while thinking about the relationship between potential points and Secret Techniques.

For most Secret Technique Levels, accumulated potential points were able to speed up the process, decreasing the time required to practice it painstakingly. Since most Secret Techniques did not require complicated sentiments or difficult conditions, they were naturally able to upgrade themselves with potential points.

Meanwhile, it was difficult to use potential points to forcefully upgrade other high-level Secret Techniques like Living Secret Techniques. Potential points could only be used to shorten the time needed to practice uncomplicated Secret Techniques that did not have checkpoints. However, high-level Secret Techniques usually involved various hardships and dangers. Extremely powerful Halos with terrifying potential strength involved incomparable difficulties and required a lot of awareness and accumulated experiences and knowledge before it could evolve one step at a time.

This was probably the reason why it was difficult to use potential points to strengthen and upgrade Living Secret Techniques.

"In other words, potential points can only provide accumulated quantities, but qualitative changes depend on oneself." Garen made the conclusion before suddenly remembering the problem he had with his Soul Seed. That uncertainty became more obvious after he had fought with Nadia.

"Right, Black Sethe," Garen closed the Demonic Book gently before speaking. "If three Soul Seeds can strengthen a General level Secret Technique and upgrade it by one level, why was Nadia still unable to achieve the Demon King level after so many years?"

Black Sethe remained quiet for a moment before speaking slowly.

‘It's rare to find those who belong to the Demon King level now.'

"Why?" Garen was shocked.

‘The fury of Mother Stream destroyed everything who belonged to the Demon King level, regardless whether they were our own people or others. There were many things, not just Secret Techniques that were able to achieve that level. We had once tread across that summit,' Black Sethe replied. ‘During the ancient Warlock era, countless Warlocks were endowed with outstanding natural talents. They practiced various high-level Secret Techniques that were equivalent to the Demon King level. However, how many of them were able to reach the peak in the end?'

He paused before continuing. ‘It's similar to your awareness that you'll be able to succeed in anything as long as you fight determinedly, practice everything diligently, and add a pinch of inspiration and perseverance. But knowing it is one thing. Everyone already knows that as long as you persevere without giving up, you will succeed in the end even if you fail many times. However, there are only so many people who can actually endure numerous failures and persevere through such extents.'

Garen was speechless because Black Sethe's words were right.

The greatest drawback in life was giving up.

Even if an individual was able to face something without giving up, he would still encounter countless failures. However, even the unluckiest person would taste success one day. This was the principle behind ‘practice makes perfect' and ‘failure is the mother of success'.

He suddenly remembered the ancient Chinese teaching methods of Earth.

Those teachings had seemed outdated at that time because they focused on making students persevere in repeatedly reading and memorizing works of famous writers.

However, it now seemed extremely reasonable as it was suitable for everyone. It was a teaching method that could be used for anyone regardless whether they were naturally talented, slow-witted or bright.

Memorizing something many times would allow a person to be more familiar with a certain subject, allowing them to remember their punctuation marks as well. Therefore, the surface meaning of this literary work could be understood easily.

Meanwhile, the work of a renowned writer would contain layers of deeper meanings. The minds of most people would be unable to detect the profound meanings and philosophy behind it.

However, once someone was undeniably familiar with the text and continued to recite it by memory, this would certainly become mentally easy. Once the surface meaning of the text was recited and understood many times, the mental strength and attention used for reciting would be freed up. They would unconsciously focus on the concealed paths and cracks within the famous work instead. As one continued to unearth more information from the cracks, they would finally be able to find the deeper meanings and philosophies there.

This kind of wealth and knowledge that was gained from painstaking perseverance was truly the most precious thing to men. Things that could be obtained easily were not considered to be precious at all. The human subconscious was aware that anything that could be easily obtained could simply be found again in times of need. Furthermore, it knew that if it persevered slightly harder, it would be able to gain even more, leaving no need for such valuable things.

Chapter 663: Surprise Attack 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Garen's thoughts flowed through his mind quickly for a few moments while he pondered about several things.

Undoubtedly, he was currently at a level where he was already very familiar with his Secret Techniques and himself. However, after his countless practices to familiarize himself with this, and the numerous inspections of his own body, he had discovered secrets that were hidden deeper within.

‘Our world is merely a tiny part of the dark, endless, and infinite universe. A human being's electromagnetic spectrum can only detect less than one percent of light spectrums, while the other ninety-nine percent of this is mere darkness. Meanwhile, these are merely the results of supposed scientific and technological probing. In reality, the light waves in the universe are more extensive. Occasionally, we are completely unable to use wavelengths and frequencies to differentiate spectrums,' said Black Sethe softly.

"I understand these things that you are saying," said Garen quietly. "The universe that we can see is less than one percent of the true universe. This is only the light that we are able to see. Out of the parts of the universe that can be seen because of this light, we would gradually be able to unearth the true enigmas of the universe if we were able to see the remaining dark areas of the universe, is that true?"

‘The Warlocks have already done a part of it. They were able to come into contact with a broader world through the Dream World. Furthermore, they were also able to contact stronger civilizations through their Secret Techniques. Once they had seen the world outside the spectrum, that magnificent and unimaginable world was something that you would not be able to comprehend at all. Various life forms and different types of marvelous laws. The universe is so mysterious but you and I are so insignificant. Even the entire Warlock civilization was but a tiny wave in the universe, and perhaps not even that. Even the Mother Stream which we regard as vast and infinite is merely a belief that we hold because of our inexperience and narrow-mindedness.'

Garen was temporarily mesmerized by Black Sethe's descriptions of these characteristics.

‘The Underworld is what we regard as the deepest and most mystical part of our universe and is collectively known as the eternal depths. We can only see a tiny part of the universe while the rest is merely endless darkness that forms the depths of eternal mystery. We pursue the different lights that we see. Some of those lights bear knowledge while others bear the weight of history. We firmly believe that there is only one ray of light that we are able to see in this universe. That light has recorded all of the mysteries and history of the universe. Its wavelengths are unimaginable while its frequencies use units of millions of years. It views the effects of stronger gravitational forces and rules as merely light rain.' The tone of Black Sethe's voice made him sound like an extremely devout follower who was describing his one and only firm believe.

‘That, is the Eternal Light.'

Garen held his breath and remained silent for a moment.

Eternal Light was a piece of information that he had been completely unable to find in his books. Although Ancient Endorian civilizations worshipped the Underworld, the thing that they were actually pursuing was the Eternal Light that recorded all knowledge.

‘Legend has it that as long as you can adjust the frequency of your soul to a weird degree, you will be able to absorb a certain extent of the Eternal Light's effects and gain some of its mysterious knowledge,' Black Sethe lamented. ‘It's unfortunate that no one has been able to accomplish this successfully before. We have never been able to prove the existence of the Eternal Light the same way we have yet to prove the existence of the eternal Underworld.'

Garen listened quietly. He had never heard these things that Black Sethe was saying before as they were the cores essences of the beliefs of the Ancient Endorian civilizations.

‘Whatever, what's the use of saying this now?' Black Sethe was somewhat down-hearted. "Organize all of this properly. This Demonic Book may end up affecting your martial arts greatly.'

His voice drifted off into silence. It seemed as though this conversation had caused his yearning for the once prosperous civilization to reemerge.

Garen sat at his desk for a long time, waiting for his emotions to calm down before knocking the table slowly.

"Come in."

His subordinate who had been waiting outside the door for a long time pushed it open slowly before walking into the room.

He was a young man with golden hair who was fully clad in black clothes. A silver colored ‘7' was embroidered on the collar of his clothes.

"Reports that were just delivered from the hidden room." The man placed the informational documents that he was holding on Garen's table.

Garen picked up the information and scanned through it before his brow wrinkled slightly at once.

Information about most of the forces that participated in carrying out surprise attacks on the Nighthawks was written there.

The largest Primary Color group was apparently listed there. The Primary Color's White Phoenix whose person in charge was Gremlin, an arrogant man who was currently 56 years old, had an irritable personality and was haughty and rude towards others. Garen could not understand why he was leader of White Phoenix at all.

The Viper mercenaries were next. They were one of the top ten mercenary groups in Europe which possessed an abundance of strength. Their expertise lay in silent hunting tactics that allowed them to complete various tasks in extremely quiet conditions. The name of their commander was unknown as everyone merely referred to him as King Snake.

The Bailey Group came after that. Their boss was called Kabb while the person in charge was Medis. His behavior was kind and gentle, and it was rumored that he only joined their operations because he was forced to participate by the Primary Colors.

White Phoenix, Viper, and the Bailey Group were the three key participants who were involved in this incident. However, there were more than ten other smaller mercenary groups and assassin teams with lower rankings as well.

The group that caused the greatest losses within the Nighthawks were White Phoenix and Viper. White Phoenix's strongest subordinates, the Ohio Silk mercenary group was the second mercenary group in Europe that possessed extremely powerful fighting abilities. They had robbed Jay of the various antiques and relics that Garen had found, and were even able to suppress him to the point where he was unable to escape. He was currently still at the Black Uniform's headquarters.

"White Phoenix's Ohio Silk?" Garen put the papers down. The Black Uniforms and the Nighthawks were his left and right-hand men. Meanwhile, when White Phoenix initially faced the dilemma of their destroyed headquarters, they were supposed to change their person in charge first. Instead, their previous leader remained, and they had yet to make a move until now. Currently, they had suddenly sent their strongest elite mercenary group out, meaning that they definitely had new plans by now.

The Primary Colors were like giants, humongous giants. Consenting to these actions meant that they were really planning to make their moves against the Nighthawks.

Garen tidied his train of thought. He knew that this fight would be inevitable. He lifted the landline telephone gently and dialed a number.

*********************

Jay's body was wrapped in a black trench coat. He wore a hat and sunglasses and covered more than half of his face with a mask, making it completely impossible to see his face clearly.

He strolled along the streets of Bailey, blending with the crowds as if he was merely an office worker who was completely unnoticeable.

He circled around a street performer who was playing the accordion. He raised his head and glanced at the gloomy white clouds in the sky before his phone rang suddenly.

He took his handphone out and glanced at the number before walking to the corner of an unassuming public bus stand and taking the call there.

"Boss."

"How's your situation?" Garen's voice echoed from the phone.

"The Ohio Silk members are still pursuing me, but I managed to get rid of two of them. I need backup." Jay did not dare to let his guard down when he replied. His pupils would occasionally scan from left to right. He lowered his voice to a volume that was just enough for the other person to hear.

"Listen, Ohio Silk members are subordinates of White Phoenix. In reality, this organization was formed when White Phoenix selected its own elite members. Their characteristics are their extremely powerful and technologically advanced equipment," Garen mentioned. "The latest weapons that the Primary Colors and White Phoenix created will likely be on them. Since you've been unable to escape their tracks for such a long time, it's better for you to check if there's anything wrong with your body."

He paused for a moment. "I will send some people as backup. However, Ohio Silk has adjusted our surface connections. Therefore, it is very likely that the people I send over will be monitored at once. At most, they will only be able to lighten a part of your burdens."

"This will be enough. I will head to Berlin as soon as possible." Jay had gotten used to living on the edge of life and death. His expression remained unchanged. As long as Boss did not forsake him, everything else would not be an obstacle.

"Take care of your safety," reminded Garen finally.

The phone call was cut off before Jay quickly deleted his call log. After that, he selected the function to forcefully erase the RAM. Storage tools would always be able to restore data to a certain extent. As long as one possessed adequate skills, a large amount of data could still be restored from hard disks that had been reformatted twice. In order to prevent Boss's number from getting leaked, his handphone was custom made and could hide his storage more than ten times in a short space of time to ensure that it was completely secret.

After keeping his phone, Jay stuck both of his hands into pockets and left the bus stand quickly.

Soon after, two unassuming men in plain clothes within the crowd began to tail him from different angles and speeds.

There was a spacious office in a silver skyscraper further away.

Two young men sat in front of a strange-looking computer. Both of them were donning sophisticated black earphones while they stared at the computer screen with a fixed gaze.

The shape of the computer resembled a shell that had split into two separate halves. There was a large display screen on the front while two men stood in front of two other glass screens that were nearly transparent. Various monitor screens flashed on the translucent screens endlessly.

These screens had been separated into small palm-sized areas that were neatly arranged on the screen as if they had been captured by someone from a high angle.

"The other party has either used obstructive clothing or something to cut off the signal. Make the electronic mosquitoes fly a little closer," said a man's voice from behind the two others.

"Boss, you're here." Both of them turned their heads and stood up simultaneously.

"Make sure to follow close behind so that you don't lose him." The other man waved his hand uninterestedly. "How long will the odor-tracking last?"

"About thirty-five minutes."

The man who had arrived earlier nodded.

"Get Lotus Pearl to move out. She just came back from her break but it's time for her to make a move already."

This man had a pale face, hooked beak-like nose, sinister gaze, a slightly raised lower jaw, and a height of almost 190 centimeters. There was an arrogant expression on his face whenever he spoke or looked at people.

He was Gremlin, White Phoenix's new person in charge. He was extremely dissatisfied with his predecessor and carried himself with a heavy air of influence from his moment of arrival.

"The Nighthawks all have a set of specialized ways to activate their own potentials. Pay attention and see if you can capture them alive. According to the information from our research and development section, these methods of activating potential could very likely form new impacts on our current technology. It may be able to produce new results as well," Gremlin mentioned.

"Understood," both of the people who were monitoring the situation nodded after receiving his commands.

Their fingers clicked on the keyboard constantly while countless wireless signals were continuously released.

The mercenaries in the outside world who were hidden amongst the crowds of normal people raised their wrists and looked at their watches at once. New sets of finely written characters and symbols flashed on their black watches occasionally.

Anticipation began to stir in Gremlin's heart as he watched his subordinates adjust the forces that were encircling Jay.

Ever since the Nighthawks had made a name for themselves, the source of their powerful strengths caused people in the outside world to harbor suspicions and investigate them. Recently, a high-level Black Uniform member that was seeking shelter revealed a shocking secret.

This was the key factor that influenced the superiors of the Primary Colors to strongly support the White Phoenix's counter-attacks against the Nighthawks.

When he thought of the discovery that gave normal people the chance to become extraordinarily powerful, hatred began to bubble up Gremlin's heart.

"We must obtain the Secret Method of absorbing the energy from antiques and relics! Since the Nighthawks are so powerful, it's very likely that a Secret Method like this already exists! To think that they could achieve such power in the span of a few short years…"

When he thought of this, his heart began to burn with rage.

Chapter 664: Surprise Attack 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Elvin, England.

Kabb sat upright in the electronic conference room in his own estate with a kind but serious expression on his face. On his right was golden-haired Medis. This handsome man was dressed in a suit and leather shoes with an apologetic look on his face.

There were no subordinates around them, making them the only two people who were seated inside the entire conference room.

Sunlight cascaded inside through the windows on the left and scattered golden spots on the ground.

A large display screen was currently projected on the wall on the opposite side of them. The face of a fierce bald man was displayed there.

"Mr. Kabb, the movement that your group participated in caused my wife Hera to fall into a dangerous situation. Whether or not the actions of the Vipers have your support, their attitude has already decided that there is nothing left to be said between us," The bald man Kaedun's deep voice echoed from the screen. He spoke extremely fluent English but the tone of his voice was filled with great dissatisfaction and slight anger.

"Of course, if your people had not sent the surgical specialists in time, perhaps my people would have suffered even greater injuries. I still keep all of this in my heart."

"Commander Kaedun." An apologetic yet impatient expression appeared on Kabb's face. "We have indeed been participating in the Primary Color's activities, but this does not mean that we wish to be enemies with your group. In reality, when I heard this news, I didn't dare to believe it myself because I knew that we would be drawn into this war. Although we are the underground organization of a managing department, our true nature and duty still lie with being honest businessmen."

"What do you mean?" Bald Kaedun did not want to bother himself with this nonsense and chose to dive into the main topic instead.

"I accidentally deepened the conflict between both parties and caused this secret meeting to occur." The impatience on Kabb's face became more apparent. "The information we received stated White Phoenix had sent special-class mercenaries to hunt Mr. Jay down. Therefore, I hope that you'll be able to make prior preparations."

"Special-class mercenaries?" It was obvious that Baldy had retracted his gaze. This was the nickname of the circle of mercenaries that belonged to the highest level within White Phoenix. Every single special-class mercenary was extremely mysterious and strong. Their task completion rate always remained at ninety percent and above. People even spread rumors that these special-class mercenaries were the true core of White Phoenix and it was very likely that they were the result of Primary Color members who were involved with technological modifications.

Before he met Boss Garen, he was always worried that his abilities were lacking because he could not understand how these special-class mercenaries were able to be so powerful. However, it was different now. When he thought about it now, those special-class mercenaries were probably just experts who belonged to levels that were similar to his own.

They already possessed certain specialized abilities and talents that were coupled with the latest and most technologically advanced equipment.

The special-class mercenaries were the strongest group of people in this world. As humans, they already possessed various terrifying talents that were matched with advanced technology, allowing their single-person combat skills to easily reach frightening levels.

Baldy's heart tensed slightly before he calmed down immediately.

"This piece of information was very timely and I can feel your sincerity, Mr. Kabb."

"Actually, I have a request," said Kabb softly.

"Please go ahead." After receiving this news and intelligence, bald Kaedun did not have any doubts towards Kabb's sincerity anymore.

"I was hoping that I could meet His Excellency the Nighthawk King. I don't know if this request… Of course, I'm not asking for a personal meeting, just a long-distance one," said Kabb with an honest look on his face.

"This would require me to ask for instructions before I can give you a reply," said bald Kaedun while nodding. "If Boss agrees, I will send you an invitation link."

"I sincerely thank you for this," said Kabb quickly.

"The Bailey Group has shown their sincerity. As friends, it is natural for us to show our sincerity as well," nodded bald Kaedun. "Could you tell me more detailed information about the special-class mercenaries?"

"This…" Kabb looked at Medis who stood beside him before the latter smiled and stood up.

"The special-class mercenary that White Phoenix decided to send this time is ‘Lotus Pearl'. I'm only aware of this alias, but I don't know if it's a real name or a nickname. We are uncertain about other things. Please forgive us."

"Lotus Pearl, huh?" A look of realization flashed across Baldy's eyes. As a former member of White Phoenix, it was only natural that he would recognize the name ‘Lotus Pearl'.

That insane woman or a believer of an evil cult, in other words.

She was a believer in an evil cult that was known as Jagerly and followed in their almost fanatical footsteps.

She liked using an ax to murder people and would never leave a single trace behind whenever she completed her tasks. She was arrested by the police in Europe once but the court trial concluded that she was not guilty and released her because there was no proof that she had actually killed anyone despite the fact that almost everyone knew that she was the murderer.

Kabb was so familiar with her because this woman's friend was the previous instructor of his batch of students who had taught them how to avoid leaving any kind of traces.

But none of these were key aspects. Instead, it was important to note that every single special-class mercenary possessed their own ultimate techniques, abilities, or talents. Lotus Pearl's ability was her extremely terrifying intuition.

Her intuition allowed her to notice that something was amiss during the moment when a gun was aimed precisely at her. Furthermore, she also possessed extremely frightening skills during close combat. These skills were tied to her intuition, and as long as a pointed object was precisely aimed at her, goosebumps of various intensities would appear all over her body, allowing her to react instantly.

Some people felt that her special skill was overly sensitive. Although regular people would feel a strange sensation on the tips of their noses when they aimed sharp objects there directly, she would amplify these instincts and spread them throughout her entire body.

Lotus Pearl was also one of the ten most well-known special-class mercenaries in White Phoenix.

"I never thought that it would be her…" When Baldy thought about engaging in close combat with an expert that was stronger than his own previous instructor, fearful feelings flashed in his mind but were overshadowed by excitement.

Fear and excitement soon blended with each other, making it almost impossible for him to differentiate between them.

He had once thought of the special-class mercenaries as opponents that he could never defeat. However, he was about to encounter one of them in the flesh now.

Once the call was disconnected, Kabb immediately dialed Garen's phone number.

"Are you certain that you can do this?" These were the first words that came out of Garen's mouth after he heard the entire situation.

"No," answered Baldy honestly. "Lotus Pearl is extremely powerful. My current self is unworthy to be her opponent. Meanwhile in long-range combat… It will be completely impossible for us to even find her."

"This is your own war," Garen pondered for a moment then spoke slowly. "Martial arts requires you to be bold and powerful as you forge ahead vigorously. You cannot have any forms of hesitation or shadows in your heart. What do you choose?"

This was the first time Baldy had experienced Garen's brand new tone. He had never experienced this tone of voice used for teaching and guidance in the past before.

This was a change in attitude.

"I will work hard!" Baldy calmed his heart and spoke in a low voice. He knew that if he was unable to face this trouble, there was a possibility that Garen would substitute another person to take his position of Vice Commander because Nighthawks could not be fearful.

Clap.

The voice receiver of the telephone was put down.

Garen crossed all ten of his fingers and turned his head to look out of the window. The leaves on the maple trees had begun to turn red. Some of them fell when the wind gusted and drifted downwards slowly. All of the leaves on the maple tree seemed like the feathers of flying birds that floated slowly before flying away.

"Autumn has arrived again…" He stood up and walked to stand in front of the window before opening it slowly.

There were black shadows that were faintly flashing in the surroundings outside the villa. These black shadows rushed towards the villa speedily and quietly from various blind angles as if they were insects in the shadows.

Garen glanced at the maid who was watering the plants downstairs and closed his eye suddenly. His face that was left with only one eye was currently covered by a mask, making it impossible to see his expression.

"The target has appeared."

A faint noise echoed from his earpiece.

Within the black shadows, a petite woman stopped in her tracks suddenly while sticking close to one of the blind angles near the wall of the villa. She slowly released a Black Uniform guard whose neck had been twisted brutally.

"Pay attention and stay alert. The other person is the First Nighthawk King of Africa," said the woman quietly. "Has the equipment in the various areas been installed properly?"

"Everything has been set up properly." "We're just waiting for you."

Different voices could be heard from the earpiece. If she listened closely, she could even hear that some of the voices were nearer while others were softer. This meant that different people were concealed in positions of various distances.

A stern look flashed in the woman's blue eyes.

"Well then, the Hawk Hunting Plan begins now!" She commanded immediately.

Instantly, all of the black shadows that were hidden in the ambush spots raised their various firearms and devices respectively. Some of them bent their bodies and charged towards the villa hurriedly.

The guards they encountered on the way collapsed without a fight. It was uncertain whether they were dead or alive.

Two sniper rifles were precisely aimed at Garen who was standing in front of the window at once.

The dynamiters pressed down on the buttons on the explosives in their hands simultaneously.

"Let me give the Nighthawk King a lesson that he will never forget for the rest of his life… Hehe," laughed the male deputy softly. He used one eye to look at the man in front of the window through his sniper's precise optical sight.

His finger pulled the trigger slightly.

Pfoo… A few maple leaves blew past slowly while a blob of red rolled past the sight.

Once the maple leaf had flown past, the silhouette in the sight had disappeared completely.

The deputy was slightly shocked.

"Gone!!! He's gone!" "Pay attention to your surroundings! Stay hidden, stay hidden!!"

"Get ready to blow up the dynamite at any time!!" "Dahm!"

Different voices echoed from the earpiece.

The deputy was stunned but suddenly felt a threat ambushing him from behind.

Boom!

He rolled towards his left immediately. He had no time to even look for his sniper rifle, and he used his other hand to remove the small dagger in his shoe while stumbling backward.

A gentle laugh could be heard from behind him. It sounded like a male voice.

"Members of White Phoenix?" The voice was unusually calm.

The deputy turned around after rolling about and happened to see a man in a black mask who was standing behind him. This man was holding his rifle in his hand and rotating it about to examine it. Meanwhile, his own little dagger had fallen on the floor after he dropped it. Was the distance that he estimated from the sound of the previous noise completely wrong?

Bang bang bang…!

A string of gunshots pelted the mud and lawn beside the man's feet and caused streaks of black mud and bits of grass to splatter. Strangely enough, none of the gunshots had actually landed in the area where he was standing, and all of the bullets had automatically formed a circle around his feet.

This abnormal phenomenon sent chills down the deputy's spine.

All of his group members were absolutely God-like snipers that had been handpicked. However, none of them were able to hit the target. The only explanation for this was that this man had a strange air about him that influenced their judgment.

It was similar to the incident that had happened earlier. Although he had clearly seen that there was a person there, the man was able to end up behind him instantly instead!

"Don't act rashly," said the deputy quietly. "About five powerful explosives have been placed below our feet. My group members can press the button to activate these explosives at any time depending on how things stand."

Garen furrowed his eyebrows and looked at the man who stood in front of him. This man did not seem concerned about his own safety. Instead, he could vaguely feel that something seemed to be lingering around him. It seemed like a vibration or wave motion. At times, he would be unable to feel anything, making him wonder if this was merely an illusion.

These wave motions made his head feel slightly uneasy.

Bang!!

A powerful sniper bullet flew towards him suddenly. It passed through the maple trees and the air currents, spinning quickly in the air before finally hitting the deputy's chest.

Boom!!

His entire body instantly exploded into two pieces. The upper half of the body fell and collapsed on the floor in a bloody mess while the body half exploded and was sent flying towards a distance of more than a few meters away. There was a look of disbelief on his face.

Garen put the sniper rifle down and walked towards the other places slowly.

"We've gotten rid of him! I injured him!" "The Nighthawk King is not even a big deal!" "We must be careful not to be careless during the final battle!"

Different voices echoed through their earpieces, but the woman who led the group was the only one who could vaguely sense that something was amiss.

Chapter 665: Intensification 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Boom!! Bang!!

A series of explosions burst around Garen but none of it accurately hit his position.

The ground was destroyed beyond recognition and the bullets left rows and rows of bullet holes on the wall. The smokes and flames lit up more than half of the villa and most of the villa was engulfed in a sea of flames.

Yet strangely, the red flames did not cause any disturbance to the surroundings. The surroundings were quiet and the residents of the suburban did not have any sort of reaction.

Garen walked into the barrage of bullets. From time to time, there were balls of fire exploding in the places he'd walked through.

"I blew him up! Hahaha!!"

"I hit his right arm, avoid him, he went towards Jack's directions!"

"Ready for melee! Support cover!"

One by one, men dressed in black came out of their hiding places and charged towards the empty air near Garen. As though performing for some sort of martial arts film, they punched and kicked and sometimes took out knives and guns to shoot a few times.

Garen slowly walked beside them and poked their shoulders.

Peng!

The upper body of one person burst open and blood scattered around.

This was the power of Fantasy Fist.

Garen sighed. Facing these elites who had never encountered this kind of fist techniques, Fantasy Fist easily deceived their perception and allowed them to see a completely different vision.

In this illusion, these so-called White Phoenix elites were as fragile as babies.

Peng peng peng!!

With the sound of gunshots, the dark figures were shooting at each other and very soon the frequency of the sounds was getting lower and eventually, there were no more sounds.

Garen walked towards the back of the villa along the wall and stopped suddenly.

Hong!

The right wall with the thickness of half-a-meter was pierced through by his hand and it seized the neck of a White Phoenix man on the other side.

With a kacha sound, this man's struggling hands and feet immediately went limp.

Throwing away the corpse, Garen walked through this hole that was made by him and smashed the wall once more to enlarge the hole.

He was totally a monster right now. His combat power was terrifying and with the potential points, any kind of injuries could be healed. He had speed as fast as lightning, godly fist techniques and his body had a 7 points defense which a common knife might not even scratch.

A random punch could muster a few tons of impact. If he went all out, coupled with his speed, he could create several hundred tons of impact and could even go as high as a thousand tons. If he added Seven Star Life's Secret Point….

With immense strength and a strong outburst, that was how Nadia's projection in the distance had been destroyed. With an average of seven points in his physical fitness, after opening the fourth star, he reached the limit of the body which was the genetic limit in this life. An average of thirty points was the limit of the body and it was unable to get any higher.

The limit of power and speed coupled with a strong physique, Nadia's projection was easily destroyed by Garen.

At this point, the numbers in strength no longer had any meaning. For Garen, the measurement of strength in tons had no value, it was simply just numbers.

The hundreds of tons of power that Nadia's projection had, that was her projection's limit but it was nowhere near Garen's limit when he had opened his fourth star. She failed because she was unable to measure the momentary change in Garen's power but Garen knew that even as the distance between him and Nadia shrunk, she still had her Eighty One Life Talent. Furthermore, due to the limit in his soul, he could only reach the genetic limit of thirty points and could not proceed.

The Seven Star Life's Secret Point was a secret method that could enhance the physical fitness for a short amount of time and cause an outburst in the form of body's potential, but this secret method could not forcibly exceed the limit of what the body and soul could endure.

The limit for an average person was just two or three points but Garen was different and his limit was ten times the average person. With the help of the Soul Seed, his body and soul's limit were thirty points but not even he could surpass this limit.

Going into the hole, Garen's mind was full of thoughts while he searched for remnants of the White Phoenix attackers.

Suddenly, a black knife flew from his right side, brushing the edge of Garen's mask and stabbed soundlessly into the wall on his left side, like piercing into tofu.

Holding the black knife was a petite girl in a black bodysuit. Her shoulders were covered with two metal plates and around her waist was a black metallic belt.

Seeing that her attack had failed, the girl did a series of dodging actions and rolled away from Garen before she realized that Garen was still standing there, unmoving.

The girl armed with the black knife did a half-squat and looked unusually nervous. She was covered in cold sweat. After seeing her teammates died a bizarre death one by one, she finally realized that what she saw might not necessarily be true.

In her vision before, she saw her teammates hiding at the original ambush point but when she went over to greet them, they were motionless and unresponsive.

In the villa, except for the sound of the flames burning, everything else was silent.

Her vision was showing her that the one standing in front of her was not someone else but the deputy that was fighting the enemy at the very beginning, the affable young man that everyone was very familiar with.

Her body trembled involuntarily.

She gritted her teeth and hid in a darker corner. A teammate was also lying in the ambush point beside her, aiming a gun at the enemy.

"Jack!" She patted her teammate on the shoulder lightly.

The teammate did not respond. His gun's muzzle was still aimed at the same point with the same posture as though he was a sculpture.

The girl suppressed the chill in her heart, knowing that this was another ‘dead man'.

She came here with more than ten teammates but now she had encountered a lot of ‘dead people'. They were all unresponsive. They were all very active in the beginning but now they were all completely silent.

As long as it was the place that deputy walked past, all of her active teammates would become totally silent.

"Illusion…it was all an illusion!" As though she had understood something, she quickly took out a monocle like a nervous cheetah, from her waist.

The light blue lens on the monocle flashed and showed her some data and then went back to normal.

A horrifying sight suddenly appeared.

What she saw on the lens was completely different from what she saw with her other eye!

She was not hiding at the ambush point right now. She was squatting beside the corpse of one of her teammates, her body was stained with blood and in front of her…

In front of her was not the deputy she knew, it was that man. That man called King of the Night Hawk!!

"What a poor little kitty…" The man looked at her with a compassionate expression.

At the same time, she heard the voice of the deputy overlapping with that man's voice.

The girl's expression fell.

She looked around with her monocle and found the body of another teammate at the staircase.

The lens showed the body being licked by flame. There was the burning smell of flesh.

And in her other eye's sight, she saw her teammate smiling and waving at her, looking as though he was calling for her to come over.

A chill shuddered through her, from her heart to her scalp. The girl fell on her bottom.

This was something that she had encountered for the first time. Just which was an illusion and which was real…

"Real sleep is pathetic…" Garen raised his hands and clapped lightly.

Pa!

Fantasy Fist's horrifying effect dissipated.

He did not expect that with the support from his Soul Seed, Fantasy Fist would become so potent that the elites from White Phoenix would fall into the illusion at the first moment they saw him.

No, it was not simply an illusion.

Garen narrowed his eyes and stared at the petite girl in the black bodysuit. He had lifted the fist technique but there was still no light in her eyes.

He saw something unusual in her eyes.

Dang!

The girl's black knife fell to the ground and made a clear sound.

"No!!!" She screamed as though she was looking at something terrifying.

‘Watch out on the right!' Black Sethe's suddenly came.

Garen dodged to the side and made a punch to his right side.

Boom!! Dang!!

He did know how he got to the wall's side. This punch of his hit right on the knife that had penetrated the wall.

However, Garen's body was so strong that the knife broke.

He retracted his fist, feeling something strange spreading in his heart.

"This is not my fist technique…"

‘It's an Invisible Creature!' Black Sethe warned, ‘Careful…Void Creatures are just one of the many categories of Invisible Creatures and Invisible Creatures are just what we collectively called the creatures of the unknown world.'

‘Just now, you were moved here and the back of your fist was directed towards the knife. If you were a normal human, you would be finished!'

Garen narrowed his eyes and raised his right fist. He saw a little white spot on his fist. It was a mark left behind when he hit the knife with his strength.

He turned his head and saw that girl had fainted on the ground.

‘That girl's body seemed to have some problems. Her mind seems to have been damaged by your Fantasy Fist and it activated some kind of sense. You'd better study her for a bit.' Black Sethe said.

Boom!

A burning pillar fell on his head.

Garen smashed it to bits with a punch. The embers scattered around but he was totally unhurt.

"Hmph!" Garen snorted. He walked to the girl's side and lifted her with one hand. His body flashed as he rushed out through the hole and disappeared from the villa.

*****************

In a countryside town in Europe.

"Give me two catties of bananas, wrap them up for me."

On a street alley, a young man stood in front of a fruit stall buying bananas. He wore a mask and his body was coated in dust, looking like a traveler that had crossed a long distance to get here.

The lady seller gave him two catties of bananas wrapped in a black plastic bag.

At the moment she passed over the plastic bag, the lady seller appeared to have noticed some red spots inside the collar of the man's shirt. She seemed to have sniffed out an odor of rust and some other fishy smells mixed together.

She could not guess what smell it was at that moment.

"Thanks." The man said. On such a hot day, he was wrapped tightly in a dirty grey windbreaker that seemed to have never been washed.

Taking the bananas and handing over the money, he looked to his left and right and walked into another alley.

Taking the bananas from the bag, he peeled one of them and ate it while walking.

Turning around a corner and passing by a garbage bin.

Silently, an iron ax was raised behind him.

Pa!

Chapter 666: Intensification 2

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

The ax struck fiercely into the wall.

The man rolled forward to avoid the attack. Looking back, he did not see anyone.

"Damn! If it wasn't for the Shooting Shadow Secret Method!!" The man was furious, but he knew that even if he was at his peak condition, he would not have much chance of winning if he fought head-on with the enemy.

Mysterious and elusive, that was the enemy's modus operandi.

No matter what he did these few days, he would be attacked. His food had poison, there was a bomb under his bed and a shootout using guns with silencers at midnight. There was also backstabbing without warning.

A series of sneak attacks anywhere and anytime. No matter where he hid, the enemy would always be able to find him. There was once when he went into a toilet, a poisonous emerald green spider fell out of the toilet paper. Once bitten by this spider, if the victim was not injected with the serum within fifteen minutes, he would be beyond help. In this sort of place, not to mention the serum for this emerald green spider, a serum for a normal spider bite would not exist. Even if he was sent to the hospital, he could only wait for his death.

When Jay came all the way here, it was totally a torture. This kind of tension was what he was scared of. He could not find the enemy and could only receive attacks one-sidedly. Keeping up his vigilance anytime and anywhere for several days, he was totally overworked and his mind was on the brink of collapse.

"White Phoenix…" Jay said viciously. This horrifying killer was obviously sent by the White Phoenix, so this grudge was on White Phoenix.

He quickly took out a banana and inspected it carefully. After no abnormalities could be found, he began to peel it.

Boom!!!

An explosion occurred.

A crimson ball of fire swallowed up Jay.

His upper body was burned into cinders and was then blown backward by the impact of the explosion on a garbage bin. There was no longer any life in him.

*******************

"What!! Jay died!!" Bald head roared. He clenched his phone tightly as though he was going to break the phone.

The veins on his hands and face popped out and his complexion turned green.

Jay died…..

This was going to be a big deal….

Putting down the phone, Bald Head did not know what his feelings were like. There was a deep anger and coldness gushing out from the bottom of his heart.

It was not just him alone in the office. There were the higher ups of the Nighthawks, his wife Hera, the computer genius Angel, explosives expert Ryan… These people were those who joined the Nighthawks at the beginning and they all heard Bald Head's roar.

The expression on everyone's face fell, Jay died… The Black Uniforms were the ones providing their Boss with the ancient relics but they'd all been annihilated. Jay died and he'd been the boss of the Black Uniforms. This meant that the whole Black Uniform Organization had been wiped out.

This did not concern only the relics…

Jay was the right-hand man of the Boss. His status was equal to Bald Head's and he held great authority and a lot of connections. But now, he had died…..

"Lotus Pearl." Bald Head began, but he found that there was some tremble in his voice. "White Phoenix's Lotus Pearl."

"Where are the people we're supposed to receive?" Hera asked on the side.

"No reply, it's either we have been jammed or…" Angel said in a low voice.

Previously, they were holding an attitude of training their soldiers in handling this crisis. Now, following Jay's death and the annihilation of the Black Uniform Organization, every single person here knew what sort of storm was coming.

The fury of the Nighthawk King, how terrifying it would be.

"Just received news, an explosion had occurred at Boss' villa…. The White Phoenix's Falcon squad was annihilated," Angel said while turning the laptop in front of her around for everyone to see.

"Looks like this will be an all-out war." Bald Head said while lowering his head. Taking a cigarette and holding in his mouth, he did not light the cigarette.

No one answered him. There was a depressed and solemn atmosphere around them. Facing White Phoenix, this horrifying and extreme monster, no one could afford to relax. Night Hawk's invincible legend was completely broken by White Phoenix just now.

******************

Night time.

The bonfire crackled, releasing a yellowish red glow while illuminating the surrounding areas of the forest.

Garen and the girl in black sat under a gigantic arched root and treated it as a shelter. Around the root, the surface of the rocks and stones were covered with green moss. Small clusters of dark green thorny plants were everywhere, and inside them were full of fluttering small grey insects.

Garen sat quietly by the bonfire while fiddling it with a thick wooden stick.

"One of my subordinates died." He said.

"Must be Lotus Pearl." The petite girl hugged her knees while resting her head on top. "Gremlin must have sent her out, that dreadful woman."

"You have been abandoned." Garen continued saying.

"I know." The girl said. There was no sign of agitation, she seemed to have expected it. "Your excellent subordinate died, are you not sad in the slightest?"

"Death may not necessarily be the end, it may be a new beginning." Garen said while smiling, "Of course, in return, aren't you with me? White Phoenix's new headquarter is not that easy to find. I'm counting on you to show me the way."

"I won't show you the way!" The girl said expressionlessly.

"Never mind, I don't need you to agree," Garen said and gave her a gentle smile. The Black Uniform Organization had been completely destroyed, although there was a great loss of power previously. However, Jay had also died, and this went beyond the boundary of what Garen could tolerate. He originally thought that with the Shooting Shadow Secret Skill, normal people would not be able to pose a threat to Jay and the others. It seemed like he was wrong.

The girl felt a chill. These few days, her life had been abnormal. She sometimes had her memories and sometimes she didn't. She was unclear about what she'd done and said. A lot of times, she was not clear-headed and when she woke up, she would find herself in a completely unfamiliar place.

Everything was just like a dream. She felt that she was going to fall apart soon.

These few days, they could swagger right under other people's noses and yet be ignored completely. It was just like they were invisible whether they took a plane or a car.

Directly from America to Mexico where they were right now.

She did not know where in Mexico this place was. She only knew that when they passed by a small village, she heard people speaking Spanish in loud voices. There seemed to be no dialects mixing in their language and more like what the Indigenous people used. From what those who spoke Spanish said, this seemed to be a place in Mexico called Sidney. She did not know whether it was the name of the city or the region.

She looked at the masked man sitting in front of her. That eerie black mask made him feel mysterious yet dangerous.

If there was a chance…she hoped in her heart. Her brother was a Mexican drug lord, as long as there was a chance, she may be able to contact her brother…

"Your name is Simone right?" Garen suddenly asked.

"How did you know?" The petite girl said, alarmed.

"This time among the Primary Colors, White Phoenix finally acted. They wouldn't have just sent over little fellas like you to die right?" Garen suddenly laughed under his mask.

The girl showed a sarcastic expression.

"We already know your true identity. Someone must be on the way to Grano."

"Oh?" Garen said. "They're pretty quick."

"You're not even worried for a bit?" Simone realized and said. She had tried to escape these few days but was caught easily like he was catching little chicks, no matter what method she used. This man was always in a relaxed mood as though nothing could affect him.

She did not know why but she wanted to see a panicked and desperate look on him.

"From the moment I did not disguise myself, I already knew this was going to happen," Garen said as though there was no effect on his emotion.

"You have long prepared for this?" Simone stared at his only eye, trying to find a change in his expression from under the mask.

"Do you know what kind of people we've sent?" She said. "The Primary Colors' most elite Golden Balance Organization. Each of them has strength close to special-class mercenary. They are one of the most powerful killer organizations in the world." She stared at his eye while trying to exert pressure on him with a slow tone.

What she got in exchange was just a chuckle.

****************

Grano.

Raffaele slowly walked out of the woods while looking at the panicked group of elite killers that seemed as though they'd met a strong enemy.

The leader was wearing a white power suit that seemed as though it contained technology from the future, despite looking like ancient armor.

"The world is in my hands…"Raffaele whispered while opening her clasped hands.

Her long blond hair was dancing in the breeze as though golden threads were drifting through the sky. A dazzling light shone from her palms.

Weng…

The ground seemed to be shaking, the air seemed to be shaking and the whole forest also seemed to be shaking. An indescribable heat had gathered in her hands.

Chi!

Numerous golden lines spiraled out from her hands and shot towards the surroundings, looking like DNA double helixes.

Peng peng peng!!!

Continuous explosions occurred where the golden strands landed, dyeing the woods with blood. The killers were helpless. They'd been pursued for several days and forced into a group. They were exhausted and had reached their limits.

"Ah ah ah!! You monster!!" The leading killer screamed. He could not bear it anymore and charged with bloodshot eyes at Raffaele. However, he was surrounded by the golden strands and exploded with a bang, becoming a large cloud of bloody mist.

Raffaele raised her head, her eyes glowing.

Boom!!!

At the same time, all the killers exploded like bombs into blood mist and were absorbed by the surrounding trees and golden strands. Except for some clothes and pieces of torn cloth, there was nothing left in the place.

A breeze blew over and Raffaele disappeared from the spot.

Chapter 667: Annihilation 1

Translator: EndlessFantasy Translation Editor: EndlessFantasy Translation

Mexico, St. Jeddah

"Ha ha ha ha… Mr. Rod is indeed a man true to his words, the previous agreement has already been completed. No wonder the allies in the Alliance are convinced about Mister. It's not without reason."

In an underground cave beneath a dense forest that served as a modest white base, two groups of people dressed in suits were in a meeting. The leaders from both sides shook hands with each other. One of them had a head full of red hair and a strong body and was laughing loudly. His laughter reverberated throughout the underground hall.

"Captain White Phoenix is too polite. Naturally, we couldn't delay a request from the person-in-charge of Gremlin, so we urgently directed a batch of goods from South America and supplied it here," the person in the deep purple suit spoke. His face was full of smiles and he had a friendly look, as though he was an ordinary businessman.

After exchanging greetings with each other, the two leaders went to a separate room, sat down and ordered coffee. Several glamorous women came in and gave both sides gentle massages.

The small white room was covered with silvery-white metal walls. There were also bright green oval gems embedded in them. The gems seemed to be decorations but the dim green light that flashed from time to time proved that they were not mere decorations. There seemed to be special effects.

The redhead from White Phoenix laid on the white couch, allowing the women on the side to massage his body.

"This time, besides the shipment, Mr. Rod should have something else to discuss? Although the personnel in this new base of White Phoenix are not much, all the elites have been transferred over. So, just say anything you want."

"So generous?" Rod smiled and said. He let a woman take off his coat, revealing the white shirt below.

"You've brought us the latest Arefal materials. Without this, our armor would be just a useless piece of iron. Who would have imagined that…"

Boom.

Suddenly, a slight tremble came from the ground.

The red-haired captain's complexion became serious but he quickly reverted back to his original smiling face.

"Let me go and have a look, excuse me."

"Please go ahead." Rod made a gesture indicating that he was not offended.

The redhead walked to the door and turned around, revealing a smile.

"You can treat it as though I did not exist. Don't worry, I will not ruin the mood."

Rod mirrored his smile and indicated that he did not see anything.

Boom!!

Another loud roar.

The door closed automatically and the White Phoenix captain's expression immediately fell.

He raised his wrist. A black-haired young woman was displayed on the surface of his black bracelet.

"What happened?"

The woman answered quickly.

"An outsider had found the entrance. I'm mobilizing the surveillance…" the woman reported, but when she saw the monitor her calm facade was immediately broken.

She blinked. Suspecting that something was wrong with what she had seen, she checked the monitor once again.

"I… I see someone hitting the gate of the base… let me take a closer look… oh my goodness…"

The woman's expression suddenly became fascinated. She opened her eyes wide as though she could not believe what she'd seen. With her mouth wide open, her face froze at this moment.

"What happened?" the captain of the White Phoenix asked impatiently. He was the highest officer in charge of guarding the base and leading the core guards with the codename of White Phoenix. His position was only below Gremlin. In the absence of Gremlin, he was in charge of the whole base.

He took off the monocle over his right eye. The monocle quickly displayed rows of passwords and the passwords were soon lifted.

The surveillance footage was immediately displayed in front of him.

At that moment, his expression too became fascinated. His mouth opened slightly and became wider.

******************

Boom!!

Garen punched a hole in a thick silvery white wall. He inserted his other hand and tore open the hole.

Sila!!

He tore down a big chunk of the metallic wall. Along with the shrill alarm sound and red lights flashing, the wall emitted a piercing sound of metals being twisted, and then it was ripped off like a piece of cardboard.

Garen wore a simple black sleeveless shirt and trousers while revealing his slightly sun-tanned muscles. His muscles moved around like waves throughout his body and collected in his arms, before with some force.

Boom!!

Another punch revealed what was underneath the layer of wall, which was a deep hole going straight downwards. It seemed to be an underground elevator shaft.

Garen took a look at the surveillance camera positioned in a corner.

He could hear voices and sound of footsteps at a distance. There were also sounds of guns being adjusted.

He jumped down into this shaft with a depth that even he did not even know.

His goal was the central control room or the core control room.

There would be a core control room in any base and as long as it was under control, everything else would also be under his control.

After falling down for more than ten seconds, he could see a faint white glow at the bottom.

Both of Garen's feet landed with a loud bang and created a crater that was a few meters wide. Some of the tiny metallic parts fell out, rattling.

This base was different from the normal base. It seemed unusually small but the protection was very thick.

Garen walked out from the crater. There was a square elevator exit at his side but it was blocked by a metal door. He tore it open and went in.

Inside was a spacious warehouse-like hall. He seemed to have landed at the very bottom.

The hall was dark except for the flashes of red light from the alarm. A mechanical female voice was repeating an announcement in a language unfamiliar to Garen, hence he did not understand what it was reporting.

In the central space of the hall, there were five human figures standing on the black floor. The five figures were wearing bodysuit-like white metallic armor. Their heights were different but they all had a common point; they were all donning thin white armor and it seemed like even the place where they breathed through was covered without the slightest gap.

The leader in front stared at Garen's horrifying sun-tanned muscles, then the metallic door that had been ripped off and thrown aside. His eyelids were twitching non-stop. He was the captain of the White Phoenix, the highest officer in charge of guarding the base and leading the core guards with the codename of White Phoenix. After watching the display, he'd immediately dressed up in armor and had come to intercept to let all of the ordinary guards get away from this person.

The kind of monster that could even punch open metallic walls, ordinary guards were no match for him.

"Mister, this is the White Phoenix Base under the Primary Colors Organization, did you pick a wrong target? We don't remember offending you in any way."

Before coming here, in that short amount time, he had checked for enemies with similar features but the answer he got was none. Though this man was wearing a black mask, the characteristics of his stature and size could at least be compared.

"This is the strongest get-up that White Phoenix could assemble?" Garen looked at these five people. This white full-body armor seemed to be quite strong.

Suddenly, he took a step back. A laser swept through the place he stood just now and made a black line on the floor.

Garen's toes moved. A stone flew up and crashed directly into the laser launcher, smashing it to pieces. After a slight sound of electricity, there was no more movement.

"Remember, the one who killed you all is the Nighthawk King!" Garen stopped speaking nonsense and with a stomp, he blasted forward like a cannonball and crashed into the armored captain at the front.

His right fist could not even be seen. There was only a flash and it had already smashed into the chest of its target.

Chi chi chi…

In an instant, one laser after another shot out from the five people. Their speed was so fast that the instant they were fired, the lasers have already reached the fist that Garen punched out. Green smoke was emitted.

The foot of the armored captain made a kaka sound and propelled him backwards. His speed was only slightly slower than Garen but it was enough to dodge Garen's punch.

"Kill him!"

The captain shouted.

With some mechanical sounds, the other four armored members shot out more than ten black, fingernail-sized metal pieces that sped towards Garen from hidden locations all around.

Boom!!

One arm pierced through the captain's chest, completely ignoring the armor's defense as though it was a thin sheet of paper. The armor caved inwards, and the broken shards pierced the captain's abdomen and tore at his red flesh.

Just now, Garen had made a sudden acceleration at one moment and with an explosion, his arm, under the influence of its inertia, had pierced through the captain chest.

He slammed the captain against the wall of the base.

Only at this moment did the numerous black metal shards fly over and pierce his back.

Boom boom boom boom!!!

A series of explosions sounded.

These little black metal pieces were actually miniature bombs. A series of explosions occurred on Garen's back.

There was smoke all over the place. The other four quickly and silently stepped back without any hesitation. They appeared to be ready to escape. Their captain's current status was unknown but none of them were truly loyal to the White Phoenix. Everyone here was a mercenary, and none of them would throw away their lives for money.

"He fell down here. As long as we switch off the power, he won't be able to go up and we'll have lots of methods to deal with him! Retreat!"

"What about the captain?" a member who could not contact the captain asked.

"We won't make it! If we don't retreat now, it will be too late!"

"Go!"

These few were all ruthless mercenaries. As long as they'd made a decision, they would not hesitate. They made an agreement with their communication devices instantly.

Before the four of them finished their communication while retreating, suddenly four pieces of black metals flew over with a snap sound.

There was only a flash in front of their eyes and the metal fragments instantly arrived in front of them with an astounding speed.

Then, peng peng peng peng! After a few dull impact sounds, the four of them were sent flying and crashed into the wall. Incredibly, none of their bodies had been separated into halves. They seemed to be merely unconscious.